 <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-02-20 Saturday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>LKE (20) HYPE=10, GAMBLE=0</mention>
  <mention>XST (19) GAMBLE=0, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>BIT (13) HYPE=8, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>LOT (12) TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>BET (9) HYPE=16</mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="udunnomedoyou" created="2021-02-20 15:02:10+10:00">
   <body>Is z1p expected to go up on the 25th after their announcement? Would buying zip below $14 be worth it before the 25th? Ofc all just thoughts no one really knows</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 15:21:38+10:00">
    <body>Who knows... But their quarterly results were great. So it's reasonably safe to assume their half yearly will be good. Plus the anticipation of US investors/listings is promising.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="udunnomedoyou" created="2021-02-20 16:07:11+10:00" sentiment="TIP 10">
     <body>I was thinking of buying on monday anything below $14. Reckon it would go lower than $12 by 25th?</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 16:14:16+10:00">
      <body>Again, who knows, but I wouldn't bet on it. Watch it Monday and see what it does. I suspect the drop on Thursday and Friday was down to a level of consolidation and support.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Genghiskhanbrah" created="2021-02-20 17:57:32+10:00">
      <body>I put an order to in on Sunday night at 12.xx. Within the first hour of market open on Monday it went up to 14.xx, I ended up getting in at 13.90 and it’s since dropped and slowly climbed again over the week but I’m still in the red. I’m anticipating it to do the same thing this coming week. If you haven’t DYOR on it yet, it’s a fairly volatile stock, seems to go down on good announcements but overall I like it and in my opinion it’s a better company than Afterpay. I’ll be holding longterm. 

Not a financial adviser, DYOR &amp; DD etc.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ASXSpecLandKing" created="2021-02-20 19:16:11+10:00">
    <body>Pick up any news paper from the weekend and read about retail spending - if Z1p and APT don’t absolutely cream this report then I’ll be shocked. 

It’s about HOW well they cream it - I think they will knock it out of the park and will spend a few sessions re rating to $20.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-02-20 20:07:57+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>The stock tripled in price over the last few weeks.

Heck it was trading at like $3 last time it put out it’s first half yearly report (for FY2020). It showed it had increased its loss from -$8m in 2018 to like -$30m in 2019.

In all likelihood it’s report will show that despite the amazing “customer growf” they flog in their trading updates every chance they get it has probably recorded and even larger loss this year than last year.

Like go read their actual cash flow and profit statements buried on page 70 of their annual report. They lose money on every transaction because the cost of sales/operations/financing/bad debts are higher than the revenue they take in from operations.

Share price that tripled in 3 months on negative profit growth. How do you think the market will react when it comes out?</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="happylosers" created="2021-02-20 15:04:36+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>Definitely buy buy buy 🚀🚀</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="ohJewJew" created="2021-02-20 15:24:53+10:00">
   <body>Am I the only one holding XST?</body>
   <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="BoisterousBeagle" created="2021-02-20 15:47:29+10:00">
    <body>Holding forever. It's not a loss till you sell.</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="StrethAU" created="2021-02-20 18:13:38+10:00">
     <body>Agreed, I'll hold till I die and let my kids cop the loss. I refuse to take the red</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-02-20 17:08:54+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>Nope, you’re not alone.

 I’m gonna wait  for a pump then offload most of my XST shares, but only because after the last week I’ve learned the high risk, high reward play is not my style.

I’ve done even more DD after the shit storm that was this week, and still think there’s still potential for 2-3 bagger in the short term. So I will probably keep 1/3 of my shares.

The downrampers are not entirely wrong with their analysis but they are also exaggerating a lot of it, just as the pumpers are. (Downrampers love to use worst-case scenario figures and pumpers love to use best-case figures, to prove their respective points). I like to do my own DD and not listen to either of these parties.

The good thing about this situation is we won’t have to wait long to figure out whether to continue holding, or cut our losses. Spud announcement is imminent and drilling will only take about a month.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-20 16:31:29+10:00">
    <body>Still in . I wanna see how this plays out. I don’t get swayed by pumpers or downrampers, I am my own retard.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-02-20 16:29:29+10:00">
    <body>Nah mate holding as well, nothing is ever as bad as people make it out to be... hopefully</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="TradeCarefully" created="2021-02-20 19:53:58+10:00">
    <body>Holding both XST and SGC until I see that red turns green.. patience is the name of the game</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="martin0000001" created="2021-02-20 15:29:49+10:00">
    <body>Don’t worry lad me and some of the boys still with you stay strong I feel your pain</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="PastPrestigious230" created="2021-02-20 17:32:36+10:00">
    <body>Aye brother I’m holding the lines. In at 0.013</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Tranquilbull" created="2021-02-20 15:29:30+10:00">
    <body>I got out after I read the Mods post, Sugeknight...

Gave me the heebie jeebies, I wasn’t comfortable holding over the weekend with the directors day trading their shares</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-02-20 15:31:32+10:00">
     <body>Suge is not a mod</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 15:54:53+10:00">
      <body>I am the Captain now (not a mod lol)</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Tranquilbull" created="2021-02-20 15:41:48+10:00">
      <body>My bad</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-20 15:55:05+10:00">
     <body>You realise he bought back in at 0.08 😂😂</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 16:00:31+10:00">
      <body>No I didn't (also am not a mod guys)</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-20 16:06:53+10:00">
       <body>Hmm remember reading that in a daily thread. My apologies mate</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 16:14:47+10:00">
        <body>All good bro :) In my post I mentioned a guys DD , and he is the one who bought back in at 0.08</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-20 17:09:00+10:00">
    <body>Still holding. I add knowledge that post the other morning and it may well be true but if it is a true “scam” I think there is going to be some overhyped announcements while drilling which will move the SP. 

I put in what I was willing to lose ($2000). Bought at $0.012 so I’m even.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="BuggeredBudgie" created="2021-02-20 18:09:21+10:00">
    <body>Bought at 0.018 still holding and not letting go</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="isnotabaker" created="2021-02-20 15:31:02+10:00">
    <body>Got out at a loss. Something just feels off. It might rocket but not gonna risk it personally.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="boy_pikoy" created="2021-02-20 15:36:25+10:00">
     <body>SAme here,Something feels off, i back out when i was about to buy and YOLO!!!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="AhjiAhjo" created="2021-02-20 21:36:33+10:00">
    <body>Bought in at 0.019 and 0.015, will most likely wait and see the drilling results. Will sell once it goes green!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="sirstonkalicious" created="2021-02-20 18:09:47+10:00">
    <body>*smashes fists into chest* ape see report. Ape can't read. Ape buy more. We ape together.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-20 18:40:46+10:00">
    <body>I've put in a sell order 1 pip higher than my buy in, if drilling results are miraculously good then I'm in the queue comparatively early to at least get out adequately on hype wave 2.  

If results suck then I'll sell at market to recover (hopefully) half my capital to use it elsewhere and if there's any balance I'll leave it in for a few years until the next hype for the next well somewhere, and sell them.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="elpamyelhsa" created="2021-02-20 21:24:32+10:00">
    <body>Drilling updates due soon, confident this will be pocket rocket. Here’s hoping.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Theme8958" created="2021-02-20 12:03:08+10:00">
   <body>I’m I the only one still holding LkE and BRN⁉️🥲</body>
   <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="MotorParsnip9039" created="2021-02-20 12:05:18+10:00">
    <body>I've still got LKE 😀... and XST😒</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-02-20 12:37:22+10:00">
    <body>Sold my LKE for SGC the other day cos I'm all about the those 200IQ plays 😢</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Theme8958" created="2021-02-20 14:34:24+10:00">
     <body>How’s that working for you bro? Do you regret it</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-02-20 14:55:05+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
      <body>hard to tell yet, latest couple of red days has me low key spooked but im going to wait and see how it play out. if they can manage to start pumping gas ill def make a profit, it just going to take a few weeks and not going to be the multi bag rocket i assumed</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Asxnewb" created="2021-02-20 13:31:53+10:00">
    <body>I’m holding LKE at least till June/July</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Theme8958" created="2021-02-20 14:33:41+10:00">
     <body>I think there might be an announcement or meeting on March 11th</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Fit-Woodpecker-9308" created="2021-02-20 12:24:51+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>I’m holding Brainchip! Massive potential for share price growth if the market wakes up!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 14:32:51+10:00">
    <body>Honestly if this Roth Capital pump thing works then I might bail out soon. Wouldn't be mad at like a 20-50% return on this thing then I'll dump it in to something else.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="WimpParsnip" created="2021-02-19 18:23:20+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
   <body>The last few weeks my 80% profit on CXO has now gone back down to 0%. I wasn’t expecting it to go lower than 23-24c after the CR. CXO seems like a good buy but I must be wrong and clearly suck at this.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Dunengel" created="2021-02-19 18:33:15+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>I think it’s gone from having massive-gains-quick potential to a long term hold. It’ll regain 0.25 in the short term and long term I’d hope it hits 0.50+.

However I’m a retard that’s typing this with my feet so ya know GLTAH DYOR NFA</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-19 18:39:13+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>Same mate. Was up by a few thousand, now I'm currently holding a couple hundred in profit. I'm gonna hold and top up. I believe it has potential, and so should you.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="noirstorm" created="2021-02-19 18:13:38+10:00">
   <body>Av1 continues to let me down fml</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SignalGlittering4671" created="2021-02-19 19:02:54+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>Not much growth in ad spending in 2020 even a decline in some sectors / countries.

30/10-2020 over 50 paying customers (25% increase)

27/01-2021 over 100 paying customers (83% increase over September 2020 numbers)

They expect to convert a bunch of free users to paying users in March 2021.

Some ramblings about big international names.

The competition certainly has adds out on the keyword Trafficguard to try and redirect users away from Adveritas, maybe they are on to something about the quality of the product.

revenue up 9% to 263k, pretty good when US ad spending hardly grew and Australian spending is down.  If you look at RnD and Marketing/sales as an investment in the future and not an expense it looks good too I think.

It's still on my list of ASX\_bets stocks to watch maybe buy, even after the whole pickle thing.

With all that said you might want to sell because I suck at picking rockets

[https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1004510/AV1\_Quarterly\_Activities\_Report\_Appendix\_4C](https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1004510/AV1_Quarterly_Activities_Report_Appendix_4C)

[https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1016843/AV1\_Quarterly\_Activities\_Report\_Appendix\_4C](https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1016843/AV1_Quarterly_Activities_Report_Appendix_4C)

&amp;#x200B;

Edit :(wan to to -&gt; want)</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-19 18:16:33+10:00">
    <body>I'm still green but I was way more green before.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="happylosers" created="2021-02-20 09:57:13+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Lke lads holding about to get rewarded 🚀 Topped up on some EGR, it’s so cheap right now. Next week it will 🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BoisterousBeagle" created="2021-02-20 12:19:37+10:00">
    <body>XST is also cheap right now...so it'll rocket to right....RIGHT??</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="buffalo_bill27" created="2021-02-20 12:49:31+10:00">
     <body>Why the negs??? XST is cheap and undervalued according to Morninglory.

I reckon it's a great buy
*Not financial advice</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-20 07:53:25+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>My friend started trading in crypto at the same time I did on small caps, dude is up 400% in 2 months. Fuck my life, LRS better 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-20 09:08:31+10:00">
    <body>I know crypto talk is frowned up but it's worth putting some $ into Alts that haven't pumped imo.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-20 08:59:40+10:00">
    <body>I'm a late bloomer and dropped into bitcoin as soon as I heard Tesla bought in I basically ran to the laptop.....I'm up 20% on that it's beating my portfolio 🙄</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 10:36:19+10:00">
    <body>&gt; dude is up 400% in 2 months

What coins?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-20 10:41:15+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
     <body>Ravencoin bruh 🚀🚀🚀</body>
     <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 12:17:22+10:00">
      <body>Never heard of it but I am going to yolo everything into it</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="YungLeesy" created="2021-02-21 09:06:17+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Give me a N
Give me a V
Give me a X
What does that spell
🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-02-21 09:18:28+10:00">
    <body>Cash</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="55" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 20:33:09+10:00">
   <body>Crystal ball for next week - 
* DW8 options expire on Tuesday and I'm expecting to test 6 cents during the week
* LKE might get some early battery testing results, regardless it'll test .4 and break through
* NVX will probably retrace until more details around the microgrid partnership battery revenue is announced
* I expect SWF to rebound a little on Monday, finishing green
* APT will test 160 for absolutely no reason
* IOU to hover around .50 when the new shares hit the market
* ASIA to have a bigger percentage gain next week than FANG

If absolutely none of the above happens, I'll take a weeks ban. u/username-taken82 I'm back for more pain. 

Edit: Don't just downvote me because I've made an adverse prediction about your stock. Challenge me as to why I have that assumption.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="username-taken82" created="2021-02-19 20:41:10+10:00">
    <body>You’re an animal...</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="PopGotcha44" created="2021-02-19 22:15:59+10:00">
    <body>ill send you a shiraz if DW8 cracks 6.5</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 22:34:34+10:00">
     <body>Bring on some new ATH's</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-19 20:49:21+10:00">
    <body>I’m with you on DW8...don’t hold it but nice to see it break out from the weight of option exercise</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-02-19 20:41:17+10:00">
    <body>I hope one of those things happens.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="queens_third_corgi" created="2021-02-19 20:54:18+10:00">
    <body>What’s the assumption on lke? They had an update today.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 21:23:30+10:00">
     <body>They had a presentation to the OTC market in America, nothing we didn't already know TBH. However, they have mentioned in interviews that we could get a battery update late Feb, early March.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-19 21:31:08+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
      <body>Also they had a broker rate them with a price target of 60 cents 🚀🚀</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="queens_third_corgi" created="2021-02-19 21:31:11+10:00">
      <body>Thanks man.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-02-19 21:14:08+10:00">
    <body>What about Z1p?</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 21:22:04+10:00">
     <body>If I buy it it'll go down.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-02-19 21:23:32+10:00">
      <body>Ok my grandma asks that you don't buy that you redirect your attention</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="werty3555" created="2021-02-19 21:44:46+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
     <body>Holding solid on zip has the potential to be a $20 stock within a short time frame imo if it dips low enough for me I'm doubling down</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-02-19 21:17:39+10:00">
    <body>Ooohhh, tell me about the ASIANS again...</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 21:24:40+10:00">
     <body>Decent etf and one of the easiest ways to gain exposure to stocks that would otherwise be difficult to buy.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kervio" created="2021-02-19 21:56:58+10:00">
    <body>I reckon you're safe.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-02-19 22:45:29+10:00">
    <body>RemindMe! 1 week.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-02-19 22:58:49+10:00">
    <body>&gt;hope one of those things happens.

IXR deposit report out this week hopefully....</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-20 01:21:42+10:00">
    <body>Nice balling. Reckon you're pretty safe on your ban bet.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="werty3555" created="2021-02-19 21:21:46+10:00">
   <body>Expecting RLT to have a slight boost with vaccines rolling out 
They use helium to keep the vaccines colder for longer instead of dry ice which is more costly to make and consumes more space during transport</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-19 22:01:20+10:00">
    <body>I’d like to see them monetize it first...</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 21:29:14+10:00">
    <body>Cuuuuunt RLT is the shit we are parachuting vaccines to villagers pump the fuck outta this</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="werty3555" created="2021-02-19 21:31:22+10:00">
     <body>Why is nobody talking about it we need to jump on this before it hit $5-6 and we're all regreting it</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-20 16:43:11+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
      <body>It jumped to $3 not too long ago and I think it will head back there very soon. Very exciting to read about!</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="69" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-02-19 19:02:15+10:00">
  <body>Stocks were more fun when I was making money</body>
  <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-02-19 19:03:31+10:00">
   <body>And fuck being banned for a week. Not being able to make fun of big loss porn feels just like a weekend</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="aegistwelve" created="2021-02-20 10:07:34+10:00">
   <body>wait you guys were making money?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="55" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 20:33:09+10:00">
  <body>Crystal ball for next week - 
* DW8 options expire on Tuesday and I'm expecting to test 6 cents during the week
* LKE might get some early battery testing results, regardless it'll test .4 and break through
* NVX will probably retrace until more details around the microgrid partnership battery revenue is announced
* I expect SWF to rebound a little on Monday, finishing green
* APT will test 160 for absolutely no reason
* IOU to hover around .50 when the new shares hit the market
* ASIA to have a bigger percentage gain next week than FANG

If absolutely none of the above happens, I'll take a weeks ban. u/username-taken82 I'm back for more pain. 

Edit: Don't just downvote me because I've made an adverse prediction about your stock. Challenge me as to why I have that assumption.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="username-taken82" created="2021-02-19 20:41:10+10:00">
   <body>You’re an animal...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="PopGotcha44" created="2021-02-19 22:15:59+10:00">
   <body>ill send you a shiraz if DW8 cracks 6.5</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 22:34:34+10:00">
    <body>Bring on some new ATH's</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-19 20:49:21+10:00">
   <body>I’m with you on DW8...don’t hold it but nice to see it break out from the weight of option exercise</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-02-19 20:41:17+10:00">
   <body>I hope one of those things happens.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="queens_third_corgi" created="2021-02-19 20:54:18+10:00">
   <body>What’s the assumption on lke? They had an update today.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 21:23:30+10:00">
    <body>They had a presentation to the OTC market in America, nothing we didn't already know TBH. However, they have mentioned in interviews that we could get a battery update late Feb, early March.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-19 21:31:08+10:00">
     <body>Also they had a broker rate them with a price target of 60 cents 🚀🚀</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="queens_third_corgi" created="2021-02-19 21:31:11+10:00">
     <body>Thanks man.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-02-19 21:14:08+10:00">
   <body>What about Z1p?</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 21:22:04+10:00">
    <body>If I buy it it'll go down.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-02-19 21:23:32+10:00">
     <body>Ok my grandma asks that you don't buy that you redirect your attention</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="werty3555" created="2021-02-19 21:44:46+10:00">
    <body>Holding solid on zip has the potential to be a $20 stock within a short time frame imo if it dips low enough for me I'm doubling down</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-02-19 21:17:39+10:00">
   <body>Ooohhh, tell me about the ASIANS again...</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-19 21:24:40+10:00">
    <body>Decent etf and one of the easiest ways to gain exposure to stocks that would otherwise be difficult to buy.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kervio" created="2021-02-19 21:56:58+10:00">
   <body>I reckon you're safe.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-02-19 22:45:29+10:00">
   <body>RemindMe! 1 week.</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-02-19 22:58:49+10:00">
   <body>&gt;hope one of those things happens.

IXR deposit report out this week hopefully....</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-20 01:21:42+10:00">
   <body>Nice balling. Reckon you're pretty safe on your ban bet.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="47" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-02-19 18:58:24+10:00">
  <body>Not a terrible week, only lost like 60k</body>
  <comment ups="40" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-19 19:05:12+10:00">
   <body>-$156k 😭</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 19:07:49+10:00">
    <body>Yikes</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 19:26:50+10:00">
    <body>This coming Monday +250k I’m sure of it for you</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-19 21:03:05+10:00">
     <body>I’ve got to +$250k intra-day before but never closed a day up that much. Maybe one day.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="ShoddyClue7113" created="2021-02-19 19:21:25+10:00">
    <body>Holy moly</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 19:28:10+10:00">
    <body>XST hurt you too?</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-19 19:29:56+10:00">
     <body>Haha no chance, looked like a PnD to me</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-02-20 07:05:29+10:00">
      <body>It was literally a gamble on results. Like almost every other spec mining company on the asx</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-20 07:34:52+10:00">
       <body>Why not both?</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-02-19 20:04:58+10:00">
   <body>Only a loss if you sold - did you</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-02-20 07:04:35+10:00">
    <body>Not all bad, went from plus 100k to plus 38k. Some of it sold out and im still up 40k from this year alone in realised gains. &lt;3 xst/lrsoc</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="alg1979" created="2021-02-19 19:03:07+10:00">
   <body>Hate that for you</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Goody55" created="2021-02-19 19:09:13+10:00">
   <body>Whats the dog stock?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="49" downs="0" author="Truck-Deep" created="2021-02-20 01:40:04+10:00">
  <body>These posts like “can’t wait till Monday, what even is weekend” make me sad. Enjoy your time off Cunts, if you’re not making money so you can have infinite weekends then why you here</body>
  <comment ups="46" downs="0" author="Mitchuation" created="2021-02-20 06:12:21+10:00">
   <body>Bro I agree with you but you sent this shit at 3am. Might be time for some introspection</body>
   <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-20 07:15:26+10:00">
    <body>Clearly he was out racking lines with his boys</body>
    <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="biscobisco" created="2021-02-20 07:28:34+10:00">
     <body>Quick philosophical post from a cooked Uber ride - why naht?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Truck-Deep" created="2021-02-20 12:17:46+10:00">
      <body>Hahahah fuck you got me</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-20 15:30:00+10:00">
     <body>On the RAC</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Almighti3" created="2021-02-20 06:10:41+10:00">
   <body>Some are addicted to the thrill of it, like gamblers.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-20 07:18:10+10:00">
    <body>“Like”?</body>
    <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-20 07:35:08+10:00">
     <body>No, it's LKE, lake. Autocorrect gets me all the time too.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="41" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-19 18:17:15+10:00">
  <body>Fucking fuck. 

That is all.</body>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 18:35:46+10:00">
   <body>Cmon Jimbo, take the green pill already ☢️☢️☢️</body>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-19 19:13:14+10:00">
    <body>It's my fear that i've missed it and when i invest you will all lose your money</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 20:08:12+10:00">
     <body>If that's all it takes to finish us, we didn't deserve the gains in the first place ☢☢</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-19 20:33:13+10:00">
      <body>Lol,  true.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-02-20 21:43:59+10:00">
     <body>Go look at the URA.nys chart, then zoom out a few years.

You haven't missed it, it's just that nobody is really sure if this is it or not</body>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="The-Slippery-Wizard" created="2021-02-19 18:44:30+10:00">
   <body>Its only 10k gone its still good its still good</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-19 19:13:54+10:00">
    <body>Close to 20k since the end of January. :(</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-19 22:26:58+10:00">
     <body>I bought SBW when it fell and i might break even with that but RRL fell and I bought that it fell more and then I bought JAT and it fell too. 

I can't help but day trade after watching BD1, FFG and others.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="The-Slippery-Wizard" created="2021-02-19 21:55:52+10:00">
     <body>The 10k was this week for me, I have had some other losers but ihl, lke and rfx have kept me whole. But I may have to lock in some of those losses.
When I think about the losses lately I think how far I've come since march the 22nd, I bet if you look back on your year its pretty fucking good.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Darcyjay_" created="2021-02-19 19:10:34+10:00">
   <body>Here here</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="37" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-19 19:10:18+10:00">
  <body>Ok peeps, 3100 pushups, pull ups and sit ups. You guys are absolute freaks but I'll do it. 

I was only expecting maybe 50 likes, which is still a fuck ton, but hey ho. 

Obviously I can't do all of those in one day, so I offer two options. 

1 : I do it all, but over the course of multiple days 

2 : I spend 1 WHOLE day doing it, seeing how much I can get though over the course of 24 hours. I think I could probably get a lot done, or end up hospitalized. Either way.

Completely up to you guys, most upvoted response to this comment will be the option I do. 

Otherwise, keeping buying the LKE dip and enjoy the weekend!

*Edit*

Have gone with option 2. Will be doing that on Tuesday me thinks, expect record high LKE movement on that day!

Just found out the fucking world record for pull-ups in a day is 7000 LOL ok I'm doing that last. 

3000 pushups will suck, but I think I can do it. 

3000 sit ups is probably harder then the pushups. So I'll do that second.</body>
  <comment ups="33" downs="0" author="HomerQuotingHomer" created="2021-02-19 19:26:50+10:00">
   <body>A WHOLE 24 hours of doing as many push ups, sit ups and pull ups as possible will completely fuck you up. You'll be fucking broken. 

I vote for that.

Edit: my comment is getting upvoted but I don't want you to do this because I think you'll hurt yourself. This edit will probably mean more upvotes.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="28" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-19 19:57:28+10:00">
   <body>What about if you eat just a little tiny bit of you're own poo poo. Prob be easier.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 19:26:22+10:00">
   <body>3100 each?

🤔

Nah man, unless you've been doing them for a while you aren't knocking them out in one day.

I vote 2 days, no trading over the weekend anyway. Get the boyfriend to take the wife out so you can focus.
Make sure you stretch. First day feels alright, 2nd day is pain!</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-19 20:10:52+10:00">
    <body>Yes 3100 each haha. 

Don't tempt me man, I thrive off people telling me it's not possible and then proving them wrong haha</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="sirstonkalicious" created="2021-02-19 20:41:31+10:00">
     <body>1000% impossible to do this. Definitley cannot be done....can it?</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-19 21:15:37+10:00">
      <body>Fucking option 2 it is. I'll take 2 days off work next week so I have a day to recover. LETS FUCKING GOOOOOO</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="sirstonkalicious" created="2021-02-20 06:22:50+10:00">
       <body>In all seriousness, stay safe fellow autismo. An entire day of push/sit ups would be brutal.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ImHiFunctioning" created="2021-02-19 21:40:03+10:00">
     <body>It's just not possible for someone to sell everything and then go all in on Z1P...</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="loaf-of-breddit" created="2021-02-20 22:26:47+10:00">
     <body>It's not possible. This is the opposite of Autist.</body>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="comninos" created="2021-02-19 19:49:00+10:00">
   <body>Spread it out over a few days you dont wanna end up with rhabdos and kidney failure</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="BigKevStocking" created="2021-02-19 20:12:24+10:00">
    <body>I got rhabdo from a burpee challenge.  Didn't even know over exercising could ever be a bad thing.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 12:23:13+10:00">
    <body>&gt; and kidney failure

You can get kidney failure from exercise?

&gt;rhabdos

Wtf is that?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="comninos" created="2021-02-20 14:45:01+10:00">
     <body>Your muscles breakdown into your bloodstream and your kidneys arent designed to deal with the shit that gets released when this happens and shit gets all funky and then they fail</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="willybhoy1" created="2021-02-19 20:02:15+10:00">
   <body>No 2. 

2.15 push ups a minute for 24 hrs? Go get em tiger! 

I have no idea why you are doo g this but if it was a bet then man the fuck up and be good on yer word. Good luck and god speed</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-02-19 19:53:51+10:00">
   <body>2 absolutely.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CyclexLifts" created="2021-02-20 11:29:25+10:00">
   <body>As a fellow ape, I will offer to take upon 20% of your struggle in hopes that BPH comes out with NOPTA approval before I die.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="33" downs="0" author="BillyZaneTrain" created="2021-02-20 14:56:43+10:00">
  <body>4DS - Waiting for this sucker to fly (hopefully) and hold on for dear life until it gets bought out (even more hopefully)

AVA - Hoping it'll be heading on an upwards trajectory, albeit slowly slowly slowly

LKE/NVX - The dynamic duo; thinking these two are a tandem team and should do well together but shouldn't fall apart together. Holding these for the long haul.

LRS - Strapped in for the results rocket when it comes out next Millennium

NVA - My achey breaky heart

PEN - Microwaving my nuts every couple of hours just so they get used to the coming nuclear renaissance

VML - Do something...</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="28" downs="0" author="DJ_B0B" created="2021-02-19 18:50:58+10:00">
  <body>My portfolio was so good until the dog cunts at SGC fucked it up. Legit sp would be fine if they didn't fuck us with the unlisted options and ceo sells.

1st and last time I break my own rule of not buying from cunts who did holes. 99% are rat bastards.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-02-19 22:50:41+10:00">
   <body>Agree</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="ASXg0d" created="2021-02-19 19:23:25+10:00">
  <body>Cunts, enjoy 2 days without losses!</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Impossible-Magician" created="2021-02-19 19:43:13+10:00">
   <body>We’ve still got the NYSE session at 1:30am.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="KrondorMocker" created="2021-02-19 19:42:00+10:00">
   <body>......nobody mention bitcoin to me at all. Shhh!!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="27" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-19 19:44:43+10:00">
  <body>ROFL hot copper is a Boomer treasure trove.
Check this out 

https://i.imgur.com/soJeGZK.jpg

The response

https://i.imgur.com/6NL7rVU.jpg</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="yogaisnow" created="2021-02-20 10:53:31+10:00">
  <body>Appears that Roth Capital is going to start pumping LKE (probably have already started) after they upgraded it to a buy rating with a target of 60c</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-20 11:03:00+10:00">
   <body>Wouldn't be mad about a double bagger 🤞</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="MajorPlay4839" created="2021-02-20 11:06:08+10:00">
   <body>So good</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mantyq" created="2021-02-20 13:01:24+10:00">
   <body>May i ask where you hear about this?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-20 15:07:16+10:00">
    <body>Well you can google it. Read the report. Come back and join the discussion.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-20 17:35:18+10:00">
     <body>&gt;Roth Capital

[https://www.reddit.com/r/WallStreetbetsELITE/comments/lmy7r0/roth\_capital\_has\_just\_initiated\_coverage\_on\_lake/](https://www.reddit.com/r/WallStreetbetsELITE/comments/lmy7r0/roth_capital_has_just_initiated_coverage_on_lake/)

LKE, . It can double in price and then its priced in production. How is that a good bet?</body>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="happylosers" created="2021-02-20 09:57:13+10:00">
  <body>Lke lads holding about to get rewarded 🚀 Topped up on some EGR, it’s so cheap right now. Next week it will 🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BoisterousBeagle" created="2021-02-20 12:19:37+10:00">
   <body>XST is also cheap right now...so it'll rocket to right....RIGHT??</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="buffalo_bill27" created="2021-02-20 12:49:31+10:00">
    <body>Why the negs??? XST is cheap and undervalued according to Morninglory.

I reckon it's a great buy
*Not financial advice</body>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="michaelbellturner" created="2021-02-19 21:00:52+10:00">
  <body>Anyone looking to buy LRS on Monday?</body>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 21:25:52+10:00">
   <body>Some hobo at the bus station told me Elon Musk is looking to acquire the company, do with that what you will.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="michaelbellturner" created="2021-02-19 21:39:23+10:00">
    <body>Sounds a legit tip</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="cheebaihai" created="2021-02-19 23:33:38+10:00">
    <body>Trust all hobos, bus station is a 88x believe bonus</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-19 21:54:26+10:00">
  <body>Every stock on HC is seriously undervalued right now</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-02-19 21:55:35+10:00">
   <body>especially HT8</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-19 21:59:09+10:00">
    <body>💯</body>
    <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-19 22:14:22+10:00">
     <body>yea its seriously undervalued if you are bag holding forever.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="workoutsesh" created="2021-02-20 22:22:57+10:00">
  <body>I've done a decent bit of DD recently on a few companies. They're not rockets, but I definitely think they will do well in the short term and long term (one is a safe bet, can be a few bags in LT). You autists want a proper DD post? I'll likely post on Monday  
edit: after XST i've learnt my lesson to do my DD, and fuck oil/gas/mining companies</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="imapassenger1" created="2021-02-21 07:07:43+10:00">
   <body>I saw the hype about XST and said "I'm not investing in old world carbon polluters" and then days later bought in near the top. FOMO is real but at least it will be a cheapish lesson never to do it again.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-21 08:12:41+10:00">
    <body>dont be too hard on yourself. the results could have been better and we'd all be high fiving</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 08:24:51+10:00">
    <body>It was a strong gamble, didn't pay off.
It you had considered it, but didn't buy in, and the results were huge - you would have been writing the opposite story now about how you missed out due to hesitating.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="yogaisnow" created="2021-02-19 20:51:38+10:00">
  <body>LKE &amp; NVX came through on a red day for me</body>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="BoisterousBeagle" created="2021-02-19 20:53:25+10:00">
   <body>LKE was the band-aid applied to my ripped asshole after XST got through this week.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 20:59:33+10:00">
  <body>American Uranium miners are rallying in premarket  following their dip yesterday, the show goes on ☢☢☢</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="trashbets" created="2021-02-19 21:53:40+10:00">
  <body>My asshole is so sore from XST i don't think I can handle the weekend of coke and hookers I've got planned</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-19 22:14:56+10:00">
   <body>well you need more pepper with lube. After you can't feel anything.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="RockyRoaded" created="2021-02-20 09:26:57+10:00">
   <body>Right there with ya 

Feeling more fingered than a passed out  22 year old in a liberal politicians office</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 12:10:20+10:00">
   <body>Ask the hookers to use the little strap on</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 20:50:34+10:00">
  <body>Alright so I’m m drunk as fuck, staring down at my red portfolio. But I just count that as a subscription to this fuckery of a sub. Love you all.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 20:52:21+10:00">
   <body>Love you too cunt 😘</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 21:20:04+10:00">
    <body>Cunt I wish nothing but green pastures and fat lines of RAC for you x</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 21:21:31+10:00">
     <body>We're fucked up and gonna make it</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="agree-with-you" created="2021-02-19 20:52:32+10:00">
    <body>I love you both</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 20:53:12+10:00">
     <body>My liver hates all three of us lmao</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="alg1979" created="2021-02-19 21:08:36+10:00">
   <body>Treasure you forever more</body>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 22:06:17+10:00">
    <body>The real profits were the mates we made along the way</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 21:20:30+10:00">
    <body>Stonks only go up my brother we are all going to make it x</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="ohJewJew" created="2021-02-20 15:24:53+10:00">
  <body>Am I the only one holding XST?</body>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="BoisterousBeagle" created="2021-02-20 15:47:29+10:00">
   <body>Holding forever. It's not a loss till you sell.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="StrethAU" created="2021-02-20 18:13:38+10:00">
    <body>Agreed, I'll hold till I die and let my kids cop the loss. I refuse to take the red</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-02-20 17:08:54+10:00">
   <body>Nope, you’re not alone.

 I’m gonna wait  for a pump then offload most of my XST shares, but only because after the last week I’ve learned the high risk, high reward play is not my style.

I’ve done even more DD after the shit storm that was this week, and still think there’s still potential for 2-3 bagger in the short term. So I will probably keep 1/3 of my shares.

The downrampers are not entirely wrong with their analysis but they are also exaggerating a lot of it, just as the pumpers are. (Downrampers love to use worst-case scenario figures and pumpers love to use best-case figures, to prove their respective points). I like to do my own DD and not listen to either of these parties.

The good thing about this situation is we won’t have to wait long to figure out whether to continue holding, or cut our losses. Spud announcement is imminent and drilling will only take about a month.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-20 16:31:29+10:00">
   <body>Still in . I wanna see how this plays out. I don’t get swayed by pumpers or downrampers, I am my own retard.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-02-20 16:29:29+10:00">
   <body>Nah mate holding as well, nothing is ever as bad as people make it out to be... hopefully</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="TradeCarefully" created="2021-02-20 19:53:58+10:00">
   <body>Holding both XST and SGC until I see that red turns green.. patience is the name of the game</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="martin0000001" created="2021-02-20 15:29:49+10:00">
   <body>Don’t worry lad me and some of the boys still with you stay strong I feel your pain</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="PastPrestigious230" created="2021-02-20 17:32:36+10:00">
   <body>Aye brother I’m holding the lines. In at 0.013</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Tranquilbull" created="2021-02-20 15:29:30+10:00">
   <body>I got out after I read the Mods post, Sugeknight...

Gave me the heebie jeebies, I wasn’t comfortable holding over the weekend with the directors day trading their shares</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-02-20 15:31:32+10:00">
    <body>Suge is not a mod</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 15:54:53+10:00">
     <body>I am the Captain now (not a mod lol)</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Tranquilbull" created="2021-02-20 15:41:48+10:00">
     <body>My bad</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-20 15:55:05+10:00">
    <body>You realise he bought back in at 0.08 😂😂</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 16:00:31+10:00">
     <body>No I didn't (also am not a mod guys)</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-20 16:06:53+10:00">
      <body>Hmm remember reading that in a daily thread. My apologies mate</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 16:14:47+10:00">
       <body>All good bro :) In my post I mentioned a guys DD , and he is the one who bought back in at 0.08</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-20 17:09:00+10:00">
   <body>Still holding. I add knowledge that post the other morning and it may well be true but if it is a true “scam” I think there is going to be some overhyped announcements while drilling which will move the SP. 

I put in what I was willing to lose ($2000). Bought at $0.012 so I’m even.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="BuggeredBudgie" created="2021-02-20 18:09:21+10:00">
   <body>Bought at 0.018 still holding and not letting go</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="isnotabaker" created="2021-02-20 15:31:02+10:00">
   <body>Got out at a loss. Something just feels off. It might rocket but not gonna risk it personally.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="boy_pikoy" created="2021-02-20 15:36:25+10:00">
    <body>SAme here,Something feels off, i back out when i was about to buy and YOLO!!!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="AhjiAhjo" created="2021-02-20 21:36:33+10:00">
   <body>Bought in at 0.019 and 0.015, will most likely wait and see the drilling results. Will sell once it goes green!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="sirstonkalicious" created="2021-02-20 18:09:47+10:00">
   <body>*smashes fists into chest* ape see report. Ape can't read. Ape buy more. We ape together.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-20 18:40:46+10:00">
   <body>I've put in a sell order 1 pip higher than my buy in, if drilling results are miraculously good then I'm in the queue comparatively early to at least get out adequately on hype wave 2.  

If results suck then I'll sell at market to recover (hopefully) half my capital to use it elsewhere and if there's any balance I'll leave it in for a few years until the next hype for the next well somewhere, and sell them.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="elpamyelhsa" created="2021-02-20 21:24:32+10:00">
   <body>Drilling updates due soon, confident this will be pocket rocket. Here’s hoping.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-20 07:53:25+10:00">
  <body>My friend started trading in crypto at the same time I did on small caps, dude is up 400% in 2 months. Fuck my life, LRS better 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-20 09:08:31+10:00">
   <body>I know crypto talk is frowned up but it's worth putting some $ into Alts that haven't pumped imo.</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-20 08:59:40+10:00">
   <body>I'm a late bloomer and dropped into bitcoin as soon as I heard Tesla bought in I basically ran to the laptop.....I'm up 20% on that it's beating my portfolio 🙄</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 10:36:19+10:00">
   <body>&gt; dude is up 400% in 2 months

What coins?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-20 10:41:15+10:00">
    <body>Ravencoin bruh 🚀🚀🚀</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 12:17:22+10:00">
     <body>Never heard of it but I am going to yolo everything into it</body>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-20 18:08:26+10:00">
  <body>Fuck me weekends are boring as fuck</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 18:55:56+10:00">
   <body>All I think about on the weekend is gambling, but I have nothing to gamble on. The casino no longer has poker thanks for Covid, and there's no sports on at the moment I care enough to watch and gamble on... Weekends are the fucking worst.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-02-20 20:01:37+10:00">
    <body>Dudes asleep, r/crypto_betsAU 🤙</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 20:03:45+10:00">
     <body>Don't get me started... I can't open that door again.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-20 19:47:56+10:00">
    <body>u/ramzataztaz may have something to say</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-02-20 19:30:11+10:00">
    <body>Yep it's fucked. Bring back pokerstars.</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 19:34:45+10:00">
     <body>Fuck I miss PokerStars so much.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="StrethAU" created="2021-02-20 18:11:21+10:00">
   <body>Oath</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 18:39:51+10:00">
   <body>Netflix</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-20 18:42:13+10:00">
    <body>Can't trade NFLX during the weekend??</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Skjjjjjjj" created="2021-02-20 21:35:32+10:00">
   <body>atleast fuck is interesting broh</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-02-19 19:59:39+10:00">
  <body>What a week !  Now some of these gains were handed back - but all are still multi bags up in the same week

BD1 600% in a week (on news)

FFG 575% in a week (on news )

PRL 470% in a day (on news)

And to finish AQS 1900% in a week - on \*zero\* news - nothing, zilch, zippo, nada  


&lt;Edit&gt; for the record - my share of those golden runs.....I squeezed out a tiny T+2 25% on PRL - all the others just flew by my nose</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-19 22:19:07+10:00">
   <body>i watched them and I didn't get on but I tried to get on prl. BD1, i was trying to do a valuation and kept on moving. But its a lesson. 

I got on JAT and it fell right away . I am probably going to wait around abit and hope to get out.  My plan is to watch for something else running and jump on it and eat the loss.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Substantial-Ad-6856" created="2021-02-19 21:04:15+10:00">
  <body>Z1P half year results next Thursday, can only mean positive results right??😬</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 21:22:04+10:00">
   <body>It is my duty on this subreddit to talk shit about Z1P. Cunts fucked sorry folks</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Substantial-Ad-6856" created="2021-02-19 21:27:21+10:00">
    <body>Thanks, I’ll take your advice and pump it.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 21:30:04+10:00">
     <body>Companies without profit make heaps of money for us</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="alg1979" created="2021-02-19 21:08:08+10:00">
   <body>True? What else do we know?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-19 22:28:04+10:00">
   <body>Unless the hype priced into Z1P expects bigger growth than the earnings report delivers...then it could receed even if the report is fairly positive. It happens all the time STONKS receed a bit on good news.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-20 11:29:45+10:00">
  <body>Hoping a spud ann will get XST up a couple of pips so I can break even and dump it into LKE/EGR

Also waiting for LRS to get into those juicy increments past 10c</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-20 12:55:16+10:00">
   <body>LikeLy course of action for myself too.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 16:25:14+10:00">
  <body>Why the fuck isn't it Monday yet?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-19 18:44:25+10:00">
  <body>I actually had an absolute ripper week. I've never had this much (unrealised) money in my life. DW8 is fucking pumping. LKE and LRS are getting there. NVX gave me a little surprise today too to top off the week. ADN is doing it's thing and I'm gonna top up on CXO and EMN. Feels good to be on the winning side for once. Also still waiting for KLL to blow it's lid. Fuck yeah</body>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-02-19 18:48:41+10:00">
   <body>I got in on DW8 late but it seems like it will crank soon.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="UnbanCatgirls" created="2021-02-19 21:35:34+10:00">
  <body>I bought 12 thousand shares of SVL because im a retard and people were screeching that silver was going to moon all week. It helped that they released an “outstanding” drill result right at market open. Low and behold those cunts dumped 100 million shares on the market 2 hours after the drilling report and the price drops. God i hate miners.</body>
  <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 21:40:43+10:00">
   <body>A hole in the ground and A LIAR STANDING NEXT TO IT</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="cockatoo1234" created="2021-02-19 21:51:22+10:00">
   <body>Silver is the most manipulated market on this earth. I don’t know if the companies like JP Morgan will ever get a lesson.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-02-19 22:43:06+10:00">
   <body>Fuck miners</body>
   <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-20 01:13:02+10:00">
    <body>That's super illegal of you say it out loud.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Roc390" created="2021-02-20 10:21:54+10:00">
   <body>Welcome to the life of 88E holders</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 18:20:56+10:00">
  <body>High profile autist Michael Burry doubles down on his Uranium endorsement ☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️

https://twitter.com/michaeljburry/status/1362594234436448257

Also he's talking about Hyperinflation and racial crime statistics....

Edit: Andd tweets deleted lol</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-02-19 18:46:06+10:00">
   <body>u/mutated_cunt in before Burry, that's class...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-02-19 18:30:14+10:00">
   <body>While a genius when it comes to economics, he has some seriously shit takes on everything else.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 18:32:43+10:00">
    <body>I give him a pass because he really is a sperg, but he's linked/promoted some absolute conservative dogshit tabloid articles before.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-02-20 14:14:24+10:00">
     <body>Totally. [Shit like this makes me laugh though](https://twitter.com/michaeljburry/status/1362954014862626816?s=21)</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="The-Slippery-Wizard" created="2021-02-19 18:38:10+10:00">
   <body>If he sold he was one of the biggest gainers off game stop pretty sure he had over a million shares.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 18:40:05+10:00">
    <body>He sold out before the squeeze lmao, think he made about 4x on his initial investment</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="The-Slippery-Wizard" created="2021-02-19 18:43:35+10:00">
     <body>Oh no fucking way I hadn't seen a portfolio update haha</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Cruffsies" created="2021-02-19 18:44:55+10:00">
  <body>Down 3k this week, not as bad as the 5k from last week. So I'll consider this week a win.</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-19 22:05:28+10:00">
   <body>You’re essentially 2k up</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-02-19 19:51:03+10:00">
   <body>yeah....im down too...dunno how much im not counting...been a lot of red lately.....crossing my things for a run from something !</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="InexpensiveHat" created="2021-02-19 19:58:04+10:00">
  <body>Wife’s boyfriend’s dad had sex at me so I guess I did ok. 

Got PEN on me.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="scyllallycs" created="2021-02-19 20:09:39+10:00">
   <body>Not sure if I should upvote this comment tbh. I feel dirty enough just appreciating it</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-20 07:40:08+10:00">
    <body>Same here. Awkward.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="lululemonhead" created="2021-02-19 23:12:24+10:00">
  <body>There’s no greater feeling than cracking that first Friday night beer and seeing green everywhere on my futures screen.

Happy Friday everyone.</body>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Greyhounds_Are_Cool" created="2021-02-19 23:52:59+10:00">
   <body>Can't relate</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-02-20 10:14:50+10:00">
  <body>FOMOing into a stock after a big rise is never a good idea because they eventually come down.
Except fucking LKE. Fucking keeps going higher and doesn’t wait for us to catch up. Does not fucking complete my buy order for 1 month.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-20 10:20:30+10:00">
  <body>Praying for one last xst pump so I can escape 🤕</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-20 11:22:13+10:00">
   <body>Sitting on it till I break even. Could be a long wait</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-20 11:50:49+10:00">
    <body>Hopefully pending results will be enough for a small bump</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Rude-Letter" created="2021-02-20 10:42:08+10:00">
   <body>Same mate but most likely going to be selling for a loss 😑</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lokkel_18" created="2021-02-20 11:15:32+10:00">
    <body>Setting that sell and hoping to come back to and see it gone above purchase ha</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="s1ut" created="2021-02-20 14:30:34+10:00">
   <body>It's retards like you the reason it got dumped so hard.   XST still has not peaked.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-20 15:25:21+10:00">
    <body>How tf does buying and holding make me responsible, fuck you</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 15:09:13+10:00">
  <body>Dumped all my cash into EGR.

- Has had support from the Australian government 

- CR just completed at 60c 

- Has listed on the German stock exchange and plans to list in the US soon

- Their recycling process recovers graphite anode material for re-use in lithium-ion batteries for EVs with a 99.95 per cent carbon purity (worlds first non toxic patent pending process)

- Plans to use those funds raised for the construction of the world's first (outside of China) battery anode material purification facility in Western Australia. 

- That facility will use the "EcoGraf purification technology" (the elimination of the use of toxic hydrofluoric acid (HF)) to provide quality battery anode material products to lithium-ion battery and anode manufacturers.

- ASX-listed GR Engineering Services (GNG) to engineer the new battery graphite facility 

- The new facility will be capable of producing 20,000 tonnes per annum 

- As companies around the world are trying to stop relying on China , and also be "green" / eco friendly , this puts EGR in a very good position for global clients and electric vehicle manufacturers 

- Recent forecasts have indicated that the battery graphite market is expected to grow by over 30 per cent per year over the next decade as the world moves to electric vehicles and clean, renewable energy.

- European Union tightens regulatory environment for battery recycling - EGR passes the new EU regulations

- GM has pledged to end production of carbon emitting vehicles by 2035

- President Joe Biden has pledged to boost sales of EVs, including purchases by the US government.

In the media:

In addition to its recycling project, EcoGraf is building a state-of-the-art facility in WA to manufacture spherical graphite products for export markets in Asia, America and Europe.

EcoGraf is developing its TanzGraphite natural flake graphite business in Tanzania for which sales agreements have been negotiated with Germany’s ThyssenKrupp and Japan’s Sojitz.

The Epanko graphite project is located 370km west of Dar es Salaam in Tanzania and has a production capacity of 60,000 tonnes per year over an 18-year mine life.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-20 15:31:56+10:00">
   <body>Very strange SP movement, it pumped to over a dollar after the cap raise then dumped relentlessly since - and finally given up on Friday. Held up decently on the German market overnight (10% drop), not sure if ASX will match up this week.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 15:53:38+10:00">
    <body>The shares from the CR were only issued on Friday. 

So from the announcement (12th Feb) until Friday (19th Feb), some people were selling with the intention of "sell now and buy back in at a cheaper price". 

Some people done that,  some didn't as they didn't believe the price would go down and didn't want to miss out / lose their shares. (Aka diamond hands)

EGR was shorted approx 600k with the expectation of the SP drop upon issue of shares. 

On Friday the shares were issued and you would of had some sophs flipping the shares , and retail holders panic selling. 

There was however VERY strong buying / accumulation  happening at the same time.

The prediction was that the SP would drop to between 60-70c once the shares are issued (this is only temporary though). You can see for example when WBT had a CR , same kind of deal. 

The shorters will close their positions soon and EGR will be back in the green. I dont think its going any lower from here</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="conqerstonker" created="2021-02-20 20:01:35+10:00">
     <body>As someone who has made a couple of bags on EGR, my big concern was the lack of any real 'cornerstone investor' despite Andrew Sprinks stating so, FS and Mitishubishi just upped their holdings. My other concern is whether or not there will be much demand for recycled graphite in Perth. Are they going to ship from recycling factories in Europe and America to Perth to be recycled? 

I get that a Europe based factory is on the cards, but I believe that the CEO (Andrew Sprinks) is being vague.

\-Still hold EGR.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Almighti3" created="2021-02-20 19:54:59+10:00">
    <body>Yeah, it was weird that it pumped after the CR. I was ready to sell before the freeze at open of $1.20. And then I got $1.05 at open after the hold. But it actually went above that the day after. I thought it would drop straight away. I guess the old saying any news is good news and it brought extra attention for a bit. I was thinking it would hold around $0.70 and I think it would have if the market didn’t turn on Friday as well. Now it could go lower but I’m expecting a bounce on Monday. I might leave it settle for a bit before looking of getting back in but I’ll be watching close Monday.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DanceRain" created="2021-02-21 05:34:57+10:00">
     <body>Went up because it was final confirmation thing was actually funded for sure, Export Australia finance started looking at funding it Feb last year and still hasn't committed, the CR did however fund it. People took profits after</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Over-Historian" created="2021-02-20 18:13:29+10:00">
   <body>EGR is great, they're also about 20 mins away from where i am so if they lose my money (unlikely) its on sight</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-20 20:41:02+10:00">
    <body>https://youtu.be/H1Y9HC5cmI0</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Morlsy" created="2021-02-20 15:25:34+10:00">
   <body>Where do you reckon the SP will settle based on this info?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="chaddownunder_" created="2021-02-20 21:02:36+10:00">
   <body>This actually sounds good</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hanstarinoz" created="2021-02-20 20:56:00+10:00">
   <body>What a bargain it was yesterday. I bought some at .67</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Theme8958" created="2021-02-20 12:03:08+10:00">
  <body>I’m I the only one still holding LkE and BRN⁉️🥲</body>
  <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="MotorParsnip9039" created="2021-02-20 12:05:18+10:00">
   <body>I've still got LKE 😀... and XST😒</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-02-20 12:37:22+10:00">
   <body>Sold my LKE for SGC the other day cos I'm all about the those 200IQ plays 😢</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Theme8958" created="2021-02-20 14:34:24+10:00">
    <body>How’s that working for you bro? Do you regret it</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-02-20 14:55:05+10:00">
     <body>hard to tell yet, latest couple of red days has me low key spooked but im going to wait and see how it play out. if they can manage to start pumping gas ill def make a profit, it just going to take a few weeks and not going to be the multi bag rocket i assumed</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Asxnewb" created="2021-02-20 13:31:53+10:00">
   <body>I’m holding LKE at least till June/July</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Theme8958" created="2021-02-20 14:33:41+10:00">
    <body>I think there might be an announcement or meeting on March 11th</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Fit-Woodpecker-9308" created="2021-02-20 12:24:51+10:00">
   <body>I’m holding Brainchip! Massive potential for share price growth if the market wakes up!</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 14:32:51+10:00">
   <body>Honestly if this Roth Capital pump thing works then I might bail out soon. Wouldn't be mad at like a 20-50% return on this thing then I'll dump it in to something else.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-02-19 21:57:55+10:00">
  <body>someone start petition for the casino to stay open on the weekend please</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="steveydraws" created="2021-02-20 03:11:57+10:00">
  <body>Dammmm 55k, where did time go? This sub getting older and older 😢</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-20 13:37:27+10:00">
  <body>Does everyone here turn less retarded on the weekend compared to weekdays? 

Do we channel that 10% rainman on Saturday’s and every other day we’re Leo in whats eating Gilbert grape?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Big-Dog419r" created="2021-02-19 19:18:45+10:00">
  <body>EGR back to my purchase price ugh.
But on a good note got on the PENi5 at 0.14 ☢️☢️☢️</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 20:09:37+10:00">
   <body>Welcome fellow PEN15 holder, you won't regret this journey ☢☢☢</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-02-19 19:48:42+10:00">
   <body>which means you havent lost - thats good</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-19 19:25:41+10:00">
   <body>I was considering getting in on this.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Almighti3" created="2021-02-19 19:26:38+10:00">
   <body>I set my PEN but at 13.5 and didn’t get in :(

Edit I will leave it there though, you never know.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 20:10:00+10:00">
    <body>You gotta time the PEN edging just right, otherwise the magic won't happen 💦💦</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tofuroll" created="2021-02-19 20:17:43+10:00">
    <body>PEN was at 0.135 earlier in the week I think. I also just missed out.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Almighti3" created="2021-02-19 20:51:07+10:00">
     <body>Yeah, I saw that after it happened and had a look at the graph and thought it might be possible again but no luck. I’ll sit it there though. Mines only for 1k so I’m not bothered.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="hippoctoraptor" created="2021-02-19 19:29:51+10:00">
  <body>Z1P was surprisingly stable today. I don’t think it even moved. Could be consolidation.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-20 17:02:47+10:00">
  <body>BPH is looking better and better, latest interview with Keith Pitt pretty much implies PEP11 is going to get approved and he doesn’t give a shit about tree huggers https://abcmedia.akamaized.net/radio/local_newcastle/audio/202102/adg-2021-02-18-keith-pitt-pep11.mp3</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 18:29:01+10:00">
   <body>Thanks for the audio post. its bloody hard to read between the lines. Im holding BPH and sticking with them</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-20 18:32:21+10:00">
    <body>Yeah it’s a tough hold but I believe it will it go ahead personally</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 18:41:22+10:00">
     <body>I bought last week when they got smashed so im pretty happy</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-02-20 20:30:54+10:00">
   <body>Onto a winner 💪🏼</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-02-20 22:30:00+10:00">
   <body>Makes me wish I bought more than 1k at 0.12. But instead I have twice in BUY and sitting at a nice 500 loss lol</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Unknown_Gromm676" created="2021-02-19 18:34:40+10:00">
  <body>Well that was a fuked week..... Anyone chasing a kidney or sumin? Got 1 going cheap</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 18:58:23+10:00">
   <body>Do you take XST shares as payment?</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Unknown_Gromm676" created="2021-02-19 19:02:46+10:00">
    <body>Probably would have bought more after selling my kidney anyway.....
I dont learn from my mistakes apparently</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-02-20 12:00:01+10:00">
  <body>Eyes on 4DS 👀 looks oversold and ready for a break upwards 💹🛐</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BillyZaneTrain" created="2021-02-20 14:39:05+10:00">
   <body>Bit suss by the username... I've got a lot riding on this... You holding big?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-20 15:13:30+10:00">
    <body>[deleted]</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BillyZaneTrain" created="2021-02-20 16:11:10+10:00">
     <body>Yeesh only my entire portfolio on it! I wish you many gold plated tenders sir</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="MajorPlay4839" created="2021-02-20 16:00:31+10:00">
    <body>He’s got the shifty eyes too</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-20 12:59:18+10:00">
  <body>OTC NVX NVNXF held up nicely overnight at $3.37AUD equivalent. Motley Fool put out a pump article Friday, as did the Market Herald and Yahoo. There was also a presentation Friday arvo with the NVX CEO presenting as a part of the ShareCafe webinar with talks about their graphite plays on 2021. Even the boys at HC been doing some digging and finding links with NVX to the US DoD. US markets relatively flat with VIX down 2%, so moderately confident my NVX T+2 should work out.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Residual_spark" created="2021-02-20 13:29:58+10:00">
   <body>Very solid gains overnight. I think market will start reacting more to Friday's announcement this coming week.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="SAIUN666" created="2021-02-21 05:43:44+10:00">
  <body>This may come as a great surprise, but Monday I'm gonna buy more RAC.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-21 08:30:33+10:00">
   <body>The more I read on RAC you can’t fkn lose. Why isn’t everyone on this??</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="YabbaDabaDo" created="2021-02-21 08:04:00+10:00">
   <body>Who’s your dealer?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="cheebaihai" created="2021-02-19 18:22:07+10:00">
  <body>Everyone disappeared after the casino’s closed?</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-19 18:35:25+10:00">
   <body>Mate, Domino's isn't gonna order it's self.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 18:59:22+10:00">
   <body>Wife's boyfriend taking me out to try to cheer me up.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SortbyPriceAustralia" created="2021-02-19 21:14:36+10:00">
   <body>Was at the stores buying 2 min noodles for a month</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="WimpParsnip" created="2021-02-19 18:23:20+10:00">
  <body>The last few weeks my 80% profit on CXO has now gone back down to 0%. I wasn’t expecting it to go lower than 23-24c after the CR. CXO seems like a good buy but I must be wrong and clearly suck at this.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Dunengel" created="2021-02-19 18:33:15+10:00">
   <body>I think it’s gone from having massive-gains-quick potential to a long term hold. It’ll regain 0.25 in the short term and long term I’d hope it hits 0.50+.

However I’m a retard that’s typing this with my feet so ya know GLTAH DYOR NFA</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-19 18:39:13+10:00">
   <body>Same mate. Was up by a few thousand, now I'm currently holding a couple hundred in profit. I'm gonna hold and top up. I believe it has potential, and so should you.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Scarletbiscuit" created="2021-02-19 22:25:26+10:00">
  <body>I know we all enjoy crapping on hotcrapper, so if anyone would like something humorous to read over the weekend keep your eye on [this boomer fest WBT thread](https://hotcopper.com.au/threads/50-support-and-perhaps-lower.5911445/?direction=previous); complete with name calling, boomer memes, alternate accounts, conspiracy theories, and inane ramblings.</body>
  <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-19 22:33:47+10:00">
   <body>Sometimes I feel like the main guy in Memento reading through threads over there with half the comments redacted, trying to piece it all together.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="willybhoy1" created="2021-02-20 09:15:35+10:00">
    <body>Memento thats like finding dory right?</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DrizzyDradle" created="2021-02-20 11:19:14+10:00">
    <body>You mean the main Guy.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-19 22:59:53+10:00">
   <body>Fuck I just can't deal with HC.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-02-20 01:44:51+10:00">
   <body>Are you down ramping hot copper?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Ecstatic_Wishbone826" created="2021-02-20 12:37:07+10:00">
  <body>Overvalued stocks, new 'investors' flooding the gates every day with euphoria at an ATH. 
We all know whats coming.</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="chocchillson" created="2021-02-20 14:57:15+10:00">
   <body>If you could tell me the exact date and time, that'd be appreciated. I'll put it in my calendar.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-20 12:54:21+10:00">
   <body>Bank account is ready to pounce when it does come.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-20 15:06:00+10:00">
    <body>Cash gang getting fucked by inflation rn. That's my whole investment thesis.</body>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="MajorPlay4839" created="2021-02-20 15:58:07+10:00">
    <body>Wish I was so patient</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-20 15:59:37+10:00">
     <body>I’m definitely struggling to no touch it. A daily battle.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-20 16:46:11+10:00">
   <body>I opened an IB account purely for this reason. Gotta get in on those options</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-02-19 19:16:59+10:00">
  <body>Boys. Just let me say, QPM.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="stangroper" created="2021-02-19 20:30:29+10:00">
   <body>Have been banging on bout this better version of NVX for yonks. Get around it fellas</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Clewdo" created="2021-02-20 07:40:42+10:00">
  <body>Took profits out of the crypto space and funnelled them into small caps just in time for it to all go pear shaped, while crypto (especially BNB) continues to rise hundreds of % in a month...</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-20 08:32:55+10:00">
   <body>bought cryto last week.. up 200%.. not mad</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-20 07:51:00+10:00">
   <body>Rip</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-20 09:54:28+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-20 09:54:28+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="AccomplishedAioli698" created="2021-02-20 08:53:58+10:00">
  <body>Surely LRS results will be out this week..</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-02-20 10:21:37+10:00">
   <body>*Says nervous man for the 5th time today*</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MajorPlay4839" created="2021-02-20 11:11:35+10:00">
    <body>I like when a nervous man says their plummeting stock is 'on sale'</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="RaisedByWolves9" created="2021-02-20 11:56:00+10:00">
     <body>Btw as anyone bought XST while it's on sale? Guys?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="mantyq" created="2021-02-20 13:00:40+10:00">
  <body>Majority of punts is in : IBG PEN LKE AGY.

WIll i make it?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="ChannelVendetta" created="2021-02-20 21:27:22+10:00">
  <body>VMT - electric motorbikes, dollars are in the B2B market (think delivery scooters and hire bikes), increasing consumer sales to cashed up Asian and Indian kiddies - recent partnership with Ducati makes them look cooler particularly in those markets. They keep posting consistent quarterly results, sales increasing at a sustainable pace, hitting forecasts and projections. No crazy rockets, just seemingly good management and product. Releasing three new models on the 23rd, expecting a nice SP jump. I’m going to sell the news, wait for it to drift lower, and get back in before the next quarterly is released. Rinse and repeat until it stops working.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="shoobidoobup" created="2021-02-20 23:16:03+10:00">
   <body>I’m heavily invested in VMT and have been for a while. Consistent growth, profitable, in EV space and have just landed a massive B2B order. It’s weird how companies like that have a smaller market cap than these speculative BNPL companies. Guess it’s a competitive area. Good bet I reckon. They sell electric motorbikes mostly to Europe but branching more into Asia and hopefully other areas soon.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 22:18:38+10:00">
   <body>Alright. This sounds interesting.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 09:22:53+10:00">
   <body>Can confirm. VMT has been in my "eco friendly" watchlist for quite a while, exactly the type of company I would invest in if I didn't already have too many damn holdings.

Good sentiment sector, consistent profit growth, no bad debt, expanding to new markets. Solid business (note I don't hold).</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="BoxofYoodes" created="2021-02-20 07:18:40+10:00">
  <body>I tell myself I will not FOMO anymore after DXB, so I FOMO into SGC. I tell myself I will take profits at 20% up, which I was but I didn't. My only hope is that people FOMO again as drilling results get released, which it appears they might based on their past history</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-02-20 10:10:50+10:00">
   <body>How much of a factor would this reddit have had in the price blowing up?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Nsj_1" created="2021-02-20 12:12:27+10:00">
   <body>Conditional order "falling sell" set at the dollar value that 20% ROI is at.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="noirstorm" created="2021-02-19 18:13:38+10:00">
  <body>Av1 continues to let me down fml</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SignalGlittering4671" created="2021-02-19 19:02:54+10:00">
   <body>Not much growth in ad spending in 2020 even a decline in some sectors / countries.

30/10-2020 over 50 paying customers (25% increase)

27/01-2021 over 100 paying customers (83% increase over September 2020 numbers)

They expect to convert a bunch of free users to paying users in March 2021.

Some ramblings about big international names.

The competition certainly has adds out on the keyword Trafficguard to try and redirect users away from Adveritas, maybe they are on to something about the quality of the product.

revenue up 9% to 263k, pretty good when US ad spending hardly grew and Australian spending is down.  If you look at RnD and Marketing/sales as an investment in the future and not an expense it looks good too I think.

It's still on my list of ASX\_bets stocks to watch maybe buy, even after the whole pickle thing.

With all that said you might want to sell because I suck at picking rockets

[https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1004510/AV1\_Quarterly\_Activities\_Report\_Appendix\_4C](https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1004510/AV1_Quarterly_Activities_Report_Appendix_4C)

[https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1016843/AV1\_Quarterly\_Activities\_Report\_Appendix\_4C](https://newswire.iguana2.com/af5f4d73c1a54a33/av1.asx/6A1016843/AV1_Quarterly_Activities_Report_Appendix_4C)

&amp;#x200B;

Edit :(wan to to -&gt; want)</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-19 18:16:33+10:00">
   <body>I'm still green but I was way more green before.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-02-19 18:14:00+10:00">
  <body>JXT. 

Use your new found DD powers over the weekend to discover why this is going to be such a big deal in coming months.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Sashy313" created="2021-02-19 20:49:22+10:00">
   <body>I've actually been really interested in this company. What is on the menu for the coming months? (I'm looking at it as possibly more of a long term play, but would love to know more)</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-02-19 21:27:52+10:00">
    <body>Please read my previous posts and watch the coy webinars on www.jaxsta.com the search ‘investors’

The CEO Jacqui is the founder with her husband and can tell the story way better than me.

Edit: fixed URL</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="woodenlife" created="2021-02-20 01:15:28+10:00">
     <body>That link bounces big fella. Will dive your posts for the goods. Cheers https://i.imgur.com/3uVA91z.jpg</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="woodenlife" created="2021-02-20 01:21:31+10:00">
      <body>Sweet baby Jesus in the crib you really love JXT.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-02-20 06:56:32+10:00">
       <body>Taking a slightly different angle, I love the concept of what they’re doing.

Key points:

Run by founders (with significant skin in game)

Low MC / low SOI / tightly held / cash on hand to cover to end of year

Significant cornerstone investor (Songtradr)

Clear plan (watch the webinars)

First to market (with certified data - there are crowd sourced alternatives)

Significant moats (years to secure data deals - some exclusive - time to ingest)

6 key business elements (data apis / music rights cut / subscriptions / muso social media platform / site ecommerce / using database and algorithms for other uses)

Songtradr API live March/April

Subscriptions restart April

Nightlife API live April

37mil individual recordings uploaded with all related metadata (Spotify has 50mil tracks) meaning Jaxsta ALREADY has critical mass to be able to provide a meaningful dataset to combine with ANY of the digital music providers in the world.

Increasingly, decisions are being assisted by AI/bots/algorithms. To be effective they require clean, certified data. In the music world, Jaxsta is the only supplier currently.  Per the webinars they’re talking businesses that NEED this data. 

Pricing / Profits / Risk - No holes to dig. No major capex incoming. No geopolitical risk. Pricing set by market standards. Data suppliers get 55% of API revenue so ‘skin in the game’ to help Jaxsta succeed.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Goodvibesguy88" created="2021-02-19 18:51:09+10:00">
  <body>Great week, great month, great start to the year. Thanks to LRS and IBX.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Asxautist" created="2021-02-19 19:50:51+10:00">
  <body>Not seeing any mention of IXR, up nearly 30% for the week. Nearly enough to offset losses in VML.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-02-19 23:00:22+10:00">
   <body>all going well, deposit estimate next week will see it jump.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="cockatoo1234" created="2021-02-19 21:55:25+10:00">
  <body>BD1 died after its peak at 5.6$ and as well as my savings. Any suggestions</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-19 23:37:47+10:00">
  <body>Bought 11K worth of calls in APT at $274 strike expiring 18 March - solid Ann yesterday, profits upwards of 2.8B, dividends paid out &amp; vaccine role out &amp; still down today to the strike price  🤦‍♂️</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-20 07:18:33+10:00">
   <body>$274, bold</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Truck-Deep" created="2021-02-20 01:33:25+10:00">
   <body>What does any of this mean</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="KyrieIsSmarterThenU" created="2021-02-20 03:16:12+10:00">
    <body>It means old mate is probably not getting his tendons next week</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Residual_spark" created="2021-02-20 05:55:58+10:00">
     <body>Mmmm tendons...</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-20 07:35:32+10:00">
      <body>Almost as good as tripe. 

(Just kidding. Really not a fan)</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="conqerstonker" created="2021-02-20 05:25:09+10:00">
   <body>Afterapy dividend?</body>
   <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-20 07:16:52+10:00">
    <body>He's smoked out of his mind. He means CSL</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-02-20 10:08:07+10:00">
     <body>LOL here I was wondering how APT posts almost identical figures to CSL considering the diff in revenue... was gonna jump onboard if they went from $150m to $1.8b rev in a year.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-20 10:43:12+10:00">
      <body>Not $1.8B revenue, $1.8B NPAT</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-02-20 13:58:49+10:00">
       <body>No Profit, Afterpay Time?</body>
       <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rexkicker" created="2021-02-20 08:47:58+10:00">
     <body>And here I was thinking I missed a gigantic Afterpay rocket!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Endoyo" created="2021-02-20 09:23:51+10:00">
   <body>What was the premium price?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-02-20 20:13:53+10:00">
  <body>Stupid fucking ecoins which make no sense and I did absolutely 0 research into saving my ass from the pain inflicted by my dumb decisions on shit I stare at all week</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="MikeSellas" created="2021-02-20 23:21:06+10:00">
   <body>BNB for me bro.. $200 to $2,000 in a day of buy low sell high.. lost it with 30min on a free fall margin call.. I should have pulled out when my partner told me to, (no pun intended) - it was like playing a video game till it screwed me</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 20:31:42+10:00">
   <body>Might be a hidden message in that</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-02-20 21:29:47+10:00">
    <body>A couple of wisdom nuggets in there yeah.

Any of my good results anywhere were 100% luck, and even crypto isn't as wild west as listed microcap asx resource companies</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 08:28:24+10:00">
   <body>They are a gamble. No future in them, they honestly cannot work, but they are a strong trade right now if you time it right. Buy dips, sell after a short recovering, DON'T HOLD.

This will end with a lot of dumb people holding, victims of ignorance and FOMO, but you can make a killing in the mean time if you don't get greedy</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="lycheeboi21" created="2021-02-19 18:17:48+10:00">
  <body>Green Friday and my net worth is back at 100k after dipping a solid 10k though the middle of the week

Around 45k of that is from stonks from a 10k investment and it has been a wild ride to say the least lmao</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-19 18:24:14+10:00">
   <body>Goddamn . How long did that take you?</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="lycheeboi21" created="2021-02-19 18:31:46+10:00">
    <body>Started in September with 30k, made some costly errors and only got into the positives from January onwards

Also I (24M) live at home with parents on a 62k salary so that definitely helps a lot not only with savings, but knowing I have a safety net so I can take bigger risks</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-19 18:53:29+10:00">
     <body>Either way nicely done. You plan to cash out? Dudes yr age are chucking it all on crypto</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lycheeboi21" created="2021-02-19 19:24:17+10:00">
      <body>About half of my portfolio is crypto lol

Not gonna cash out for stonks anytime soon to get the CGT discount but I might reshuffle my crypto holdings towards the end of the bull market</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-19 19:47:00+10:00">
       <body>Ha nice!</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 12:27:07+10:00">
       <body>&gt; towards the end of the bull market

How are you going to know when it's the end of the bull market?</body>
       <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-02-19 20:27:50+10:00">
     <body>Lives at home with parents, and his incredibly large balls. Kudos, pal.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-19 18:25:04+10:00">
  <body>Ugh ! The weekend!</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ImInTheRedz" created="2021-02-19 20:12:30+10:00">
   <body>I will be up more on the weekend than the whole week...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="ImHiFunctioning" created="2021-02-19 18:50:14+10:00">
  <body>Uranium came back from death and finished flat on close. Hopefully it was just the big players shaking out the paper hands. Glad the week is over.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-19 23:07:12+10:00">
  <body>Somehow finished the week green after being down all week, thanks mostly to one well timed trade - $7k profit from MXC in about 30 mins of market time 😅 

Tried to board 2 other rockets (JAT, SRN) and got stopped out. In hindsight they were poor entries and I should’ve just held them but that’s how this caper goes sometimes. 

Now balls deep in IXR and SRX and also took new positions in QPM and CPT.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ironchefdonichi" created="2021-02-20 00:48:59+10:00">
   <body>Why is MXC suddenly ballooning? I can’t get a read on it</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-20 06:51:42+10:00">
    <body>Combination of a new deal announced (non price sensitive??), stockhead article and pump and dump target possibly.

I was quite surprised to see it close at the same price it opened at actually. Still might have some legs in it.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mr_X2017" created="2021-02-20 08:48:31+10:00">
   <body>I entered QPM as well. Nice little +15%. Lets see if it keeps running next week.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-02-20 14:25:28+10:00">
  <body>DFV has doubled down on $GME.  

I’m thinking that’s a sign to buy more $JXT.

Convince me otherwise.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Calculated-Punt" created="2021-02-20 14:27:50+10:00">
   <body>Doubled down hey.
 So he had initial investment of $53k in 2019. He sold some call options and cashed out $13mill couple weeks ago.

 Is his double down an additional $53k? Or more?</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-02-20 14:29:06+10:00">
    <body>Doubled his shares - 100k now</body>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="udunnomedoyou" created="2021-02-20 15:02:10+10:00">
  <body>Is z1p expected to go up on the 25th after their announcement? Would buying zip below $14 be worth it before the 25th? Ofc all just thoughts no one really knows</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 15:21:38+10:00">
   <body>Who knows... But their quarterly results were great. So it's reasonably safe to assume their half yearly will be good. Plus the anticipation of US investors/listings is promising.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="udunnomedoyou" created="2021-02-20 16:07:11+10:00">
    <body>I was thinking of buying on monday anything below $14. Reckon it would go lower than $12 by 25th?</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-20 16:14:16+10:00">
     <body>Again, who knows, but I wouldn't bet on it. Watch it Monday and see what it does. I suspect the drop on Thursday and Friday was down to a level of consolidation and support.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Genghiskhanbrah" created="2021-02-20 17:57:32+10:00">
     <body>I put an order to in on Sunday night at 12.xx. Within the first hour of market open on Monday it went up to 14.xx, I ended up getting in at 13.90 and it’s since dropped and slowly climbed again over the week but I’m still in the red. I’m anticipating it to do the same thing this coming week. If you haven’t DYOR on it yet, it’s a fairly volatile stock, seems to go down on good announcements but overall I like it and in my opinion it’s a better company than Afterpay. I’ll be holding longterm. 

Not a financial adviser, DYOR &amp; DD etc.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ASXSpecLandKing" created="2021-02-20 19:16:11+10:00">
   <body>Pick up any news paper from the weekend and read about retail spending - if Z1p and APT don’t absolutely cream this report then I’ll be shocked. 

It’s about HOW well they cream it - I think they will knock it out of the park and will spend a few sessions re rating to $20.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-02-20 20:07:57+10:00">
   <body>The stock tripled in price over the last few weeks.

Heck it was trading at like $3 last time it put out it’s first half yearly report (for FY2020). It showed it had increased its loss from -$8m in 2018 to like -$30m in 2019.

In all likelihood it’s report will show that despite the amazing “customer growf” they flog in their trading updates every chance they get it has probably recorded and even larger loss this year than last year.

Like go read their actual cash flow and profit statements buried on page 70 of their annual report. They lose money on every transaction because the cost of sales/operations/financing/bad debts are higher than the revenue they take in from operations.

Share price that tripled in 3 months on negative profit growth. How do you think the market will react when it comes out?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="happylosers" created="2021-02-20 15:04:36+10:00">
   <body>Definitely buy buy buy 🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="lokkel_18" created="2021-02-20 15:18:48+10:00">
  <body>Waiting for market to remember CXO again and light the fire under the rocket that that little beast can be!

I haven't lost or made money on it, the stock seems to just go up and down around 22c to 26c. Thinking the next couple of months could be big for it though! 
Anyone else bought in while it is low?</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Over-Historian" created="2021-02-20 17:41:28+10:00">
   <body>I think for its immediate future it'll continue to go down,  it has been hyped a fair bit at the moment and we are still far from production. The best thing you can do with this stock is not look at it for a while.
 - I have a large position of CXO &amp; rate the company.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-20 15:30:46+10:00">
   <body>CXO = LKE's dumbass brother =/</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-20 15:21:30+10:00">
   <body>Yep I can see it going to the 🌚
In the next few years</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="BillyZaneTrain" created="2021-02-20 15:43:16+10:00">
    <body>Emoji could be moon, but also could be a grey dead person. Sum's up the market perfectly</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FlaminChain" created="2021-02-21 09:40:54+10:00">
  <body>Got to admit I'm concerned with the amount of clueless punters entering the market and the effect it'll have. Was having beers lastnight with some of the boys who are in all honesty, complete morons, they're all hyped on "getting into the market and making bank". These cunts don't even know how to search a ticker on their commsex app let alone research and shit like that. They were just handing me their phones and saying "put an order in for me"... debated putting them in XST so I could dump my bag on them /s</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 18:58:01+10:00">
  <body>Trying to keep up to date with bph, getting blasted with prostate cancer or something.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-19 19:59:04+10:00">
   <body>Just need to go into a coma for 3 weeks and wake up hoping nopta gets approved.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-19 22:23:44+10:00">
    <body>i keep saying I won't day trade and then i do. I piss away hard won swing trades.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-19 22:26:10+10:00">
     <body>Yeah swing trading and holding good stocks wins hands down. Until I learn how to day trade properly.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 19:10:55+10:00">
  <body>Is LRSOC just free money? Seems like it's constantly been trailing the heads by 0.5-0.8c, but never actually catches up</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-19 19:48:05+10:00">
   <body>Well convert them then</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 19:51:03+10:00">
    <body>Nah I don't own any, just wondering if by buying them so cheap they will ever catch up to the strike price and I can flip them back for guaranteed profits</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-19 19:56:01+10:00">
     <body>Strike price? That’s not how these options work. You pay the company money they convert them into real shares.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 19:57:14+10:00">
      <body>I mean catch up to the heads. Ie. Buy them at 5.6c while LRS is at 7.4c. 5.6+1.2 strike price = 6.8, 0.6c cheaper than they should be. Theoretically they should eventually move up to 1.2c below LRS but I haven't seen it yet</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="brayboy200" created="2021-02-19 22:07:45+10:00">
       <body>They caught up a fair bit today tbf</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ANDYX102" created="2021-02-19 21:14:50+10:00">
   <body>Prior to this Halloysite anticipation run they were following at pretty much strike....</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="crabbypattytata" created="2021-02-19 19:30:04+10:00">
  <body>Wishing I bought more NVX last year</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Coral_Rooster" created="2021-02-19 19:30:33+10:00">
  <body>AR9 off trading halt on Monday!!!
Lets see it overtake TNT ;) 

(DW I love you TNT, I want you both to succeed)</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-19 19:48:44+10:00">
   <body>Us TNT lovers appreciate all Cyber players

P.S. You're getting acquired soon 😈😈😈</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-19 19:47:25+10:00">
   <body>I hope it’s a cap raise with that negative attitude</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-19 21:04:51+10:00">
   <body>Yeah I'm very bullish on AR9 I sold back in the 50c range but I have a soft spot for Daniel.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-02-19 21:12:24+10:00">
   <body>I think AR9 will tank for a couple days like Cro

then head north like cro did.  I'm gonna hold on AR9. I only invested like 600 bucks so. And yes please TNT do something!!!1</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Middle_Chapter" created="2021-02-19 20:45:39+10:00">
  <body>US Congress talking about RobinHood

[https://twitter.com/themartinirita/status/1362511918817185793?s=21](https://twitter.com/themartinirita/status/1362511918817185793?s=21)</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Brilliant-Contract16" created="2021-02-19 20:59:53+10:00">
  <body>Wrap up this KIS DD for you animals to enjoy, lots of pictures to help.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Saphiaer" created="2021-02-19 23:05:30+10:00">
  <body>Futures are up. Pls America be kind to me tonight I’ve had a shit week 🥺</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-02-19 18:53:01+10:00">
  <body>PUR is the only reason I'm up this week. Feels like I've had a chapped arsehole for a month now!</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-19 18:57:53+10:00">
   <body>Same. Despite pur being so green, today was so bad that the today's change on my portfolio was barely impressive. I think it'll push to the 6s again next week and wondering where it will consolidate after the madness is over. Looking into some options too but they've risen a lot.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-02-19 19:21:08+10:00">
    <body>I think it might slowly go up from here if the surveying keeps being impressive. I don't know if I'd be getting into the options, it's a bit early for mine. But i think long term the SP can become life changing.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-19 19:28:00+10:00">
     <body>Yeah definitely there's 3 blocks to go along with the expanded survey area for the East block. Options expire 31st October with 10c strike; I dont see PUR being under 10c by end of October unless it has found nothing significant and if that's the case then it would be close to zero cents anyway. So it's either gonna be above 10c/80M mc, or near worthless, making the options a good punt for a small parcel imo. Can always dump them off for big gains if it rockets again on pre drill hype. Pretty disappointed i didn't free carry today at 6c because I was greedy &amp; thought it could hit 7c and then it tanked hard but whatever, good day anyway.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-02-19 19:38:56+10:00">
      <body>I guess when you look at it like that it's not a bad move. I reckon it might be 10c by June if all goes well. I really can't see why it can't be the next CHN in 12 months or so. I'm not sure if I'll free carry yet.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-19 20:58:10+10:00">
       <body>There is a few reason why PUR can’t do a CHN. Mainly it’s related to SOI whose holding and whose interested. CHN at its lowest was probably about a 13cent share just for some context. 

Not saying it can’t hit 10cents but it’s certainly not one id pick to make a 1.5 billion dollar market cap.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="BOUND_TESTICLE" created="2021-02-19 19:35:46+10:00">
  <body>If you could all make SWF do that thing on Monday where it turns green it would be great. 

Surely there is a big brain meme about buying shares on SWF and buying SWF shares on SWF.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-19 22:03:36+10:00">
   <body>Do you use SelfWealth ?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-19 22:05:08+10:00">
  <body>any one know best api for stock data for asx?</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Bleachtastegood" created="2021-02-19 22:15:51+10:00">
   <body>Tradingview is pretty good</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-19 22:27:37+10:00">
    <body>best one so far but kind of funky where do they keep the nice api calls instead of widgets but cheers</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-19 22:09:29+10:00">
   <body>I'd be curious to know too actually.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-19 22:14:07+10:00">
    <body>so far, all I can find is asx seems to have limited data vendors</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-19 22:13:20+10:00">
    <body>its not commsux</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-20 08:48:42+10:00">
  <body>I was holding NVX at about 2.9.....then I offloaded it for a break even because I was convinced I could get in cheaper........now...I have....huge....fuckin...FOMO...stay calm...assume it's not going to hold the friday gains and try and get back in under the 3 mark.....oh god...real bad FOMO</body>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="Nocashgang" created="2021-02-20 08:50:36+10:00">
   <body>Mate.. There is always another trade</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Residual_spark" created="2021-02-20 10:32:51+10:00">
   <body>Novonix is a solid long term hold. Announcement yesterday gave it validation and scope. I don't regret buying in at close - strength in OTC markets proves sentiment is good.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-02-20 09:20:56+10:00">
  <body>https://smallcaps.com.au/shareholder-disclosure-on-the-line-reduce-class-actions/

What’s everyone think? Maybe stonks will stop pumping and dumping as much needlessly with fewer announcements for people to have opinions on?</body>
  <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-20 10:32:57+10:00">
   <body>This is going to breed corruption and insider trading. So, mission accomplished for the LNP I guess.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 10:30:51+10:00">
   <body>Or insider trader will increase with execs pumping and dumping with impunity and claiming to be honest idiots</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-02-20 10:31:30+10:00">
    <body>Yep that is probably likely, seems like this may be a shit idea</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-02-20 11:05:41+10:00">
   <body>There was a discussion on it here;

[https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX\_Bets/comments/lm5v4t/this\_could\_be\_serious\_game\_changer\_for\_our\_bets/](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lm5v4t/this_could_be_serious_game_changer_for_our_bets/)

&amp;#x200B;

In short, it's sketchy as fuck and a terrible move that only serves the interests of directors/insiders</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Soft-Leek-280" created="2021-02-20 09:32:48+10:00">
   <body>Also less accountability to directors of a company to people who own a stake in it?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-02-20 09:38:44+10:00">
    <body>Yeh seems that way</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Rosencrantz1710" created="2021-02-21 09:29:31+10:00">
  <body>According to my spreadsheet that I’m just bringing up to date, if my investment in VML continues on its current rate of return, I stand to lose 396.54% of my initial investment on an annual basis 😂</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="dick-face-dick-face" created="2021-02-21 09:32:15+10:00">
   <body>obviously a bipolar penny stock could be rationally predicted by a spreadsheet formula. 😉</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-21 09:38:44+10:00">
    <body>Imagine trying to chart FFG</body>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="KingDavo1995" created="2021-02-19 18:15:59+10:00">
  <body>What are the best/cheapeast brokerage platforms you use for day trading? SW is great for larger transactions but I wanna trial with something in the hundreds so % based may work better so I dont blow my load on transaction fees. Recomendations?</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-02-19 18:17:44+10:00">
   <body>If you are going to be serious about it then you don’t want to be looking at what’s cheap. 

You get what you pay for in this business.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="KingDavo1995" created="2021-02-19 18:29:10+10:00">
    <body>In time atayls... for now just want to trial with a small amount and see if I stonk or stink</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-02-19 18:34:45+10:00">
     <body>Good luck with it mate.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-19 18:20:39+10:00">
    <body>What broker do you reccomend atayls?</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-02-19 18:21:21+10:00">
     <body>FP Markets and Invast, using IRESSTrader.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-19 18:36:35+10:00">
      <body>Invast looks a but much for a spud with less than 20k like me.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Impossible-Magician" created="2021-02-19 20:03:00+10:00">
      <body>Is FP &amp; IRESS only CFDs?</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-02-19 20:09:25+10:00">
       <body>Equities also.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 18:49:42+10:00">
  <body>Does anyone here use their realised gains as a safety net for running big T2 trades? 25k bet on a ticker with good depth or good ann and a 5% gain is like $1250 profit that you keep for yourself - worst case you sell off at 10% down and dip into your "bank" of 50k (for example) sitting in your CDIA to cover it while offsetting your CGT.

Is it a viable strategy, or a case of the market being too volatile to win more than you lose?</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-02-19 18:51:08+10:00">
   <body>Works but don’t get greedy . Seen some posts on here that ended up wiping their whole portfolio out to cover a bad T+2</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Byron_10121" created="2021-02-19 19:20:50+10:00">
    <body>was greedy and lost my portfolio and more on t+2 a while back and am still recovering. don’t make the same mistake i and many others made and use stop losses!!!</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-19 22:05:12+10:00">
     <body>How did you manage that?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 18:52:37+10:00">
    <body>But I mean your actual gains rather than your portfolio. So having 50k as a bank of sorts to day trade and not holding any stocks more than a day or two.

I don't have 50k to do this for the record but further down the line I see this as a much less risky way of making quick gains over bag holding forever</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-02-19 18:59:29+10:00">
     <body>Ahhh I get you , yeah look in theory sounds good but personally I wouldn’t be able to differentiate gains from capital once I’ve pulled it out . You may be built different</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-19 21:16:23+10:00">
   <body>You ok with losing 2.5k if it drops quick and gaps your stop loss?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-19 21:18:53+10:00">
    <body>Yeah because the 50k would just be ammo to make the T2 gains and not part of my personal finances. Kind of like spins on the pokies to hit the feature but more calculated 🙃

Lose 2.5k (10% loss), make 15% gain the next day? I'd ideally be doing it on green US futures days and only on companies getting hype pumps/not nano caps</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-19 22:46:30+10:00">
     <body>So you don’t have an issue losing paper gains? Just because it’s not realised doesn’t mean you’re not losing money</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Woodcuttering" created="2021-02-19 20:08:08+10:00">
  <body>[I hate the weekend](https://imgur.com/a/Ewh75U3)</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ImInTheRedz" created="2021-02-19 20:24:20+10:00">
   <body>It’s the only time I ain’t be losing money😂</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="SFJeanie" created="2021-02-19 20:54:18+10:00">
    <body>That's what crypto is for!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="werty3555" created="2021-02-19 21:21:46+10:00">
  <body>Expecting RLT to have a slight boost with vaccines rolling out 
They use helium to keep the vaccines colder for longer instead of dry ice which is more costly to make and consumes more space during transport</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-19 22:01:20+10:00">
   <body>I’d like to see them monetize it first...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-19 21:29:14+10:00">
   <body>Cuuuuunt RLT is the shit we are parachuting vaccines to villagers pump the fuck outta this</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="werty3555" created="2021-02-19 21:31:22+10:00">
    <body>Why is nobody talking about it we need to jump on this before it hit $5-6 and we're all regreting it</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-20 16:43:11+10:00">
     <body>It jumped to $3 not too long ago and I think it will head back there very soon. Very exciting to read about!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="imapassenger1" created="2021-02-20 07:11:31+10:00">
  <body>I've got a buy order for PEN at 15c. I'll probably get cold feet and cancel it over the weekend and then it will take off anyway and not even drop to 15c first...</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Brilliant-Contract16" created="2021-02-20 09:44:33+10:00">
   <body>I'm thinking of similar play but for me it's adding a bit more.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 10:03:58+10:00">
   <body>Ima wait and greedily hope to get in at 10-12. Ill probs miss out lol</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="basstwomouth" created="2021-02-20 08:59:13+10:00">
  <body>FFF $17mil mcap. $5mil revenue expected. $3mil cash. 
Baby Bunting deal
500 store Aus Retailers United Deal
Sigma Healthcare deal
Expansion into China and SE Asia</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-20 09:44:24+10:00">
   <body>Due for cap raise soon, burning cash regardless</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Jcow7166" created="2021-02-20 09:36:53+10:00">
   <body>I bought this one straight after the IPO at 39 cents and ever since the SP has barely moved despite all these huge announcements. Stubbornly around 23-25 cents - not sure why!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DrCharlesKnocklier" created="2021-02-20 10:40:42+10:00">
  <body>I am looking at getting into WOO for next week.
They've been up in the last week and the last month, 0.003 -&gt;0.006.
I think they're going for a run next week after they clear the 'going concern' after capital raising</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-02-20 11:22:45+10:00">
   <body>WOO is a trap</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DrCharlesKnocklier" created="2021-02-20 11:28:21+10:00">
    <body>What's the trap??</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-20 11:44:59+10:00">
     <body>Soph cap raise , Sophs then continue to support price on market while offloading cap raise stock to unsuspecting retail at around 100-200%. There is a reason this stock was 0.001 until a few weeks ago.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-20 13:54:53+10:00">
      <body>Have some promising contracts in the pipework, however they literally doubled their SOI with the cap raise. Raised to remove debt too, so not for growth. I like where these guys can go in the future, but with that many new shares flooding the market I'm gonna be sceptical short term</body>
      <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-20 11:10:44+10:00">
  <body>https://youtu.be/QQbBUNce5m8

Watch this Jack Lifton interviews. Whether you are in Rare Earth's, Lithium or Copper its a good insight to China ect.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-20 11:22:24+10:00">
   <body>Just want to add. If you want a good understanding on the nickel market here’s a great resource from Crux with Mark Selby. https://youtu.be/nsRLn1Ph7kA

Mark is involved with nickel mining companies so usually views can be bias but I believe this is a nice honest representation on the volatility of the nickel market</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-20 11:24:52+10:00">
   <body>Is it expensive to construct a rare earth mine? Does it take long to start mining? Just wondering. Seems lithium takes ages to start mining.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Brilliant-Contract16" created="2021-02-20 15:47:20+10:00">
    <body>Got you covered, this book is great as it walks you through it.  https://www.amazon.com/Mining-Explained-11th-Northern-Miner/dp/B007RF07YU?ref_=d6k_applink_bb_marketplace</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-20 16:13:13+10:00">
     <body>Good idea to invest 20 bucks to read it when some of us are invested 1-20k in mining stocks lol.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-20 17:28:11+10:00">
      <body>Some of us have gambled alot more on some mining stocks haha.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-20 11:42:17+10:00">
    <body>It can be yes. It's not the mine itself that takes so long its all the crap to get up to it.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Aleckrandall" created="2021-02-20 11:50:35+10:00">
  <body>AR9 Holders where you at. What’s your Monday’s game plan? 

Hoping a good announcement will come in before the market opens Monday to soften the blow that is expected.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-20 12:02:39+10:00">
   <body>Slight hit to the SP but long term still good man. Just go back and read their quarterly to firm your stance, and remember that quarterly had bugger all of NC contributions.

Also note all options are used up and its cash flow positive... shouldn't be any more un needed dilutions.

Yes I regret selling AR9 haha.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Aleckrandall" created="2021-02-20 12:08:11+10:00">
    <body>Contemplating buying more if it does take a big dive Monday. If they release a few good results after the dip + people buying up I can see it going back towards that .36-.40 range</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-20 12:09:34+10:00">
     <body>Yeah be hard to say what it does, he'll it could go up haha.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Aleckrandall" created="2021-02-20 12:49:53+10:00">
      <body>So true who knows! do know Was great it didn’t open on Friday... would’ve been bloody</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="plucky26" created="2021-02-20 17:28:37+10:00">
  <body>I seem to be part of the pump on PWN, parkway minerals . I got a message informing me that the pump groups on twitter . I do not hold PWN , though I did research into it. Its just another bet and could or might not be good.

Trade the trade.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hardnuggett" created="2021-02-20 17:46:38+10:00">
   <body>I've seen this too, ratio of buyers to sellers at the moment is 3:1. I reckon it takes close to 7:1 to see any real movement, but this could change come Monday.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 18:21:32+10:00">
    <body>Just curious does the 7:1 ratio apply to all stocks generally?</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-20 19:36:50+10:00">
     <body>Trading on market depth is retarded. It's easily manipulated and you won't know a big sell order is coming until after it's executed.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-02-20 20:03:46+10:00">
      <body>Yeah the amount of references to market depth on this sub as a reason to buy is quite fucked up.</body>
      <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 19:54:35+10:00">
      <body>you never know when the big sell is coming anyway.. I go with my gut and strangely its been working well lol. What indicators do you use?</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Residual_spark" created="2021-02-21 09:22:46+10:00">
  <body>I'm confused. Why is everyone so excited about XST/SGC and some 'spud'? Last time I checked potatoes were dirt cheap at woolies. Even comes with a free bag so you can carry them.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-19 18:05:13+10:00">
  <body>Long week, red week, red Friday. Cracked four beers already, May crack four more. Kubrick collection arrived in the mail today so might put on some Barry Lyndon. Heard it’s long and beautiful.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="JimFromTheOffice1" created="2021-02-19 20:48:18+10:00">
  <body>Anyone know when RAC’s next lot of announcements are?</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="silent--echo" created="2021-02-19 20:52:28+10:00">
   <body>At this point it's just "in the current quarter" I'm pretty sure. Their last quarterly has a short bit of info on it:

"Expected news In the current quarter, investors can expect Race to provide an update on the following:

* FTO preclinical activity (Pillar 1).  
* The George Clinical breast cancer trial review (Pillar 2).  
* The AML programs (Pillar 3)."</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-19 21:03:36+10:00">
    <body>Also will be interested to know who the new CMO is.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-02-19 21:16:29+10:00">
     <body>Who would be your pick?</body>
     <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-19 21:22:41+10:00">
      <body>Glad you asked. Probably my friend Lawrence. Only run a couple of trials so far. One where he drank salt water for a month to train his body to process it - failed. Another where he slept in a sack outside every night for a year to try and make his body mosquito proof - success.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-20 07:38:21+10:00">
       <body>What’s Lawrence up to these days? Sounds like an interesting guy</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-02-20 09:18:51+10:00">
       <body>Hahaha, what a bloke! All power to him.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="notasabretooth" created="2021-02-19 22:03:42+10:00">
  <body>ALC absolutely delivered the goods today. Kicking myself for not buying CGO. Thought I had a bit more time to put together some capital.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-20 07:19:51+10:00">
  <body>Well, at least the market didn’t crash so this weekend. I was all puckered up tonight</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="GingerBreader781" created="2021-02-20 09:09:16+10:00">
  <body>Surprised no one is talking about RNT hitting 1 million resumes on there site with 700+ new resumes daily. Incredible report, and a highly user centric company

The average age of the renters is 18 - 34. I suspect the ‘buying’ market gap is only going to increase as housing prices continue. I have so many friends that are struggling to find places to rent right now, so obviously something is up 

Rent pay getting launched soon early this year will be a big changer in the renter market.

Disclaimer. I’m in with 10k</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-02-20 10:10:03+10:00">
   <body>Considering the age of users I’d say it has a good future. Got the exposure it needed from Bevan Slattery, now word of mouth will expand users
Gotta be patient with this like all small companies...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-20 09:43:12+10:00">
   <body>Looks like the SP has settled somewhat</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-20 10:31:57+10:00">
   <body>I am not familiar with how RNT works. Does it remove the need for RE agents and make it easier for landlords to deal with potential tenants?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-20 09:11:16+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-20 09:11:16+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Over-Historian" created="2021-02-20 13:56:42+10:00">
  <body>https://gifer.com/en/OZQC</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="grayza84" created="2021-02-20 18:23:13+10:00">
  <body>Bring on Monday, weekends are a bore. Got a fair bit of cash in Australis Oil and Gas (ATS) 

Market Cap: 55.21M
Current Price: 0.056

Fundamentals - 2019 Annual Report (USD)

• $53m Revenue (+56% YoY)

• EBITDAX 14m (+638%)

• Net profit after tax $7m (+8415%)

• Earnings per share $0.391 (+5.4%)

• Debt $33m

• Cash $16m

Australis Oil &amp; Gas (Australis) is an oil and gas company formed by the founder and executives of Aurora Oil &amp; Gas Limited (Aurora), which was sold in June 2014 for an enterprise value of A$2.6 billion including assumed debt of approximately A$800 million ($4.10 a share). In essence, the founders of Aurora pursues a countercyclical acquisition strategy at the bottom end of the industry cycle, which could provide value to shareholders if successful executed.

Here the founders an executives are attempting to re-create that success again in Through two acquisitions completed in 2016 and 2017 and an ongoing leasing program, Australis has accumulated a strategic position within one of the last emerging oil shale basins onshore in the USA.  Australis has become the largest acreage holder in the production defined core area of the Tuscaloosa Marine Shale (TMS), onshore Louisiana and Mississippi. TMS is a largely undeveloped play with a bucketload of proven reserves. It’s also not on federal land, so as Biden squeezes drilling in the coming months, the TMS is going to become attractive for developers. Indeed, there are already some players coming in. ATS has the most significant land hold of anyone. 

Australis has a clear "in and out" strategy, which is what I like. Management will look to sell or JV at a time when the price of oil is cyclically appealing, hopefully providing shareholders with significant capital gains in the process. 

Obviously COVID has significantly impacted the oil industry, however ATS had a hedge book of about 8.2m (priced between $51 - $55 per barrel) which has protected them from the worst of it. In addition, management are financially prudent and have ensured that the business remains sustainable in the downward cycles. My expectation is that ATS will continue to post operating profit while other on-shore companies have struggled to remain viable. This years annual report will show impairments which are no surprises in this industry, however operating profit will remain positive. 

IG has recently listed this as the top Penny Stock for 2021 https://www.google.com.au/amp/s/www.ig.com/au/trading-strategies/top-10-asx-penny-stocks-for-traders-200107.amp

Disclosure - I hold.</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-02-20 20:02:28+10:00">
   <body>I could not tell you held without the disclosure so I appreciate it.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-20 18:38:09+10:00">
   <body>Thnx for the info. Why u reckon its been trending downward albeit gradually since nov?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="chaddownunder_" created="2021-02-20 21:02:01+10:00">
  <body>What’s the go with SGC?</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-02-20 21:33:19+10:00">
   <body>Wait and see. Spud should be announced  early next week, then regular updates after that. IF they hit recoverable gas at good pressure, its only 5km to hook up to a major supply line. Not the multi bag rocket we were hoping for but we'll get some profits. Or the well is dry and we're all crying into ramen for a while</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-02-20 21:34:52+10:00">
    <body>Bit of a gamble at this point, so no problem getting out if you're not comfortable with risk</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SeaworthinessOwn7916" created="2021-02-21 08:53:47+10:00">
  <body>Can see CRO in US OTC market. Search CROTF in bloomberg.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Beeskneas" created="2021-02-19 19:03:15+10:00">
  <body>Boomers trying to keep up lol 

https://instagram.com/stories/selfwealth.com.au/2512365809960841092?utm_source=ig_story_item_share&amp;igshid=yygt8j1n0td5</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 19:27:19+10:00">
   <body>Switch to the app... 

I hate modern times

🙄</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Coral_Rooster" created="2021-02-19 19:29:35+10:00">
    <body>For the lazy. What are they on about?</body>
    <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-19 19:34:40+10:00">
     <body>Don't know. I saw selfwealth at the top, it told me to switch to the app, I pressed switch, it's asked me to install Instagram, I told it to go fuck itself, now I'm back to watching the clock, waiting for Monday</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hanstarinoz" created="2021-02-20 20:57:40+10:00">
  <body>MLX. Tin price is going up nonstop</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="YungLeesy" created="2021-02-21 09:06:17+10:00">
  <body>Give me a N
Give me a V
Give me a X
What does that spell
🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-02-21 09:18:28+10:00">
   <body>Cash</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Residual_spark" created="2021-02-21 09:26:40+10:00">
   <body>Tendons</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Tygarbyte" created="2021-02-21 09:27:47+10:00">
  <body>ART who likes **A**i**RT**asker. IPO is 65c a share on March 22. I tried the gig economy as an airtasker - howerver i cant be f fixing peoples computer issue below market rate. ie perform a miracle for peanuts, but then there are other no brain task that require skills. ie ikea lego pieces. So on the fence on this one.

[https://smallcaps.com.au/upcoming-ipos/](https://smallcaps.com.au/upcoming-ipos/)</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-19 19:18:36+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-19 19:18:36+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-19 20:12:25+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-19 20:12:26+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. (Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki) [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/]

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
