<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-03-05 Friday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>BPH (18) HYPE=8</mention>
  <mention>VML (16) TIP=20</mention>
  <mention>LOT (15) HYPE=24, GAMBLE=0, TIP=10</mention>
  <mention>EGR (13) HYPE=40, GAMBLE=0, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>NVX (8) HYPE=16, TIP=15</mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-03-04 19:49:25+10:00" sentiment="TIP 15">
   <body>Overall red and total down but
But a couple of greens - EPN &amp; JXT and
Still holding profits in DW8, CI1, IOU, LIT, AEF, IHL, PPH, VAS &amp; Z1P.
Looking to buy the dip in VR1, A3D</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-03-04 17:49:24+10:00">
   <body>probs write off all of march tbh, just keep buying dips i guess......</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-04 18:16:01+10:00" sentiment="TIP 15">
    <body>Easier said than done. I would buy the dip if I could find it.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:41:36+10:00">
     <body>Buy the edge :P</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-04 18:45:09+10:00">
     <body>...seem to be catching falling knives instead</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-03-04 19:46:47+10:00">
   <body>serious question time: I have an average buy in price of 9.9 on z1p, given the economy right now and the constant red dildo days I am thinking about cashing out tomorrow..the anxiety is killing me. I figured it will continue to drop until next quarter update.. and I'll buy back in once this bullshit has blown over.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-04 20:13:34+10:00">
    <body>This mentality is what makes the stocks drop and continue to drop though, if everyone bought company’s based on fundamentals there’s zero reason to sell just because the market is having a bad session.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-03-04 20:18:59+10:00">
     <body>I know and I agree .. that's why I'm torn. I truly believe in the business but can't sit by when I'm certain it's going to continue to tank as long as this bond yeild bullshit is happening. im seeing a clear rotation out of speci techs to blue chips. I happen to hold both and lucky for me the big 4 held my profile together today. everything else went to shit. big question is , is this rotation temporary or is it the end of the bull market ...</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-04 20:24:41+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
      <body>People and markets fear change, just like when the first lockdowns and shit happens it tanked and panic selling happened, now economy is going good and interest rates may rise so it’s a change and people once again panic but it all settles eventually. The economy is becoming stronger and that’s awesome it’s just a cycle that will eventually level out, if I was you and I truly believe in the company long term I’d try time the bottom and dollar average down but that’s just me. I’ve held plenty of stocks that have halved and eventually return to normal and continue to go up. I guess it depends if you’d rather relocate that capital somewhere else with potential higher growth over the short term. Personally I stay away from BNPL I held IOU at .185 and it sat at 13c for ages and I got out at 23c and even though it’s higher now I couldn’t care less because it’s just too up and down for me. But my opinion is just one opinion</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="JacDizzy" created="2021-03-04 20:20:47+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>You could be right but IMO dont paper hands on a Friday.  Monday’s = more green stonks and profit taking if you must. Not financial advice. I’m in at 7.9 but was thinking of averaging up at 10 because I like the stock so 🤷🏼‍♀️🤣</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-03-04 20:21:03+10:00" sentiment="TIP 15">
    <body>also, I know we like to think of ourselves as a bunch of smooth brain autist cowboys, but I also think this community is full of legit smart and logical people. I think we could be doing better as a community talking about this challenge instead of constantly saying buy the dip etc..</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 20:26:32+10:00">
    <body>I jumped out today, less than I wanted but I'm losing faith in bnpl. It's very suddenly getting saturated, and at the price you and I got Z1P, I honestly think there is more risk than reward.

If you still have faith in the sector, I'd pull out of Z1P and jump into IOU.

However, that's my opinion. Today I pulled out of Z1P and went hard into BPH, soooooo</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="adibart" created="2021-03-04 20:00:20+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>Based on US pre-market, might as well get dressed up for the red wedding...running out of red packets though ... Maybe VML or VUL if I can bring myself to look at my portfolio :-|</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="JustARandomMoniker" created="2021-03-04 18:29:02+10:00">
   <body>Dump VML or buy more. Depends just how fucked tomorrow is.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:57:14+10:00">
    <body>I'll take it;)</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:38:54+10:00">
    <body>Dump it to me 😀</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="genuinelivesmatter" created="2021-03-04 18:57:00+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>Rare earths are potentially good stocks. VML has a generally upward trend. But it depends on the current market conditions. I'd say follow, watch and monitor given the current circumstances. Could buy on a dip if it doesn't rise abruptly.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-03-04 19:15:28+10:00">
     <body>Good discounts on IXR at the moment</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-04 19:18:27+10:00">
      <body>Yep I’d second that. I got back into ixr today</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-03-04 19:52:12+10:00">
      <body>Yep - I was tempted by VML but the IXR clearance sale sucked me in.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snappo_B" created="2021-03-04 19:54:32+10:00">
    <body>I sold out of VML earlier in the week to take out some gains, but given today's dip I think I am going to buy back in. I have no doubts it will be siting above .08 pretty quickly!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-04 17:12:19+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 16">
   <body>Planning on buying some EGR if the market turns around early on. was looking for a dip to get back in.
this company is going places with 2 factories in construction now and their share price is in a temporary dip in my opinion.

also looking at NVX for a t+2.  it's below my original buy in a month ago and sold for some profits but I reckon buy Friday sell Monday for some tendies 

this is the dip we've all been waiting for.  
opportunity is in front of us 🙂</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:25:59+10:00">
    <body>EGR @ 60c and NVX @ $2.40 are both absolute steals</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-04 19:06:36+10:00">
     <body>totally agree</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PogoStyle" created="2021-03-04 17:39:01+10:00">
    <body>How confident are you that EGR is in a dip at the moment?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-04 19:06:16+10:00">
     <body>Dropped from $1.10 a couple weeks ago.

maybe it will go down a bit more but long term it's going to go up as they will be producing when the plants are up and running next year I guess.

I guess all indicators point to it being in a dip, maybe watch and see if it flattens out.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="joeycloud" created="2021-03-04 19:23:53+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>LRS: bought more at dip today. 3 🚀 to go this year.


MNS: hold. 2 🚀 to go this year.


HWK: hold. 1 🚀 to go this year. 


Working on my model this weekend to hopefully take advantage of a market wide price drop.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="RayGamble" created="2021-03-04 19:20:18+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>topping up on OAR whilst it’s down before the March results🚀</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="No_Nefariousness_131" created="2021-03-04 20:16:09+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>LETS GO</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:10:31+10:00">
   <body>FUCK YOU BPH.

FUCK YOU SBW.

FUCK YOU EMN.

FUCK YOU GENERAL MARKET.</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 17:13:14+10:00">
    <body>FUCK YOU LPD.

FUCK YOU XST.

FUCK YOU IBG.

AND MOST OF ALL - FUCK YOU BPH</body>
    <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:14:07+10:00">
     <body>FUCK YOU BPH</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:26:48+10:00">
      <body>Why you buying into fossil fuels anyway? The writing is on the wall</body>
      <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:29:23+10:00">
       <body>Cause when i got them my chance of 10 bagging was very high.</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-03-04 18:45:00+10:00">
       <body>I’d suggest doing some reading on gas. Nobody is buying it for oil.</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:01:27+10:00">
        <body>What exactly are you wanting me to read about gas? Or are you claiming that gas is not a fossil fuel?</body>
        <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-03-04 19:47:48+10:00">
         <body>Of course it’s a fossil fuel but it’s the cleanest *socially acceptable* alternative we have to coal and it’s abundant in Australia. We’ll be using gas when the wind doesn’t blow or the sun doesn’t shine, alongside some batteries probably.

I’m not hearing anything other than “gas fired power stations” for base load power. I’m happy to be corrected?

It’s gotta come from somewhere and I doubt we’ll want to be at the mercy of other countries if we learned anything from the last 12 months 👌🏼

Exactly why I own VEN and BPH</body>
         <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:48:49+10:00">
          <body>You lost me at “when the wind doesn’t blow or the sun doesn’t shine”</body>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-03-04 17:57:07+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
     <body>Please retract LPD.

Will provide many tendies</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kestoili" created="2021-03-04 19:37:07+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>EMN going to the moon. Tell me a box it doesn’t Fkn tick.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 19:46:05+10:00">
     <body>It's further away from producing manganese then i originally thought</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="36" downs="0" author="theblueberryfarmer" created="2021-03-04 17:16:10+10:00">
  <body>Hello friends. I have found a way that I can finally make money from stonks. And the best part is, it will help you all. From now, if you each pay me $1.00 per week, I will tell you all what ticker I'm about to buy into, thus giving you a 10 minute window to sell off your shares in that company before I buy.  Given everything I touch turns to shit, you will be able to get out before I buy in and the share price plummets like a fat chick falling down a flight of stairs. I think this represents outstanding value. Just send your cheques to "World's shittiest trader, cardboard box lane"</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:25:24+10:00">
   <body>The best thing would be if we gave you $1 every week and you just gave $52 back to us at the end of the year</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="28" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-03-04 17:38:27+10:00">
  <body>Obligatory FUCK SCOTT MORRISON post. What the fuck does he think, changing his stance on gas will get him votes? Cunt people who don’t want gas will not vote for you in the first place, they’ll vote Labor. Cunt changes his views based on the fucking weather. The people who voted for you wanted jobs and that’s what BPH and BUY provides.
Will be letting everyone I know in vital voting areas about SCUMO if the libs give in to the pressure of following their fat fuck face of a pLeader.</body>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="Impossible-Magician" created="2021-03-04 17:56:21+10:00">
   <body>Completely inappropriate for the PM to be making random comment on a market sensitive matter that is sitting for approval with a federal body.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Blisser_the_Sniff" created="2021-03-04 18:38:59+10:00">
    <body>any chance one of you whiz kids could hack his TelePrompTer Ron Burgundy style?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-03-04 17:39:38+10:00">
   <body>He has a coastal electorate. He would never openly say he was for PEP 11. 

But it was the most rushed, hushed, no I've ever heard. 

He just wanted to brush the question away</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-03-04 17:42:13+10:00">
    <body>One coastal electorate will have cost him a few other vital regions of lib voters I know where word of mouth spreads faster than the news. I’ll be doing everything I can even if it make only a tiny bit of a difference if PEP11 doesn’t go through.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-03-04 19:23:17+10:00">
   <body>Yeah so he's *said* he supports gas but have you actually looked at the official plan? Not the 'leaked' one News/Murdoch keeps bringing up that talks about gas pipelines and penny farthings, I mean the actual plan. 

There is $0 dollars towards a gas pipeline, new gas developments, etc. The 'roadmap' is a fucking mud-map, it's literally just a list of ideas that happens to mention gas. The actual budget allocation is $1.9bil total, $1.62bil to ARENA and the rest assorted small projects, none of which are gas and only ~$50mil that coal companies can apply for. IE the recent APA &amp; AGL announcements about having to close plants due to being unable to secure funding? Yeah, $50mil isn't enough for all of them. They've been getting 3m delays on approval for a year now and have decided to cut their losses. Our government is finally caving to the scientists, economists, populace other countries, etc. It's just their PR team- Morrison &amp; Murdoch- are spinning the opposite. IDK why, but if they're saying one thing you should probably check because there is no punishment for lying in their positions. 

For more examples see the antivax sentiment in Murdoch news- he was among first non-trial patients to be vaccinated FYI. The whole bushfire fiasco. This rape allegation his office replied to last year but somehow no one had heard of... fool me once, shame on you. Fool me twice, a fooled man don't get fooled again.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:11:08+10:00">
   <body>Lol you think he changed his stance for votes? More likely he changed his stance so Australia can fall in line with the World Economic Forums plan in collaboration with the ECB, IMF and Biden, Yellen and Powell. 🤷‍♂️ But they'll call me a conspiracy theorist and that's OK.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="mulligun" created="2021-03-04 19:09:46+10:00">
   <body>Hahahaha epitome of boomer rage posting.

Order corn.


I will be writing a sternly worded letter to Mr Morrison and letting him know he no longer has the vote of myself nor the South Wagga Wagga Men's Shed Committee!

Siri order corn.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-03-04 17:31:55+10:00">
  <body>Pouring one out for all our homies in **BUY/BPH** 🙏</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:10:31+10:00">
  <body>FUCK YOU BPH.

FUCK YOU SBW.

FUCK YOU EMN.

FUCK YOU GENERAL MARKET.</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 17:13:14+10:00">
   <body>FUCK YOU LPD.

FUCK YOU XST.

FUCK YOU IBG.

AND MOST OF ALL - FUCK YOU BPH</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:14:07+10:00">
    <body>FUCK YOU BPH</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:26:48+10:00">
     <body>Why you buying into fossil fuels anyway? The writing is on the wall</body>
     <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:29:23+10:00">
      <body>Cause when i got them my chance of 10 bagging was very high.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-03-04 18:45:00+10:00">
      <body>I’d suggest doing some reading on gas. Nobody is buying it for oil.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:01:27+10:00">
       <body>What exactly are you wanting me to read about gas? Or are you claiming that gas is not a fossil fuel?</body>
       <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-03-04 19:47:48+10:00">
        <body>Of course it’s a fossil fuel but it’s the cleanest *socially acceptable* alternative we have to coal and it’s abundant in Australia. We’ll be using gas when the wind doesn’t blow or the sun doesn’t shine, alongside some batteries probably.

I’m not hearing anything other than “gas fired power stations” for base load power. I’m happy to be corrected?

It’s gotta come from somewhere and I doubt we’ll want to be at the mercy of other countries if we learned anything from the last 12 months 👌🏼

Exactly why I own VEN and BPH</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:48:49+10:00">
         <body>You lost me at “when the wind doesn’t blow or the sun doesn’t shine”</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-03-04 17:57:07+10:00">
    <body>Please retract LPD.

Will provide many tendies</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kestoili" created="2021-03-04 19:37:07+10:00">
   <body>EMN going to the moon. Tell me a box it doesn’t Fkn tick.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 19:46:05+10:00">
    <body>It's further away from producing manganese then i originally thought</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="27" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-03-04 18:38:41+10:00">
  <body>I don’t feel bad for BPH players because fuck fossil fuel. You can make more money in EV plays and you don’t have to live with the fact that you’re contributing to climate change.</body>
  <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-04 19:07:06+10:00">
   <body>What if I told you there was a certain sector looking to change things for the better that wants to power those EVs free of carbon? ☢️☢️☢️</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-03-04 19:11:37+10:00">
    <body>Oh I haven’t invested in uranium yet but I’m a huge advocate for it irl and I’m looking to get into LOT I think as my first entry.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-03-04 19:56:11+10:00">
    <body>Do they have some sort of gang? Stocks aren't fun by yourself.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-04 19:56:52+10:00">
     <body>Funny you should ask that 😉</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="chillinintheburn" created="2021-03-04 20:29:40+10:00">
    <body>You son of a bitch I'm in</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Nordvegr" created="2021-03-04 18:44:44+10:00">
   <body>It's a decaying industry anyway 😴

Governments (not ours of course) are hesitant to support it.

Regardless, I don't want to see people here lose money.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="galantree" created="2021-03-04 19:27:05+10:00">
    <body>😂oldest joke in the book</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Nordvegr" created="2021-03-04 20:08:30+10:00">
     <body>Que?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="stevco-" created="2021-03-04 19:20:09+10:00">
   <body>I 
Drink
Your 
Milkshake</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-03-04 18:40:38+10:00">
   <body>The large majority of us don't give a fuck. We're here to make money, not discuss the ethics of companies.

Fuck off to ausfinance</body>
   <comment ups="33" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-03-04 18:41:49+10:00">
    <body>You’re allowed to make money AND have a conscience.</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-04 18:54:06+10:00">
     <body>So your saying the pollution that can be caused from nickel mining to water sources by arsenic is fine. Or the the slave labour in the Congo for cobalt and human rights violations keeps your conscience at bay.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="willybhoy1" created="2021-03-04 19:03:20+10:00">
     <body>I generally agree with your sentiment but with this specific stock you are way off the mark. As fossil fuels go gas is the lesser of evils compared to coal, there has to be a transition period anyone who thinks we can go straight to renewables is clueless and the CCS is huge. There is potential to sequester upto 33% of Australias C02 emissions. 

On a socio economic level the fact we are here punting illustrates that we have some disposable  cash but for those who have literally nothing with kids, relatives to look after or the businesses that are within a bees dick of going under I’m sure the option in the short term (see transitional) is a welcome respite to have cheaper energy bills. 

Don’t get me wrong we do need to push for renewables but in the short term I can’t see any other viable option without having to rely on fossil fuels</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-03-04 18:56:25+10:00">
     <body>Buy any bank stock, even in an index fund, and you’re a standover goon. Buy EOS and be a gun runner. They are lines in the sand with stocks- the businesses will just carry on regardless if there is money to be made.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-04 19:05:25+10:00">
     <body>Whilst making money in arguably the most capitalist way do you feel for people in third world countries living off a couple dollars a day? Will you give all your tendies to them so your conscience is clean?</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-04 19:46:31+10:00">
     <body>Risk/reward.
Nothing wrong with mining we've been doing it for years. Without it this country would be a third world shit hole.

You're parents would never of met and you wouldn't exist if it wasn't for mining.

Provides an income for men and women and it's great for the economy.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:06:49+10:00">
    <body>I don't mind a little discussion on business ethics https://youtu.be/xKGeHuln08A</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-14" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 18:39:35+10:00">
   <body>Hey, do me a favour and go fuck yourself while I fuck your wife</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-03-04 18:40:50+10:00">
    <body>Whilst you fuck the earth*</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 18:42:29+10:00">
     <body>She's not *that* big</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="InexpensiveHat" created="2021-03-04 19:07:24+10:00">
  <body>Can that cunt-truffle Scotty from marketing hold a conference and tell everyone how good IOU is tomorrow please?</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="autodidact31" created="2021-03-04 19:12:54+10:00">
   <body>Hi I'm the PM Scomo and IOU is a great stonk and has my full support</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-03-04 19:58:53+10:00">
   <body>It is a rapist, there appears to be general support for that so I can’t see why not...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="vadsamoht3" created="2021-03-04 18:39:25+10:00">
  <body>This red period has been going on longer than Farnham's farewell tour.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Timeflyer4357" created="2021-03-04 17:21:43+10:00">
  <body>I still have faith in our #ZipNation brothers, sisters and other genders. We will prevail and not cut loose to paper handed fools, we are strong like 💎 fireball dumplings</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 18:26:32+10:00">
   <body>Look, I didn't want to sell it... But I needed a quick 5k to buy the BPH dip 😑</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="hanstarinoz" created="2021-03-04 20:23:08+10:00">
    <body>Smart and brave man</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="ASXSpecLandKing" created="2021-03-04 18:13:03+10:00">
  <body>I reckon NASDAQ up 1.5% and a merry Green Friday for us 🤞🏼💎</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Logicorluck" created="2021-03-04 18:48:12+10:00">
   <body>If the Nasdaq is up 1.5% tonight I'll eat my own.......nah better not say it, we all know what happened last time🤪</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ASXSpecLandKing" created="2021-03-04 19:31:22+10:00">
    <body>Say it say it say it!!!!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="shitforbrainstoo" created="2021-03-04 19:46:15+10:00">
   <body>Fuck me, love the optimism. Hope you are right.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-04 19:01:47+10:00">
   <body>Hope so, I ended up putting $50k into a NDQ ETF which dipped hard today, not chasing rockets - just want to skim a couple grand with this play</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-04 18:06:41+10:00">
  <body>Just posted a thread for the Final draft of the PEN holder letter, will be emailing it tonight, feel free to drop some edit/suggestions before this gets sent off ☢️☢️☢️</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Azarael101" created="2021-03-04 18:09:07+10:00">
   <body>Letter. What are those?</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-04 18:10:13+10:00">
    <body>Its a boomer thing, ancient technology, this one will be an e-letter at least</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 18:40:24+10:00">
   <body>Haha awesome</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="dhking71" created="2021-03-04 17:28:00+10:00">
  <body>I still believe in IOU... I still believe in IOU... I still believe in IOU</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-04 19:45:56+10:00">
  <body>https://asxbot.io/indices

We're -6% but Hotcrapper is -7%

Get fucked boomers</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-04 19:49:30+10:00">
   <body>EM1 is the only green stock in the Hotcrapper index today, I'm fucking done 😂😂😂</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-03-04 19:23:43+10:00">
  <body>Hearing the Bear fags saying HuRr DuRr tOLd U sO!! CaSH gAnG!! Is worse than any loss porn from today. Fucken un-bear-able</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:23:23+10:00">
  <body>Even though I'm 20k down in the red, im happy with my decision to invest in EGR. Might be a longer wait for returns but im confident it'll eventually bring tendies to the table.

If you're confident in your choice of stock and nothing had changed fundamentally, then sleep well at night and all this will pass. Dont be too caught up in the daily fluctuations.

I've always said I wish I could be a long term holder / investor but can't (OCD Flipper), but now I'm being forced too. Maybe it's a good thing</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-03-04 17:26:48+10:00">
   <body>welcome to the bagholders club mate</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:30:03+10:00">
    <body>🤣🤣🤣 thanks bro , please show me around</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 17:27:31+10:00">
   <body>Exactly mate, keep that conviction.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:30:38+10:00">
    <body>Cheers bro</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-04 18:03:58+10:00">
   <body>I have a much smaller position in EGR but bought what I thought was the dip at 0.73c at the start of the week. Two days later and I'm down 10%! But absolutely agree it's a great company long term and will turn around. If it's still in the 0.60s I'll top up next week.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 17:27:12+10:00">
   <body>Hmmh the way I see it I'd be upset that I could have gotten a stock much cheaper even if im 100% convinced that it will surpass my purchase price</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:37:19+10:00">
    <body>Yeah but that thinking doesn't help you. You made the best decision you could with the information at the time. If we all knew when the share prices would go down, we'd be billionaires</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 17:38:29+10:00">
     <body>Yes I agree. I'm not saying its good that I think like that but it just happens to me in those scenarios.</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:40:00+10:00">
      <body>I'm saying it partly because I do exactly the same thing. I big brain a stock and think I'm so clever for identifying value, then it crashes and some fucking mouth breather can pick it up for 25% less than the bag I'm holding :P</body>
      <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 17:42:59+10:00">
       <body>Hahahaha after I do &amp; read DD I usually try to buy in at support or keep an eye on MACD and stuff sometimes it works but then a lot of the time it just breaks the support hours after I buy and im just sitting there trying to not open commsec.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:31:23+10:00">
    <body>Most definitely, but we can't win them all. Just trying to convince myself that everything is all good lol</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:12:30+10:00">
   <body>EGR is dogshit</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 20:20:55+10:00">
    <body>Far from it
https://www.ecograf.com.au/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/2175604.pdf</body>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:23:19+10:00">
     <body>Big hmmmmmmm.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="DanielTraj" created="2021-03-04 17:30:43+10:00">
  <body>to DW8 or not tomorrow... that is the question</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-04 17:47:23+10:00">
  <body>At least US futures are getting better, still red but a lot better...</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-04 19:20:36+10:00">
   <body>Yep. Nasdaq futures are almost green. Was showing down 100 points a couple of hours ago. Maybe it will be a green Friday</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="simcityrefund1" created="2021-03-04 18:19:20+10:00">
   <body>where do u see this?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FRjunkie" created="2021-03-04 18:24:34+10:00">
    <body>https://edition.cnn.com/business/markets/premarkets</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Rowgy8" created="2021-03-04 19:14:47+10:00">
  <body>Learnt great amounts of knowledge today. Will bring lube tomorrow 👍</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 17:21:08+10:00">
  <body>Will JPow come to the rescue of markets tomorrow?</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:35:03+10:00">
   <body>Who is JPow?
A: The guy with the money printer that goes BRRRRRRR</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 17:37:03+10:00">
    <body>Technically they can’t print currency by law and he was quite disingenuous with the create it digitally. I suppose it had the desired effect though.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:13:59+10:00">
     <body>Technically, they not allowed to charge taxes either.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 20:17:18+10:00">
      <body>That’s all rolled up in Treasury?</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:22:18+10:00">
       <body>That's in their year 1718 constitution which for some reason much of population refuses to update 🤷‍♂️</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 20:29:26+10:00">
        <body>Yeah the yanks are a bit mad like that aren’t they.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-03-04 19:08:30+10:00">
   <body>I’m counting on it. They will panicking about the bond market atm.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 19:12:06+10:00">
    <body>You reckon strong bounce?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-03-04 19:34:39+10:00">
     <body>Not sure about rest of market, but I expect gold has at most one more weak sell down attempt over next few weeks to around $1680USD before the last 9 month consolidation is finished. The fed will buy however many bonds they need to get yields under control and once yields fall gold will catch a bid again.

I’ve been loading up on miners recently, SLR, NCM, AMI, AUL/WRM. RMS also looked super strong last few days so will try to try to buy into that soonest chance I get. So many PM miners trading barely above their March lows when they have been putting out record profits and are flushed with cash reserves.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 19:41:31+10:00">
      <body>I am long gold so I would like to see it back above 1800.

I was pretty successful trading the 1780-1840 zone over the last two weeks. Some fairly consistent price action.

I'm gonna sit on a short NDQ long SPY spread overnight and see how the markets react.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-04 20:25:47+10:00">
       <body>I generally agree with you but gold looks primed to crash =p</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="joeycloud" created="2021-03-04 19:23:53+10:00">
  <body>LRS: bought more at dip today. 3 🚀 to go this year.


MNS: hold. 2 🚀 to go this year.


HWK: hold. 1 🚀 to go this year. 


Working on my model this weekend to hopefully take advantage of a market wide price drop.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="PM_me_ur_bingo_nos" created="2021-03-04 17:15:45+10:00">
  <body>Given back all my gains since mid December. Nearly 3 months in 7 or 8 trading days. FML</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 17:17:45+10:00">
  <body>EV’s (Lithium, nickel, cobalt play)

Is there really any doubt that EV’s are only gaining more and more momentum? 

I’m in the process of trying to sell my existing positions so I can set up a proper EV portfolio which I can only see going up in the next 5-10 years. 

What are everyone else’s opinions?</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 17:34:37+10:00">
   <body>How did u miss Rare earths... Rare earths will be used more than the rest because the magnets are needed in Wind turbines ect also.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 17:38:18+10:00">
    <body>Sorry I have a measly $500 invested in LYC which is up 30% but didn’t mention. Wish I invested more but now waiting to dip.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 17:39:14+10:00">
     <body>All good. I would recommend IXR or VML as good RE plays.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 18:30:00+10:00">
      <body>Do you fully believe in IXR and VML?

I’d like to look more into VML but with the pump and dumps being made with it has made me categorise it as more of a meme stock..</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:31:05+10:00">
       <body>Have a look at my DD on VML. I have gone all in VML at 2.6mil shares so yes I believe.</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 18:38:10+10:00">
        <body>Sorry new to reddit, I’ll check it out and get back to you. Feel free to let me know if anything else news related pops up.</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:40:48+10:00">
         <body>Yeah feel free to ask me any questions.on vml been holding since late September</body>
         <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 18:48:27+10:00">
          <body>One more question - what’s a good entry price for VML? 

I feel like it’s been extremely volatile lately with the hype, maybe worth waiting a month?</body>
          <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:51:37+10:00">
           <body>Honestly under 7c is pretty dam good, if u wait 1 month u will miss quite a few Ann's this month VML will be moving from a RE Explorer to a producer with the mobilisation of mining fleet, construction and clearing of mining pit, sending samples to other customers and potentially another offtake.
By May we a in full production.</body>
          </comment>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:52:05+10:00">
        <body>FYI anyone interested, the DD is here https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lr0clx/doomkoons_vml_dd</body>
       </comment>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:49:30+10:00">
        <body>Now that’s conviction!</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:52:28+10:00">
         <body>Been in it since 3.3 in October had many a scary red day but it's payed off and I'll be holding for years.</body>
         <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:58:30+10:00">
          <body>I’m holding IXR but aiming to buy into VML tomorrow. Wish me luck</body>
          <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:59:31+10:00">
           <body>Honestly if today wasn't a shit fest I doubt we would of gone under 7c so ur lucky there.</body>
           <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
           </comment>
          </comment>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:47:14+10:00">
       <body>Try and ride out the pumpiness on it, don’t get suckered into FOMOing into it in the way up. It’s a long term value stock, find a price you are happy to buy in at and hold.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-03-04 19:04:28+10:00">
     <body>The Lynas money machine just keeps printing</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:27:51+10:00">
   <body>Many car manufacturers have stated they'll be going all electric by the year xxxx. GM , VOLVO. 

A lot of stocks available for this play. EGR RNU TLG etc.  Probably a lot more but these are the ones I've looked into (graphite for lithium batteries / EV)

Edit to add:
I found that RNU currently has the most risk/reward ratio,  being a small market cap. But they've also dipped their toes into other things like gold (which is a bit of a turn off because they don't specialise in one thing). Surprisingly they held up real good and didn't get affected in today's bloodbath. Very speculative and volatile rn though. Its a bit pumpy dumpy and id approach with caution. If I was in the green and sitting on profits I'd take a punt on this. But because I'm in the red overall, I need to be more conservative and calculated moves.

EGR already has instos and they specifically are aiming for the EV market. They have a patent pending clean recycling program, "eco / green friendly" complies with EU regulations. Constructing first facility in Australia,  second in Germany. So it feels they are more established and have government backing too. Already listed in Germany and will list in the US. That's why I liked them the most. If you read through their last PDF brochure kinda thing,  it explains everything they're doing and planning and where they're at rn</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 17:37:01+10:00">
    <body>I’ve seen those stocks mentioned a lot, I’m slowly looking more and more into them all as I get time. Trying to be somewhat selective in my process but still trying to leave no rock unturned so to speak. 

I believe for example these have great potential for the following reasons - 

VUL - aiming to be first carbon neutral lithium source 

LKE - pioneering cutting edge process to extract lithium at quicker rates and minimising water waste

NVX - leading battery tester supporting LKE to produce a high quality product 

PLL - Tesla deal and solid support</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TinyParamedic" created="2021-03-04 19:27:50+10:00">
     <body>Ｉ see a lot of people talking about NVX but not mentioning about its synthetic graphite business. It is something worth nothing as they plan to upscale significantly，to 150k tons per year by the end of the decade (2026-2030).</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="shitforbrainstoo" created="2021-03-04 19:55:00+10:00">
     <body>I am pretty sure that VUL and LKE will use the same lilac process. One of the Lilac founders works for VUL</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:24:27+10:00">
   <body>Yep, got an EV/green energy portfolio. 

Lithium, Graphite, Manganese, Nickel, Cobalt, Rare earths and battery tech

Will consider a move into green hydrogen at some point as well</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 17:30:19+10:00">
    <body>What EV stocks are you currently following? If you don’t mind me asking ofc. 

I had a gut feeling on Afterpay at $9 and I didn’t make the leap. I feel like this is the age of EV’s and I don’t want to miss the next big movement and regret not weighing in when I’m in my 40s. 

I’m currently investing in NVX, VUL, PLL and LKE. I feel like other lithium stocks would have similar or more potential but those seem to regularly give updates and I like being informed and following along.</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:33:16+10:00">
     <body>Lithium - LKE, ASN

Graphite - EGR, RNU, TLG

Manganese - EMN

Nickel &amp; Cobalt - QPM

Rare earths - IXR, VML

Battery tech - NVX &amp; CXL (bit of a stretch, but they are doing some interesting stuff)

Mineral recovery - NMT, PWN</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="gboy333" created="2021-03-04 18:27:57+10:00">
   <body>Anyone looking into cobalt blue or jervois?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="youngworld2" created="2021-03-04 18:34:44+10:00">
    <body>What is this? 
Enlighten us please</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gboy333" created="2021-03-04 18:36:22+10:00">
     <body>Jervois mine nickel, cobalt and copper in the US, some Africa nations and Aus + cobalt blue have a number of ongoing cobalt projects and look very promising imo</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-04 19:07:52+10:00">
    <body>I did the sums a while back on COB and I was super not impressed. I’ll see if I can find it.

Edit:

Found it. 

A full feasibility study isn’t due until 2022, with just some lower scale pilot/demonstration plants in the meantime. That’s potentially quite a long time before this really takes off if ever. 

But more importantly. Page 16 of the 16 July 2020 announcement has what I’m looking for. This project looks quite marginal financially. 

Change the discount rate from 7.5 to 10 (entirely reasonable imo - 7.5 is low) and change the assumed cobalt price down slightly and all of a sudden the project is worth nothing. The current cobalt price is around $20/lb so even without changing the discount rate the NPV shifts close to zero at current cobalt prices. Probably a negative NPV currently using a discount rate of 10. 

The IRR is also way too low. Can’t see how it will ever get funding.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gboy333" created="2021-03-04 19:16:54+10:00">
     <body>Cheers for that, I feel like I’m still keeping this on the watch list purely because I feel cobalt (and other critical minerals) are going to fly over the next few years</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-04 19:24:25+10:00">
      <body>Yeah if cobalt itself rockets it could be on. It relies heavily on increased cobalt $$</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gboy333" created="2021-03-04 19:27:01+10:00">
       <body>For sure, also been keeping an eye out on CleanTeq</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-03-04 19:02:48+10:00">
   <body>I'm balls deep in lithium and rare earth.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-03-04 17:25:01+10:00">
  <body>Oh good, US futures have almost recovered, just in time for their session tonight 🙄🙄🙄</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 17:55:43+10:00">
  <body>Feel bad the most for BPH holders honestly. Who would of thought that a simple sentence from Scomos mouth would crush the stock. 

To be fair, in Australia things have to pass senate and they're not decided by 1 man like in the USA (Trump executive orders and so on). Well I think so anyway. So there might be some hope depending on who gets donations and what deals are made. But yeah understandably the stock would crash like it did from what he said.

He should've answered in a different way. Like "thats something were still discussing". 

On the flip side, it should of been apart of the DD , that this project is subject to approval or whatever and the risk priced in. Like with XST/SGC , we knew the risks. I dont think people knew of this.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-03-04 17:59:40+10:00">
   <body>I dont own BPH but what did that scumbag say? 

I will retract "scumbag" when he lifts ban on Uranium☢☢☢</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 18:03:04+10:00">
    <body>He said he opposes the PEP-11 gas exploration license</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-03-04 18:01:47+10:00">
    <body>He basically said he is not onboard the  pep11 project</body>
    <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-03-04 18:03:24+10:00">
     <body>Probably wasnt bribed enough</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-04 18:36:30+10:00">
      <body>Maybe a trip to Engadine Maccas will change his tune</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-04 18:53:55+10:00">
     <body>Plausible deniability when it gets approved?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-04 18:12:15+10:00">
   <body>It's hard to compare the crash of XST/SGC to that of BPH.

The risks for XST/SGC have not changed. Gas = $$, no gas = no $$. That has always been the case as even a lesser amount of gas would still bring about an sp increase. People hyping up the report were to blame for the huge dump.

What SCUMO did actually increased the risk of investing into BPH. Now there's a real chance BPH won't even get a crack at gas.

But yes, at the end of the day, you are right we should all know the risks before we invest.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 18:40:27+10:00">
    <body>💯</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 18:22:43+10:00">
   <body>Honestly I never considered the prime minister of my country poking his nose where it shouldn't belong in my DD.

Might need to consider this for my LGP stocks</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:40:42+10:00">
    <body>I would consider ANY fossil fuel stock at risk from this point in</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="JustARandomMoniker" created="2021-03-04 18:44:29+10:00">
   <body>Didn't the AEMO come out and say the LNPs gas led recovery plan was a bit shit couple of days ago?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-03-04 19:07:56+10:00">
   <body>Super suss government. They vocally support gas projects, but cut/delay funding to them until companies are forced to abandon them. They state they'll fund XYZ project (gas pipeline etc) but then have rolling 3m approvals- anyone who's gotten Centrelink will know how long those will take lol.

Meanwhile huge private capital, huge government funding &amp; huge ACT interest in greentech over same time period. Seems like they're pulling the ol` switcheroo to me. Saying "hey guys gas is totally the future lol ur grandad was right" while furiously dumping gas assets &amp; cranking money into (the stuff every other country has been investing in for last 5-10yrs). Shouldn't really be surprised, writing has been on the wall for a long time. Latest WA leadership is at least honest about it, but bludging billions into gas would have been a fucking robbery-seriously, invest as much money into the stop-gap as the end goal would cost? Corrupt as fuck if they did. Not sure how to feel about it overall. Obviously lying is bad, but the follow through would have been even worse.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="HomerQuotingHomer" created="2021-03-04 18:42:37+10:00">
   <body>Ex holder here, paper handed at a loss. I also didn't expect Scomo to wiegh in on it, but I fully well knew that the political winds determined fate here. It all looked good with KP, but I don't think it's worth holding with the Scomo statement (for me)... Could still be approved.

Anyway, you gamble and you lose.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="OneOfTheManySams" created="2021-03-04 18:41:50+10:00">
   <body>In retrospect it probably wasn't a good sign how this any day approval kept getting pushed back and back. It indicated strong enough opposition to it and the LNP getting slaughtered the past week was definitely going to create even stronger opposition to it.

Definitely going to take note of more factors the next time i need to wait for approval of something for a stock to rise.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-04 18:08:55+10:00">
  <body>trade fake yu gi oh cards to the 1st graders</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-04 19:03:27+10:00">
  <body>Dumped BPH at 0.145 so I feel like I got out easy. I also earlier sold near the highs a few weeks back and bought back in at the lows so it doesn’t owe me anything. Still more than tripled my initial outlay. 

Bought into WBT, PSC, BRK and EXR. Bought more MNB and VML. 

Busy day all around. 

I’m particularly excited about PSC and EXR. In a way I’m glad BPH gave me a reason to sell because my short list had been itching for ages.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-03-04 17:20:52+10:00">
  <body>"Be brave when others ar.... AHH FUCK IT, FUCK IT ALL TO HELL!"</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-04 18:56:15+10:00">
   <body>I can stay brave longer than I can stay solvent</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-03-04 17:45:17+10:00">
  <body>Welp, someone should have some T2 loss porn from today?

And who will champion for tomorrow!?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-03-04 18:24:28+10:00">
  <body>Pretty sure my portfolio is planning on committing seppuku tomorrow.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="chillinintheburn" created="2021-03-04 20:25:19+10:00">
   <body>Is that where you cum all over it to perform a tribute?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-03-04 20:27:06+10:00">
    <body>Nah it’s where it bleeds red, I then post a photo of it at 4:12pm and then you guys cum all over that</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="adibart" created="2021-03-04 20:00:20+10:00">
  <body>Based on US pre-market, might as well get dressed up for the red wedding...running out of red packets though ... Maybe VML or VUL if I can bring myself to look at my portfolio :-|</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="nsjmas" created="2021-03-04 17:09:31+10:00">
  <body>When do i start making money?</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:12:38+10:00">
   <body>Walk away  and come back in a decade.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DuckDuckWin" created="2021-03-04 17:33:19+10:00">
   <body>We're making money?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:15:15+10:00">
   <body>When you start selling memes on memefactory.io</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-03-04 19:34:26+10:00">
  <body>RNT cucked me again</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-03-04 19:53:33+10:00">
  <body>Topped up NVX two days in a row, planning on holding out until Tuesday before going back to the well to see what happens in case it free falls and I can really load up.

But it'll probably drop another 10 cents and I'll have a buy order in place by 1pm since I am weak, weak man.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-04 17:10:16+10:00">
  <body>Fuck I'll just repost my thoughts on the new thread. 

Honestly when you have all the US theme park and entertainment stocks like NYSE:SIX, NYSE:FUN and NYSE:SEAS booming. 

It doesn't make sense why ALG (Ardent Leisure Group) doesn't move when it has 44 Entertainment venues in the US. 

Predicting a re-rate for ALG and dropped $135k on it. www.imgur.com/8pDjB6J.png

Also dropped $150k on MYQ today. Too many pussies here.</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:12:11+10:00">
   <body>That might qualify you for a "big swinging tits or dick" flair.

Or is it 1 million that gets the flair? Can't remember.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 17:13:51+10:00">
   <body>Can I borrow 150k to drop in something?

Or you know, give me whatever job you have</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-04 17:20:33+10:00">
    <body>Entry-level Consultant / Analyst, doesn't really pay much for the amount of studying I've done.

Most of my funds are from the ASX. Up ~450% since May 2020.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 17:31:35+10:00">
     <body>... can I borrow 150k then?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-04 17:40:08+10:00">
      <body>Yeah you can borrow my ALG shares to short.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-04 17:51:58+10:00">
   <body>Tbh, I know alot of people will think you're stupid but in all honestly, to make money you've gotta fucking risk money. 

Good luck man, i really hope those stocks boom for you!</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-04 18:04:47+10:00">
    <body>Honestly, it applies to everything in life really. If you succeed, you're a genius, if you fail, you're a madman.

Anyways, I believe the risk/reward ratio is definitely in my favour here.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-03-04 18:05:56+10:00">
   <body>Any thoughts on why they're booming? Is it because it's coming into summer,  local travel,  things opening up there with vaccine roll-out? 

What types of venues does ALG have compared to those US based ones you mentioned?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-04 18:12:00+10:00">
    <body>Many others and I believe there is currently plenty of pent-up demand for travel and entertainment at this current point in time.

Furthermore, due to reduced expenses, household savings rate has increased too, allowing for higher entertainment expenditure in a post-vaccine environment. For reference, ALG pre-covid peaked at $1.63 in January and now it is $0.60.

ALG owns theme parks and US entertainment venues (bowling, food etc.) Anyways, I'd advise reading their annual report.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-03-04 18:57:03+10:00">
     <body>👍</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-04 17:12:19+10:00">
  <body>Planning on buying some EGR if the market turns around early on. was looking for a dip to get back in.
this company is going places with 2 factories in construction now and their share price is in a temporary dip in my opinion.

also looking at NVX for a t+2.  it's below my original buy in a month ago and sold for some profits but I reckon buy Friday sell Monday for some tendies 

this is the dip we've all been waiting for.  
opportunity is in front of us 🙂</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 17:25:59+10:00">
   <body>EGR @ 60c and NVX @ $2.40 are both absolute steals</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-04 19:06:36+10:00">
    <body>totally agree</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PogoStyle" created="2021-03-04 17:39:01+10:00">
   <body>How confident are you that EGR is in a dip at the moment?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-04 19:06:16+10:00">
    <body>Dropped from $1.10 a couple weeks ago.

maybe it will go down a bit more but long term it's going to go up as they will be producing when the plants are up and running next year I guess.

I guess all indicators point to it being in a dip, maybe watch and see if it flattens out.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Away-Many-749" created="2021-03-04 17:22:14+10:00">
  <body>If it's going to be another day like today I guess you'll find me with my pants around my ankles bent over ready for a jolly ol shafting from the ASX.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Darcyjay_" created="2021-03-04 17:25:17+10:00">
  <body>Hoooeeeey I’m down 12k this week. F U N</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="JustARandomMoniker" created="2021-03-04 18:29:02+10:00">
  <body>Dump VML or buy more. Depends just how fucked tomorrow is.</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-04 18:57:14+10:00">
   <body>I'll take it;)</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:38:54+10:00">
   <body>Dump it to me 😀</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="genuinelivesmatter" created="2021-03-04 18:57:00+10:00">
   <body>Rare earths are potentially good stocks. VML has a generally upward trend. But it depends on the current market conditions. I'd say follow, watch and monitor given the current circumstances. Could buy on a dip if it doesn't rise abruptly.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-03-04 19:15:28+10:00">
    <body>Good discounts on IXR at the moment</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-04 19:18:27+10:00">
     <body>Yep I’d second that. I got back into ixr today</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-03-04 19:52:12+10:00">
     <body>Yep - I was tempted by VML but the IXR clearance sale sucked me in.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snappo_B" created="2021-03-04 19:54:32+10:00">
   <body>I sold out of VML earlier in the week to take out some gains, but given today's dip I think I am going to buy back in. I have no doubts it will be siting above .08 pretty quickly!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Darcyjay_" created="2021-03-04 17:35:58+10:00">
  <body>I did pick up some IBX for .165 though so that’s nice</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-04 18:50:51+10:00">
   <body>Keep averaging up on ibx cause love it x</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Secondary92" created="2021-03-04 17:45:01+10:00">
  <body>Looking forward to doubling down on buying the dip tomorrow only to be fisted even further</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="cambit90" created="2021-03-04 18:31:42+10:00">
  <body>Brutal</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-03-04 19:06:29+10:00">
  <body>My portfolio was green today.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-04 19:15:29+10:00">
   <body>Mine was too until 10:05</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 19:27:45+10:00">
   <body>Yeah jxt was green today</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-04 20:16:09+10:00">
   <body>Congrats and also fuck you 😘</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="RayGamble" created="2021-03-04 19:20:18+10:00">
  <body>topping up on OAR whilst it’s down before the March results🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-03-04 19:36:00+10:00">
  <body>Consider: BPH now has less chance of approval than it did when the SP was 1c, and nothing else has changed.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="lycheeboi21" created="2021-03-04 19:41:15+10:00">
  <body>Big buy orders at 10-10.5c for PEN so plenty of people buying the dip


But why won't it go back up after it's dipped 😭😭😭</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 19:46:19+10:00">
   <body>It needs some form of stimulation for that.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lycheeboi21" created="2021-03-04 19:51:41+10:00">
    <body>I know 😞 I just want stonks to always go up</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-04 17:01:21+10:00">
  <body>Maybe this thread is the reason we are all in the red?

Can we stop the daily thread just for one day, to see if I'm right?!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="KezzaPwNz" created="2021-03-04 17:01:39+10:00">
  <body>Finally buy into this bloodbath</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="PogoStyle" created="2021-03-04 17:15:28+10:00">
  <body>My optimistic crystal-ball prediction for VML recovery by next week: [https://www.tradingview.com/x/qQGjbcNt/](https://www.tradingview.com/x/qQGjbcNt/)</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-04 17:26:44+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-04 17:26:44+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-03-04 20:12:04+10:00">
  <body>I’d like to get off this ride now please

RFX and AUZ still green even tho those paper bags are just a memory and the huge CCE spike just feels like a strange dream now. Fully back into red again like everything else. Little shit.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="WeirdEngineerGuy" created="2021-03-04 17:03:10+10:00">
  <body>Last ban length needs to be updated? [New figure is 2097152](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lx974v/finding_out_that_this_morning_is_red_damages_my/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;utm_source=share)</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="phantom_hax0r" created="2021-03-04 17:20:46+10:00">
   <body>It's actually longer, VPforFree did a suicide by cop by posting the survey, I got lazy in updating the number</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="WeirdEngineerGuy" created="2021-03-04 17:27:16+10:00">
    <body>No tears shed, its a coward death

Thankyou for replying oh mighty mod 🙏</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-03-04 20:18:19+10:00">
    <body>He hinted at giving up investing before his suicide, should've seen the signs.

F.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ProfileOne8032" created="2021-03-04 17:09:43+10:00">
  <body>Not even a maxi pad could stop the bleeding today. Going to hide tomorrow and revisit my stash of hopefully in date mi goreng to console myself</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-03-04 17:26:11+10:00">
  <body>At this rate I’ll just be bloody holding everything until the next round of quarterly reports.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-03-04 17:49:24+10:00">
  <body>probs write off all of march tbh, just keep buying dips i guess......</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-04 18:16:01+10:00">
   <body>Easier said than done. I would buy the dip if I could find it.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:41:36+10:00">
    <body>Buy the edge :P</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-04 18:45:09+10:00">
    <body>...seem to be catching falling knives instead</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-03-04 17:55:45+10:00">
  <body>Keen to average down and get some more TLG- it's looking oversold but cripes the sellers to buyers ratio has me sweaty knees knocking together while I wait</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-03-04 18:58:33+10:00">
   <body>IMO TLG won't go anywhere without huge insto interest. I haven't done a detailed dive on their assets etc but from a quick comparison to other greentech companies; they have like $5mil AUD cash &amp; need $1bil USD just to complete ONE project- the Niska mine/anode refinery project. They also burn ~$12m a year.

The Smedvig family (Norways Ellison's / Rineharts) sold out completely in January. 9% of the company. Pallinghurst pulled a director in August, after paying $10m to appoint two. They've since invested elsewhere, although they hold ~3% still through Pelmer SA. Mark Creasy still around, but he's small-fry by comparison.

The narrative seems to be that they need over $1bil just to do ONE project, which is- from what smarter people have told me- nowhere near enough to complete that one project. They have lost their biggest benefactor &amp; another has gone hands-off instead of helping them get that funding. Goldman owns a tiny bit, but they got given it for free so doesn't count. Mark Thompson seems like a cool dude, but not sure if he'll be able to secure that much money + get the relevant approvals etc in Sweden, when he lives in Perth. Very big payout if he manages to, but better chance would be Aussie company in Aus or Swedish company in Sweden IMO.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 19:35:06+10:00">
    <body>Thats some impressive DD that would benefit a lot of people who are looking into TLG / graphite or already bought TLG.

I would love to hear your thoughts on EGR.

From what I understand, we have $54mill+ in the bank, enough to complete phase 1 construction of its Australian battery anode purification facility. Phase one will allow 5000 tonnes per annum production,  but they plan to expand it in the future to 20,000 tonnes per annum. They also plan to open a second plant in Germany (these things will come in time,  with possibly more funding when needed. Whether thats from future CR or from profits from the initial facility we don't know). 

But current funds are enough to complete the Australian facility , and to me it seems like they're in a very good position,  right place at the right time.

I found the best material to learn what they're doing and what they're all about from the "Investor Presentation and Business Update" announcement on the 12/02/21

Edit: here is a link to the announcement im referring to https://www.ecograf.com.au/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/2175604.pdf</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-03-04 20:14:19+10:00">
     <body>I like EGR a lot. Was in ~$0.35-$0.4 but sold when it hit $0.970 within a couple days- lucky timing but figured it was a bit too quick. Now back in at $0.665, if it stays low long enough I'll stock up anywhere below $0.650.

They have a decent cash balance, a good relationship with WA gov &amp; ARENA- grants from both IIRC. Facility is politically important, due to independence (geopolitics) &amp; job creation. Their other projects have gotten significant interest- German one especially. The instos who bought in have sold some, but it's only ~10% of their holdings for 2-3 companies- again from memory. Given they had an instant 50% premium,  not selling more is a strong signal IMO.

They cover 2/3 of the basic green principles- reuse &amp; recycle. Also cost effective, clean graphite if scaled, with a lot of potential markets to enter into. Given inroads into EU already &amp; US listing soon, seems like the best pick to me.

Also interested in NVX, but riskier from what I see. MNS similar to TLG- lots of potential, little proof. CXL &amp; RFX I just don't understand yet. HZR is cool, also at the actualization stage, but again, don't understand it enough yet.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-03-04 20:19:53+10:00">
    <body>I agree with your general sentiment and share some of those concerns, particularly around the smedvig divestment and lack of any official word on why. 

A note on the numbers though. Current cash &gt;$30m after recent CR. The first project is Vittangi (Niska is a downstream project for 2025+) and the PFS had initial capex US$27m and stage 2 US$147m, which is much more achievable and poses significantly less risk than going straight to a $1bn capex project. A DFS is due this month so we’ll learn more then. Really need some binding offtakes to de-risk it. 

If Vittangi works out then securing funding for a  future $1bn project will be easier than from a standing start. The link-up with Swedish state-owned iron ore miner (and neighbor) [LKAB](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/LKAB) is promising in reducing sovereign risk, currently non-binding though so if/when it becomes a formal agreement that will represent another very significant de-risking for me. I see the company location in Europe (mine in Sweden, production in Germany, R&amp;D in Cambridge) as a huge benefit - on the doorstep of a major market with the political will to make real change in this space. Talga are also looking for cornerstone investors and appear to be close to formalising something - I’m not usually a fan of this approach due to the dilution and loss of control, but it would appear to be the best option in this case and will be done on a project basis, not the company. 

So significant risks of never getting started remain, but if they do there’s the potential to be a business 10x or more the current market cap. I’ve put the chance of succeeding at &gt;30% so it’s a +ev bet for me.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-04 18:20:38+10:00">
  <body>Through some miracle I’m only down 3% today. SOR held up ok and I got out of VML yesterday, got into EGR at $0.62.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:39:20+10:00">
   <body>You got the SOR arse yet?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-04 18:44:42+10:00">
    <body>Nope but that’s a real possibility tomorrow..</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:45:42+10:00">
     <body>I’ve been bag holding since 90c. I’m plenty SOR</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-04 19:28:38+10:00">
      <body>Yikes. I got in at 65c but have averaged down to 49, so it’s not too bad for me.. yet. Should be some good news later this
month after that investors presentation.

Or at least I really hope so.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:32:10+10:00">
       <body>Bought in at 90c, averaged down at 50c so avg price now is 71c. It wouldn’t be so bad except I FOMOd like a total retard and threw a tonne of cash at it at 90c so I have to put in a lot more if I want to move the needle now.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-04 19:23:47+10:00">
      <body>Ouch what's the plan here</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:26:36+10:00">
       <body>Keep holding, pray for salvation. Can’t even take the L and use it to offset other capital gain because it’s CGT exempt.</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-04 19:27:57+10:00">
        <body>Yeah I know. Its why I'd didnt play with it and probably never will. Its cool but the battery hype will live. I'll say little pray for you</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:29:46+10:00">
         <body>I’m hoping that the ASV stuff pays off to the point I can exit or at least free carry, as I expect that to progress faster than the self charging battery/printable memory stuff</body>
        </comment>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:33:13+10:00">
         <body>Honestly the no cgt thing makes it really vulnerable to pump and dump and manipulation. I like the tech but regret buying into it.</body>
         <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-04 19:35:28+10:00">
          <body>That's what I thought it was trader's dream really easy profit rather then offering some stability hence why the directors took there millions so fast</body>
          <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 19:36:12+10:00">
           <body>Yep, it certainly taught me a lot about what not to do.</body>
          </comment>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-04 18:45:57+10:00">
  <body>Sell everything and put it in a HISA.

.4% PA is more than -9% per week

 

*It’s miserable to imagine that*

*My losses will be realised*

*And become*

*A light green arrow at last*</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 19:14:01+10:00">
   <body>If you want to go that route might be better to put everything into a high dividend ETF (if you have a decent amount of cash). Or a high growth fund (if smaller cash). Never the bank. Fuck the banks</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-04 19:54:28+10:00">
    <body>It was tongue in cheek. You are right</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Otherwise_Giraffe255" created="2021-03-04 18:46:02+10:00">
  <body>Keeping an eye on CI1 ann tomorrow - I only liked it enough to have a buy order set at 0.04, but that was before the trading halt / prospect of a cap raise</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-03-04 19:35:02+10:00">
   <body>if tmr is as red as today was it will get slaughtered. I also had a buy order at 0.038 but missed the rocket. not sure how I feel about it now. any upwards movement will be met by heavy selling when the baggies want to get out</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mulligun" created="2021-03-04 18:52:08+10:00">
  <body>Sold the rest of my BPH today for .125. Minor bummer but still got out with a 3 bagger overall so not too bothered. I knew the risks when I bought this bad boy and stuck to my plan, risk is too high now not to take the profits and run.

Moving those $$ into gold miners RRL and RED - I think we'll see a big uptick in both of these bad boys over the next couple of years regardless of the rest of the market (medium term). A lot of talk about a commodity super cycle imminent.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="mulligun" created="2021-03-04 18:54:52+10:00">
   <body>Also anyone here can tell you I've been a longish term BPH holder - but I still find the boomer rage over Scummo in here hilarious. Get shit on boomers, we played the scumbag game of supporting fossil fuels and lost. Deal with the karma like adults.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="GetRichOrCryTrying1" created="2021-03-04 19:33:07+10:00">
  <body>I would have been ok if NOPTA or KP didn't approve PEP-11. Having Scomo make a statement before the offical decision is absolutely bullshit.

I thought I knew the risks with BPH and BUY but being used to soften the blow of cabinet rapists wasn't one that I factored into my R/B analysis!</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="upthebaggers" created="2021-03-04 19:38:03+10:00">
   <body>The more I think about it the madder I get. The fucked thing is, this government, which has had a mare of a last 18 months, will get re-elected easily.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="hanstarinoz" created="2021-03-04 20:29:41+10:00">
   <body>Totally agreed</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Georgie_Syd" created="2021-03-04 20:19:13+10:00">
  <body>Ass raped today.. almost 6k down... just riding it out.. I am sure come April the recovery will be well underway.. Johnson and Johnson vaccines 💉 now approved and rolling out also..</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-04 20:29:52+10:00">
   <body>If there's one lesson I like to pass on is learn to cut your losses - the stock market is always there and you can always get back in =p

But if you aren't trading actively, then ignore me</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mokeh1" created="2021-03-04 17:05:19+10:00">
  <body>*sorry posted here as cannot make my own post as levels too low*

A Beginner Trader Who's Eyes Are Burnt Red

Hi everyone, 

I'm a beginner trader and my first month of trading is off to a rocky start, as to be expected...right?

I've learnt that when someone makes money, someone else loses, and I'm sick of being the one who looses. I can recognise simple stock indicators, like volume, EPS, profits, debts and most financial indicators on a balance sheet etc. But the more I learn, I realise the less I know. And the picture of an amateur trader like me getting chewed up and spat out in the big trading world becomes ever more clear. 

I realised I need an edge, I need to be smarter, make better predictions...I'm hungry for more. As trading amongst young people like me becomes more popular, I see opportunity. Opportunity to rob clueless little fish just like me, to become the shark, and pave my sweet road to riches. But I'm still the little fish, but hey...At least I know that right?  

So with a basic knowledge of shares and the stock market, what direction would you point someone like me to analyse a company, and the market as a whole, to find a good investment?  And I'm not talking about what someone finds on the first page of Google when they search "How to find a good stonk." I'm talking more detail, more in-depth, above the average person's analysis...work I can be confident in. Regardless if they're short, mid or long term analysis, if they work (even ones that don't) I want to hear 'em!  

Any direction to, or analysis method names or strategies that you've found to be successful, so I can do further research, will be greatly appreciated. Also, I'd love to hear your experiences with said methods...good or bad!

Thanks everyone, I look forward to us getting rich!!!!</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="snuffrix" created="2021-03-04 17:34:42+10:00">
   <body>Cringe</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="sims3k" created="2021-03-04 17:48:14+10:00">
   <body>This should be a copypasta</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:08:39+10:00">
   <body>Check out "invest for the future " and his negative 20/20 methodology. On youtube.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 17:34:50+10:00">
    <body>The lovely older gentleman that is Johnny Palmer.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:36:37+10:00">
     <body>I can't remember the exact number but isn't he making  close to 20% returns year on year?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 17:38:25+10:00">
      <body>I think he had a great year last year, but c’mon that’s nothing that impressive really given the markets. 

I am a little confused at his momentum approach as it seems to run contrary to his -20/20 portfolio.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:44:11+10:00">
       <body>No i thought his average over the last few years was 20%...</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 17:45:36+10:00">
        <body>That’s pretty good. If that’s the case why is he messing with his formula?</body>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:49:15+10:00">
         <body>To try and make more money???</body>
         <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-03-04 17:50:04+10:00">
          <body>Silly to try and make more than 20% per annum. If he had a system which was producing those return he was one of the worlds best investors- ever.</body>
          <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:51:54+10:00">
           <body>Look i could be wrong but i thought that was his yearly average.</body>
           <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
           </comment>
          </comment>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-03-04 17:09:36+10:00">
   <body>You fucked up somewhere, the first trades are supposed to be easy gains and the pain comes later</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:13:15+10:00">
    <body>Lol, i started around February March last year. 

No easy gains for me.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 17:21:04+10:00">
     <body>Wow if only u started right after march lmao</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-04 17:21:50+10:00">
      <body>I still made bags on stocks i just started with a 50% realized loss on most of my portfolio</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ProfileOne8032" created="2021-03-04 17:07:46+10:00">
   <body>You are in the wrong sub. This is a casino</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-04 17:08:15+10:00">
   <body>Just search this thread daily and the stock that has the most rockets next to it, just get on and you'll be right.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-04 17:07:46+10:00">
   <body>If the moon is bright and easily visible from where you are the night before you want to buy a certain stock, buy it.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="dhking71" created="2021-03-04 17:23:16+10:00">
   <body>Dude this isn’t a subreddit to ask for help. Take the shit pumps from the fuckers posting, lose money, then learn for yourself.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-04 17:27:52+10:00">
   <body>I've been doing this a few years. I still know next to nothing. People who have been in the stock market six months know alot I don't.

What I do know is buying a stock you believe in and holding that for a good six months let it blow up.

CNBC is a good tool to see what is happening in the US with certain sectors. Generally if travel stocks go up in the US it happens the next day in Australia.
Sometimes it doesn't and you can get burnt lol.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Aquadog66" created="2021-03-04 20:15:09+10:00">
   <body>Everybody needs to learn to read charts and time the market in order to make higher probability bets. I see a lot of people here buying so called dips when the actual stock is in a downtrend and expecting it to go higher in the next few days. Not a good strategy. YouTube real life trading and start learning to trade.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 17:12:02+10:00">
  <body>Sooo...

Everyone ready for Friday? 🙃</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="reckless-rex" created="2021-03-04 17:17:20+10:00">
  <body>Ready to limp some more due to torn asshole from today</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-03-04 18:03:12+10:00">
   <body>But did you have fun though?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="The_Frag_Man" created="2021-03-04 17:33:38+10:00">
  <body>I'm not even going to look tomorrow</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-04 18:43:29+10:00">
   <body>Look for bargains</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-03-04 19:49:25+10:00">
  <body>Overall red and total down but
But a couple of greens - EPN &amp; JXT and
Still holding profits in DW8, CI1, IOU, LIT, AEF, IHL, PPH, VAS &amp; Z1P.
Looking to buy the dip in VR1, A3D</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="simon2105" created="2021-03-04 20:21:48+10:00">
  <body>Lube up your buttholes, it's Friday tomorrow!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-04 20:22:55+10:00">
  <body>What a painful day...no saviours in the portfolio.

Might just switch it off and come back next week.

Good luck autismo’s !!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-03-04 20:26:54+10:00">
  <body>Sold Z1P &amp; EGR today to protect my house deposit fund still holding FYI. But this market is looking shaky for spec stocks. Probably will turn around next week now I’ve sold but</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="obctau" created="2021-03-04 20:27:19+10:00">
  <body>I'm scared for NVA</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-03-04 20:29:04+10:00">
   <body>They’re investing in electric aircraft now? wtf</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-03-04 17:33:49+10:00">
  <body>Goddamn good thing  I pulled out of MYD on the day I bought it</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-03-04 18:01:20+10:00">
   <body>Same</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-04 17:47:15+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-04 17:47:16+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Insolvable_Judo" created="2021-03-04 18:56:46+10:00">
  <body>What happened to CRO?</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-03-04 19:07:14+10:00">
   <body>They paid an asset manager called Kaai capital to pump the share price, a director also sold 3 million shares (30% of his total holding), it also made only $300k revenue and was valued in the hundreds of millions etc. Isn’t the first stock to multi bag on hype and trap a bunch of retail bagholders, nor will it be the last.</body>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Bigjohnthug" created="2021-03-04 19:35:20+10:00">
    <body>It's not even *the first time this stock* has been pumped to trap retail investors. Rule of thumb: if they have a complex software product but a default WordPress template for a website, it's a pump.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="bingeandpurgatory" created="2021-03-04 20:18:38+10:00">
    <body>Oh shit. I hold some CRO and have been trying not to check my portfolio daily. Haven't looked in a week now so this doesn't sound good. Last I checked it was all hype.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-03-04 20:09:42+10:00">
   <body>CRO’s management was sketchy as fuck 6 months ago and they’re sketchy as fuck now.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="daddyhitch" created="2021-03-04 19:05:46+10:00">
  <body>Is there a sub for IPOs</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-04 19:18:52+10:00">
   <body>https://smallcaps.com.au/upcoming-ipos/</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-04 20:12:57+10:00">
    <body>sick cunt</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="autodidact31" created="2021-03-04 19:09:24+10:00">
   <body>Also interested</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-04 19:12:25+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-04 19:12:26+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-04 19:16:56+10:00">
  <body>Slightly off topic, why can't I see my meme in new but my friend can?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-04 19:58:49+10:00">
   <body>https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lxfecq/xst_is_gonna_give_it_too_ya/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;utm_source=share

You posted it twice. 1 got deleted.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-04 20:06:14+10:00">
    <body>I deleted one to change the title my bad</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-04 20:11:24+10:00">
     <body>Maybe when you reposted you did it twice. 1 should still be on the sub (the one i linked) the duplicate was removed from the sub but is still visible on your account.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-04 20:13:15+10:00">
      <body>Aight, as long as one is up I am happy, sorry for being autistic</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-04 20:18:05+10:00">
       <body>We're all autistic here...</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-04 19:39:06+10:00">
   <body>Maybe it's shit. Na jokes haha. You looking on app?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-04 19:46:58+10:00">
    <body>Yeah the app, I'll check on the website. Can't see on website also shame</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Big_Rooster91" created="2021-03-04 19:41:08+10:00">
  <body>Glad EGR closed at 60c... was afraid of a falling knife type scenario</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-04 20:23:59+10:00">
   <body>Just feels like it was deliberately closed like that so it can be sold down even more tomorrow</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="No_Nefariousness_131" created="2021-03-04 20:16:09+10:00">
  <body>LETS GO</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-04 20:21:56+10:00">
  <body>Look, I'm not saying this just because today was red but I'm ditching the ASX. It's been fun folks. Market too small, too slow and the stonks are just shit. I don't know how in good conscience you can invest in stuff like BPH and FFG. Keep it real</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 20:22:46+10:00">
   <body>Brutal...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="chocchillson" created="2021-03-04 20:23:56+10:00">
  <body>Got a packet of SNAS using Tom's money to apply as a salve to the rest of my portfolio. Looking like it'll pay off.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-03-04 19:46:47+10:00">
  <body>serious question time: I have an average buy in price of 9.9 on z1p, given the economy right now and the constant red dildo days I am thinking about cashing out tomorrow..the anxiety is killing me. I figured it will continue to drop until next quarter update.. and I'll buy back in once this bullshit has blown over.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-04 20:13:34+10:00">
   <body>This mentality is what makes the stocks drop and continue to drop though, if everyone bought company’s based on fundamentals there’s zero reason to sell just because the market is having a bad session.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-03-04 20:18:59+10:00">
    <body>I know and I agree .. that's why I'm torn. I truly believe in the business but can't sit by when I'm certain it's going to continue to tank as long as this bond yeild bullshit is happening. im seeing a clear rotation out of speci techs to blue chips. I happen to hold both and lucky for me the big 4 held my profile together today. everything else went to shit. big question is , is this rotation temporary or is it the end of the bull market ...</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-04 20:24:41+10:00">
     <body>People and markets fear change, just like when the first lockdowns and shit happens it tanked and panic selling happened, now economy is going good and interest rates may rise so it’s a change and people once again panic but it all settles eventually. The economy is becoming stronger and that’s awesome it’s just a cycle that will eventually level out, if I was you and I truly believe in the company long term I’d try time the bottom and dollar average down but that’s just me. I’ve held plenty of stocks that have halved and eventually return to normal and continue to go up. I guess it depends if you’d rather relocate that capital somewhere else with potential higher growth over the short term. Personally I stay away from BNPL I held IOU at .185 and it sat at 13c for ages and I got out at 23c and even though it’s higher now I couldn’t care less because it’s just too up and down for me. But my opinion is just one opinion</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="JacDizzy" created="2021-03-04 20:20:47+10:00">
   <body>You could be right but IMO dont paper hands on a Friday.  Monday’s = more green stonks and profit taking if you must. Not financial advice. I’m in at 7.9 but was thinking of averaging up at 10 because I like the stock so 🤷🏼‍♀️🤣</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-03-04 20:21:03+10:00">
   <body>also, I know we like to think of ourselves as a bunch of smooth brain autist cowboys, but I also think this community is full of legit smart and logical people. I think we could be doing better as a community talking about this challenge instead of constantly saying buy the dip etc..</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-04 20:26:32+10:00">
   <body>I jumped out today, less than I wanted but I'm losing faith in bnpl. It's very suddenly getting saturated, and at the price you and I got Z1P, I honestly think there is more risk than reward.

If you still have faith in the sector, I'd pull out of Z1P and jump into IOU.

However, that's my opinion. Today I pulled out of Z1P and went hard into BPH, soooooo</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-04 18:08:50+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="The_Frag_Man" created="2021-03-04 18:20:23+10:00">
   <body>what is the TSX?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Elegantmango77" created="2021-03-04 18:25:38+10:00">
    <body>Toronto exchange</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-04 19:31:49+10:00">
     <body>If the question was how to get access i looked into it recently. Only option was to pay $60 brokerage per trade plus account keeping fee which was fine but there wasn't  enough benefit for what I wanted to put in for so eh.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-8" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-04 17:21:26+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-03-04 18:02:39+10:00">
   <body>Woeful language!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
