<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-03-12 Friday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>LOT (12) HYPE=16</mention>
  <mention>LRS (10) HYPE=16, GAMBLE=-10</mention>
  <mention>FLT (8) HYPE=16, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>SOR (8) GAMBLE=-10</mention>
  <mention>DW8 (8) </mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:35:01+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
   <body>So the ASX Sharemarket game is up, which is a thing my school is running where you can simulate investing with $50,000. The few winners take home a couple hundred bucks and it's statewide so some big competition.

[Here are the companies I can invest in.](https://www.reddit.com/user/Kriifrux/comments/lu20jm/list_of_all_asx_school_sharemarket_game_companies/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;context=3)

Let me know which ones are your top picks are what prices I should set my limit orders at.

So far I'm probably going to buy:

* A2M if it starts looking more promising
* AIA
* BRG
* CCP
* FLT as soon as it dips
* KGN
* LYC
* SFR if it dips
* SYD
* TCL
* WEB as soon as it dips
* WPL
* Z1P as soon as the dump is done

I'm likely to just split my money between all of them equally, or potentially more in one if yall are bullish on it. These are just based on suggestions of what people recommended when I asked around a week ago or so. Let me know if I should change or add some, or if I should even make a poll.

Side note: I have no idea what the fuck I'm doing. But since I won't be making any real losses, fire away with your suggestions.</body>
   <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="jaamzzz" created="2021-03-11 19:46:11+10:00">
    <body>I find it hilarious how schools try to teach students about the sharemarket using that game. It teaches you the exact opposite lesson they'd want you to know. it goes for what? like 2 months? so how else are you gonna win without yeeting 10k+ into speccy penny stocks hoping it'll rocket.

When I did it at school, we were in the midst of the GFC, so everyone got fucked and all my mates are now scared of the stock market.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:48:36+10:00">
     <body>Hahaha yeah it is a bit silly especially with the fucking dividends. I think it runs for like maybe half a year? Maybe it was until May I think.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jaamzzz" created="2021-03-11 19:55:02+10:00">
      <body>I wish you all the best, and that your companies still exist 10 years later, unlike the ones my group chose.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-11 19:58:39+10:00">
    <body>Hey champ. [Here's](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/m090uk/best_yolo_for_asx_stock_market_game/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;utm_source=share) a link to the last person who asked, and there's a link in that to the one before 👍</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 20:12:31+10:00">
     <body>Thanks mate</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="UhOhNoOnion" created="2021-03-11 19:40:31+10:00">
    <body>Only buy the minimum number of shares if you want to win, I think I’ve heard people say it’s 4? Of those you’ve mentioned, LYC, KGN, FLT and Z1P would be my picks. You could either win convincingly or come dead last</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:41:16+10:00">
     <body>Yeah max is 25% portfolio diversification on 1 company.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:43:28+10:00">
     <body>Great picks though. What prices should I set my limit orders and should I just chuck them in now?
Your guess is as good as mine and since I won't lose anything, you don't have to worry about the financial advice crap.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="UhOhNoOnion" created="2021-03-11 20:17:38+10:00">
      <body>Market buy 3;45pm tomorrow 25% each</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 20:20:12+10:00">
       <body>Would it not be a good idea to consider some other companies like WEB, BHP or AIA for example? Maybe to allocate some percentage to them?

EDIT: What about Afterpay? They seem to be below their intrinsic value.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Nsj_1" created="2021-03-11 20:14:42+10:00">
    <body>Day trade APT and Z1P.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-11 20:30:37+10:00">
    <body>I would so love to help you buddy but damn....i have 20 stonks in my portfolio and the only one i matched with from your list is WEB - and youve missed the bottom for that and shouldn't go anywhere near it now.
Good luck !</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 20:31:30+10:00">
     <body>Fair enough.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-11 17:22:25+10:00">
   <body>I now believe zip won’t hit 14 or above again
I think it’s done and PayPal will kill it
Tnt bounced a bit back
Not a lot though

Now excuse me , I’ve got grain waves to eat</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="lululemonhead" created="2021-03-11 18:23:24+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>PayPal is trash, merchants do not like dealing with them. They locked up 100k of mine back when I was a power seller and the stories seem common. Their customer support is atrocious. Go look at the trust pilot reviews and some of the stories in r/entrepreneur. I’m not even a Z1P holder, all I’m saying is PayPal will need to up their game hardcore so merchants trust them.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 19:15:05+10:00">
     <body>If PayPal offer something better than afterpay and zip they will be obliterated. Just a blip in existence.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SlaughterRain" created="2021-03-11 19:52:47+10:00">
    <body>Never trust a proud Grain Wave eater, eat a real chip cunt.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-11 20:03:07+10:00">
     <body>Grain waves and a glass of soy milk is my fav! I did the grain waves into the milk</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SlaughterRain" created="2021-03-11 20:29:55+10:00">
      <body>You are truly a lost cause.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-03-11 19:11:23+10:00">
   <body>Day two of holding my $6million market cap mining speccie. ZERO shares traded today. Try again tomorrow I guess.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-03-11 19:27:09+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>It has potential to get exciting quickly!</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="autodidact31" created="2021-03-11 19:34:03+10:00">
     <body>Ticker?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-03-11 19:55:46+10:00">
      <body>I think Mr Star is keeping to themself so that they don't inadvertently lose anyone a bunch of cash in the event it gets delisted. My comment was about how at a MC of 6 mil, any significant event has the ability to generate you a lot of bags very quickly</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ASXg0d" created="2021-03-11 19:49:28+10:00">
      <body>I bet DLP and he bought $70k</body>
      <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-03-11 19:53:11+10:00">
       <body>Nope, when I said zero shares traded I don't mean me- nobody at all bought or sold shares in this stock today lol</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 19:57:54+10:00">
    <body>Sounds like VAL, though much less market cap</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-11 20:34:41+10:00">
    <body>Zero !
Thats brilliant !

That made me laugh</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="LYC_97" created="2021-03-11 17:58:04+10:00">
   <body>Got 5k to drop what do i buy</body>
   <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="throwaway8726529" created="2021-03-11 18:04:51+10:00">
    <body>LRS or RAC. Depends how big a gamble you wanna do.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Adrenaline06" created="2021-03-11 18:35:33+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>LRS or PUR or EXR for some tendies (hopefully).

APX for a long term value hold.

ZIP if you want to age 20 years in 20 days</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:24:56+10:00">
    <body>DLC, closed 16% up on huge... volume.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 18:41:13+10:00">
     <body>😢</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:41:53+10:00">
      <body>You know I’m playing</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 18:41:31+10:00">
    <body>Rabbitohs to beat storm tonight 1.90</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="bnplstrategist" created="2021-03-11 18:46:50+10:00">
     <body>Alex Johnson first try scorer</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 19:10:51+10:00">
      <body>give me my money back</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-11 19:46:40+10:00">
     <body>I dare you to throw that down on the current odds</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Christiee28" created="2021-03-11 19:54:41+10:00">
     <body>Look for something with a money back special, not even the ASX can offer you that</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-11 17:59:15+10:00">
    <body>LRS</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SupLord" created="2021-03-11 18:11:10+10:00">
    <body>DW8</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Lkorjo" created="2021-03-11 18:40:52+10:00" sentiment="GAMBLE 0">
    <body>PUR VML or even NVA for a long term punt</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:49:46+10:00">
    <body>PUR, LRS, or LPD

Or DLC</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-11 18:48:55+10:00">
    <body>Ixr</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-11 18:13:32+10:00">
    <body>SRN</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="dahmachino" created="2021-03-11 19:06:38+10:00">
    <body>PRL</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-11 18:02:24+10:00">
    <body>CYM or MLX. They both going up till their joint announcement.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="willkds" created="2021-03-11 18:35:00+10:00">
    <body>ADN</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-11 19:12:02+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>PUR / NVA / WWI [if it dips, near term most rewarding potentially]</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Ratsbox" created="2021-03-11 20:01:41+10:00">
    <body>PUR / LRS / PRL</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 17:59:27+10:00">
   <body>Gonna try and decide tonight between QPM, ROO or NC6 to dip toes in tomorrow while they’re cheap..</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:42:28+10:00">
    <body>Never heard of them. Must be good ones</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 20:25:39+10:00">
     <body>Feeling keen on sustainable stonks as I can understand their fundamentals. QPM is aiming to be a zero waste battery metals producer. NC6 is producing plant cellulose replacement for textile industries (including face masks) made use food waste. ROO is working on technology to improve water uptake efficiency in crops based on root temperature.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FebWolf" created="2021-03-11 18:47:52+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>QPM would be my humble opinion. I'm not holding them either. Had a good look at them about a week ago but no free cash atm.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 20:19:31+10:00">
     <body>I’m torn. I love both NC6 and QPM boards and products. QPM has nearly 5 million more on the sell side than the buy, so I might wait and see if the price pushes down a bit more.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 20:27:51+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
     <body>Think I’m gonna go for NC6 this week. Love NC6 and QPM boards and products but NC6 is in a bigger dip and has higher insider ownership. QPM has 5mil more on the sell side than the buy so potential to dip further, will wait and see if I can get in lower next week.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="slipperygypsy92" created="2021-03-11 19:11:11+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Just heard us mentioned on equity mates, pretty funny conversation about iCandy and 🚀 rating system</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:00:58+10:00">
    <body>I really laughed at the REI = Rocket Emoji Indicator. Speccy McGee delivered the goods.

Honestly, a good podcast too, really enjoy those boys</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="slipperygypsy92" created="2021-03-11 20:04:08+10:00">
     <body>Same, Fucking hilarious. What about that one listener who dm’d them saying enough of this segment 🙄 boomers 🤦🏼‍♂️</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:08:03+10:00">
      <body>Haha 'you boys need to be more serious', fuck off with your Telstra and BHP shares</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-11 20:13:48+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Excited for tomorrow - should be a green Friday (for once...!!)

Oil booming, rare earths booming, iron ore booming, tin booming. Happy days at the start of this commodity super-cycle !!

SHE / SRK / IXR / TMZ 

🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:32:11+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>A small pump for BRN. Recent weeks have seen the SP drop (below what I've paid mind you), I do honestly feel it's a good purchasing opportunity as selection for phase 2 or their SBIR program takes place on the 18th of March, NASA have had access to Brainchip's Akida chip and I feel pretty comfortable that it'll make selection for phase 2. As far an on the Edge AI goes Brainchip is currently in a league of it's own, but because we all have too much time on our hands, feel free to look into it for yourself. Also with tech stocks making a slight comeback that'll also work in BRN's favour.

BUT what would I know I'm just a random reddit guy.

Oh wait I forgot  🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 17:38:43+10:00">
   <body>Posted my writeup on the DLC piss-take today in a separate thread, be interested to hear everyone's thoughts.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-11 17:44:57+10:00">
    <body> I wonder if you'll cause anyone to buy in, but then again they'll assume we're just pumping and dumping it...</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 17:47:52+10:00">
     <body>I honestly don't think anyone could be that retarded, but I think we did make something buy today (sentiment algos). Then again, the depths of autism on this subreddit might surprise me.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:26:41+10:00">
      <body>I hope it was mostly sentiment algos and not individual autists getting screwed</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:54:00+10:00">
       <body>Would have been happy day trading it today</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-11 18:29:54+10:00">
    <body>Just read it, that’s hilarious</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-11 19:02:51+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>Good write up mate. Today was fun too - I had some LOL moments. However, it is a reminder of the power of words and the damage they can do when people can't read tone or intent.

Having said that, you would have to be a special kind of special to think DLC a good get. 🚀🚀🚀</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-03-11 17:13:50+10:00">
   <body>These red days have cured all my fomo in stonks!</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:40:08+10:00">
    <body>Certainly should have cured a lot of peoples desire to chase rockets</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SoulHoarder" created="2021-03-11 19:01:01+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
     <body>Who knew it would be so bad if you pointed the rockets towards Earth🚀🌏? Can we point them back to space please?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="53" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-11 18:51:26+10:00">
  <body>Gonna be taking a break from reddit for a while. By reddit I mean this sub. Just wanna say thanks to all for keeping me entertained for the past few months. Career has just gone next level and need to dedicate alot of time to it. 

Unfortunately I have no self control to only be coming on here once a day but its been a healthy addiction thats made me laugh way to much.

Let the detox begin I guess.</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="_PixelRage" created="2021-03-11 18:52:51+10:00">
   <body>Next level career hey? You finally become a high class escort instead of working the streets</body>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-11 18:55:35+10:00">
    <body>No more sucking white shit out of dirty hose for this bad boy. 

Extras are just included in the price,</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="apejustgimmetendies" created="2021-03-11 19:07:23+10:00">
   <body>Goodluck, I'll be awaiting your return</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="logman_aus" created="2021-03-11 19:08:08+10:00">
   <body>SSkkkkkiiiiiiiiipppppeeeeerrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-03-11 19:08:24+10:00">
   <body>But.... I won't see the love ark between you and kinky penguin :( I'll miss it deeply. 


You better come back soon man</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-11 19:24:15+10:00">
   <body>Good luck and godspeed mate.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 19:42:17+10:00">
   <body>Calls on your career then

We'll miss ya, don't forget about us when they have you all suited up and looking pretty for a camera</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-11 19:32:47+10:00">
   <body>Good luck!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="woodenlife" created="2021-03-11 20:23:56+10:00">
   <body>Good luck fella, hopefully see you around the traps.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="31" downs="0" author="logofpoo" created="2021-03-11 17:10:24+10:00">
  <body>going to try meth tomorrow, everything’s down the shitter at this point, may as well swim with the tide not against it</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="LifeIsAStateOfFlux" created="2021-03-11 17:12:19+10:00">
   <body>METH is actually a ticker in US lol!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-11 17:21:05+10:00">
   <body>The crystal pistol 💎🔫</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-03-11 17:23:23+10:00">
    <body>The see through didgeridoo</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="glueckskind11" created="2021-03-11 17:40:38+10:00">
     <body>I read that as dildo</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 19:16:29+10:00">
    <body>The glass Barbie</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 18:04:24+10:00">
   <body>I don't reccomend this lol. DYOR</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:41:07+10:00">
   <body>GLTAH!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="29" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-11 17:57:52+10:00">
  <body>Gonna take a lot more than one lukewarm green day to scrape back the losses of the past several week-long shitshow 😕</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="buffalo_bill27" created="2021-03-11 18:04:48+10:00">
   <body>True, but having said that, better than another red day</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-11 18:11:08+10:00">
   <body>Yep, this. Down a good 20% the last couple of weeks.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:51:48+10:00">
   <body>I'm one LRS pip away from having an entirely red portfolio. 11 items</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="is2017goingtobebad" created="2021-03-11 17:25:41+10:00">
  <body>Holy fuck did you guys see the after close sales on Afterpay?

1 sale worth 3.5m and 5 sales worth 1m each and lots of sales well over 500k.

I guess something big is gonna happen tomorrow. Either they are in for a wild ride or they going for their next house in Toorak.

Damn.

Edit: Just saw a 333M sale. Damn even more.</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-03-11 17:31:03+10:00">
   <body>Happens daily on APT tbh

Edit: ok the 333 is big. Substantial holder notice surely.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 17:58:47+10:00">
   <body>Fuuuuck me. I'll watch when i can but i'll be working tomorrow open</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-11 18:13:47+10:00">
    <body>My bad, i bought a put 😂</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 18:15:11+10:00">
     <body>Warn me so i can buy a call</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-11 18:17:05+10:00">
      <body>😂 I'll give you a heads up</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 18:17:57+10:00">
       <body>Will this count as insider trading?</body>
       <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-11 18:20:02+10:00">
        <body>Na, but if you take the other side of my trades, before you know it you'll be rich</body>
        <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 18:21:34+10:00">
         <body>;)</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 18:44:24+10:00">
    <body>what you can't go to the toilet at open and do a bog and get on your phone?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 18:46:59+10:00">
     <body>No. Not on this job. I'm on from 8.30 till about 11am and there is no time to piss or shit.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-11 18:32:30+10:00">
   <body>That’s huge, someone loves the stock</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 18:45:03+10:00">
    <body>he said sales.</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-11 18:46:18+10:00">
     <body>Someone doesn’t love the stock.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 19:11:48+10:00">
      <body>How is it classed as a sale or as a purchase? 

Honestly thought it's the same thing. There's someone wanting to sell 333m and someone wanting to buy 333m</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="HeiPando" created="2021-03-11 19:28:33+10:00">
   <body>I bet it s Blackrock selling out lol</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-11 17:31:31+10:00">
   <body>[deleted]</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-03-11 17:33:13+10:00">
    <body>Bruh 333M?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TheIronSheiky" created="2021-03-11 18:45:36+10:00">
   <body>With that new PayPal payment plan coming for aussies  in July or whatever, what will happen to zip/afterpay pricing?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-11 18:10:10+10:00">
  <body>Whenever I doubt my portfolio I think about the poor bastard who sold $13k of WBC right before their February earnings which pushed them up 10% to buy ZIP at $14 and then planned to shift it all to IOU when it was still probably in the 60s.

(Sorry if this was you but yeah wow, rip. Thanks for the cautionary tale at least.)</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="realhero83" created="2021-03-11 18:35:20+10:00">
   <body>He's probably swinging from a rope. Hopefully this person would realise he's got no common sense and maybe Vanguard ETF investing is more for him</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tbarbeast" created="2021-03-11 19:14:04+10:00">
   <body>Sucks to be that guy</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-11 20:19:33+10:00">
   <body>I was up like 300% on IOU, now only 150%. Slowly dropping daily, do you think it has done for a good while? Would you buy it now?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-11 20:32:57+10:00">
    <body>No I wouldn’t but it’s not my style. 

I also think people misunderstand what IOU does. They provide platform services to others. So in the BNPL space they provide their white labelplatform to others. They aren’t Afterpay in that sense - they are one layer away from consumer facing. That might be fine, but it also means that they are chasing a margin of a margin and the BNPL margins already seem so thin that no one (not even a giant like Afterpy) can make money out of it even with historically low interest rates. 

There’s a reason why credit cards charge interest, and why there’s a practical floor on how low the interest gets even if you shop around. It’s not like there’s a lack of competition in the credit card space - so that’s an indicator of the true nature of what it takes to make money on mass consumer credit.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-03-11 17:13:50+10:00">
  <body>These red days have cured all my fomo in stonks!</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:40:08+10:00">
   <body>Certainly should have cured a lot of peoples desire to chase rockets</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SoulHoarder" created="2021-03-11 19:01:01+10:00">
    <body>Who knew it would be so bad if you pointed the rockets towards Earth🚀🌏? Can we point them back to space please?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 17:46:42+10:00">
  <body>OMFG NASDAQ futures are GREEN again. I'd expect another 2% rise at closing bell and for Z1P tomorrow to finish sub $7.50 because it's a shit business and people have realised that.</body>
  <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-11 17:58:06+10:00">
   <body>This is the first time you've said they're green when they're actually green.</body>
   <comment ups="-7" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 18:43:08+10:00">
    <body>oh look the autist is back. proved you wrong yesterday and now you're still crying. If you don't want to come to the moon just step off and leave your mums number.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-11 18:55:21+10:00">
     <body>You didn't. You literally posted futures were green 2.5% when they were in fact red, then you came back way later at market open when the nasdaq was green and you claimed to be correct. And if you want to play the come back later when it suits you game, nasdaq closed red anyway.</body>
     <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 19:11:43+10:00">
      <body>you're adopted.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Possible_Ice882" created="2021-03-11 17:48:19+10:00">
   <body>-2% at closing and zip finishing above $9. Got it</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="JacDizzy" created="2021-03-11 19:16:51+10:00">
    <body>Buy more ZIP. Got it.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Almighti3" created="2021-03-11 17:14:48+10:00">
  <body>FLT just sums up how stupid the market is as a whole. Full of idiots with too much money who will make more money because of other idiots. I actually feel stupid for not jumping in and taking their money. But it’s just so overpriced I just thought it wasn’t possible. I’m actually amazed.</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-11 17:36:24+10:00">
   <body>I can’t believe FLT was still in business BEFORE covid. The fact that its still worth 3.5B and recovering is staggering. Boomers gonna boom I guess.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-03-11 17:16:56+10:00">
   <body>Word, buy my shit you boomer cunts. 

Can't you all get excited about weed and copper and uranium and rare earths for a bit</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-03-11 17:41:57+10:00">
   <body>FLT will exist for as long as there’s cashed up boomers who are either too lazy, scared or incompetent to book their own flights/accomodation/tours.

They’re probably the same ones buying FLT.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-11 18:00:20+10:00">
   <body>FLT is definitely the AGL of travel stocks, for some reason the market hasn't realised this yet</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-11 17:22:25+10:00">
  <body>I now believe zip won’t hit 14 or above again
I think it’s done and PayPal will kill it
Tnt bounced a bit back
Not a lot though

Now excuse me , I’ve got grain waves to eat</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="lululemonhead" created="2021-03-11 18:23:24+10:00">
   <body>PayPal is trash, merchants do not like dealing with them. They locked up 100k of mine back when I was a power seller and the stories seem common. Their customer support is atrocious. Go look at the trust pilot reviews and some of the stories in r/entrepreneur. I’m not even a Z1P holder, all I’m saying is PayPal will need to up their game hardcore so merchants trust them.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 19:15:05+10:00">
    <body>If PayPal offer something better than afterpay and zip they will be obliterated. Just a blip in existence.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SlaughterRain" created="2021-03-11 19:52:47+10:00">
   <body>Never trust a proud Grain Wave eater, eat a real chip cunt.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-11 20:03:07+10:00">
    <body>Grain waves and a glass of soy milk is my fav! I did the grain waves into the milk</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SlaughterRain" created="2021-03-11 20:29:55+10:00">
     <body>You are truly a lost cause.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-03-11 17:24:40+10:00">
  <body>What made ADN go spastic? Was a nice lil surprise for me. Thinking of taking profits and piling it into LRS, which looks like it's at a great point to top up. 

Thank fuck CXO got it's shit together. Now for EMN and NVX to do the same. Peace</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-11 17:36:39+10:00">
   <body>My dad texted me to say go look into ADN could be a multi bagger after hearing a couple guys at work talk about it. The boomers have arrived</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-11 17:48:29+10:00">
    <body>ADN's officially at the top</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-11 17:50:11+10:00">
     <body>If my dad is talking about it who had no idea what a market cap was about an 1 hour ago a peak is near</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-11 17:53:08+10:00">
      <body>Bless their cotton socks - they just want to be included 🥰</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-11 18:28:33+10:00">
    <body>Someone I know bought it a year ago for 1.6 cents with 100k worth and is now sitting on over 1 million waiting for 12 months to expire</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-11 18:30:01+10:00">
     <body>What was the original options strike for ADN i thought it was a 100 bagger if you were in on the options</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-11 18:30:31+10:00">
      <body>No idea.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 18:03:29+10:00">
    <body>500m market cap for an explorer is quite high.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-11 18:08:43+10:00">
     <body>680 million is even higher.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 18:16:05+10:00">
      <body>oh shit lol. last time i checked it was 500m. I do like the company just seems heaps late to enter now.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:27:59+10:00">
    <body>Yikes, time to sell</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-11 18:26:39+10:00">
   <body>Rumours are an announcement soon about 5 year contracts for production in SA 

This is going to send it to the stratosphere.

rumours only not financial advice but if you don't get in you're not an autist.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="stillapunk" created="2021-03-11 17:36:56+10:00">
  <body>Wonder if it'll be a green Friday since nobody has any profits to sell?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 17:38:43+10:00">
  <body>Posted my writeup on the DLC piss-take today in a separate thread, be interested to hear everyone's thoughts.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-11 17:44:57+10:00">
   <body> I wonder if you'll cause anyone to buy in, but then again they'll assume we're just pumping and dumping it...</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 17:47:52+10:00">
    <body>I honestly don't think anyone could be that retarded, but I think we did make something buy today (sentiment algos). Then again, the depths of autism on this subreddit might surprise me.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:26:41+10:00">
     <body>I hope it was mostly sentiment algos and not individual autists getting screwed</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:54:00+10:00">
      <body>Would have been happy day trading it today</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-11 18:29:54+10:00">
   <body>Just read it, that’s hilarious</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-11 19:02:51+10:00">
   <body>Good write up mate. Today was fun too - I had some LOL moments. However, it is a reminder of the power of words and the damage they can do when people can't read tone or intent.

Having said that, you would have to be a special kind of special to think DLC a good get. 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="TesticularCamber" created="2021-03-11 18:12:13+10:00">
  <body>If VML drops under 6c I think I will top up 100k units. 

I just cancelled my sell order for PLS. I'm going to wait until the next lithium pump and sell out.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-03-11 18:38:58+10:00">
   <body>Rising lithium prices may see that be tomorrow</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-11 18:49:59+10:00">
    <body>VML is rare earths not lithium. Connected fortunes but not directly enough that the lithium spot price will do much I think.

Edit: I just re-read your comment and OP’s comment and I see that I’m an idiot. Carry on.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-11 19:04:05+10:00">
   <body>The clock is ticking..</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-11 18:47:11+10:00">
   <body>I have a buy order for 6.3. Hope it doesn’t go beyond that 😂</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-11 18:23:11+10:00">
   <body>K</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-03-11 19:11:23+10:00">
  <body>Day two of holding my $6million market cap mining speccie. ZERO shares traded today. Try again tomorrow I guess.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-03-11 19:27:09+10:00">
   <body>It has potential to get exciting quickly!</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="autodidact31" created="2021-03-11 19:34:03+10:00">
    <body>Ticker?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-03-11 19:55:46+10:00">
     <body>I think Mr Star is keeping to themself so that they don't inadvertently lose anyone a bunch of cash in the event it gets delisted. My comment was about how at a MC of 6 mil, any significant event has the ability to generate you a lot of bags very quickly</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ASXg0d" created="2021-03-11 19:49:28+10:00">
     <body>I bet DLP and he bought $70k</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-03-11 19:53:11+10:00">
      <body>Nope, when I said zero shares traded I don't mean me- nobody at all bought or sold shares in this stock today lol</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 19:57:54+10:00">
   <body>Sounds like VAL, though much less market cap</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-11 20:34:41+10:00">
   <body>Zero !
Thats brilliant !

That made me laugh</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-11 18:06:22+10:00">
  <body>I think tomorrow will be a good day.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-11 18:13:06+10:00">
  <body>Back to back meetings today and barely had time to check the market, looks like that didn’t matter. Holding on to EGR LKE LRS and maybe, just maybe that dog stock SOR will actually do something soon.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:22:39+10:00">
   <body>If only. Just need it to pump enough that I can get the fuck out and never look back.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-11 18:28:16+10:00">
    <body>I’m down about 20% on SOR but it’s not that much money and I did really well with VML so not too bad, but its pretty annoying.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:29:40+10:00">
     <body>I’m down over 40% on SOR and it’s actually a fuckload of money because I YOLOd in like a retard.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-11 18:33:11+10:00">
      <body>Shit. There should be a few more announcements soon, and I’m hoping that things will get better then but who knows. I got a little bit of cash that I’m considering putting into LRS, thought about SOR but it’s just too risky.</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:34:36+10:00">
       <body>After being in it for a little while now, I’m convinced SOR is poison. The no CGT thing makes it too vulnerable to PnD and market manipulation.</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Termsandconditionsch" created="2021-03-11 18:37:19+10:00">
        <body>Yep.. the PDFs are so tempting though. But I think you are right.</body>
        <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:43:35+10:00">
         <body>It also makes it harder to stomach the loss and sell out, because you can’t even use it to offset gains elsewhere</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="basraz" created="2021-03-11 18:45:51+10:00">
        <body>wait a min.. what's this no CGT and SOR story.. newb autist</body>
        <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:49:53+10:00">
         <body>SOR = Strategic Elements, a Pooled Development Fund (PDF) that invests in private ventures meeting certain criteria that means that there is no CGT payable on capital gains from investing in it. Google it. TBH I recommend staying away, especially if you are a newb.</body>
         <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="basraz" created="2021-03-11 18:59:02+10:00">
          <body>i missed a 10 baager opportunity on it..then unfortunately bought in one of the dips cz fomo..now -30%..but not a lot invested in it</body>
         </comment>
         <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:07:34+10:00">
          <body>By the end of March there should be a great ANN coming out, and there as per their timeline the next one should be 2-4 weeks after that. The technology is great and I think 40C's is a steal, however yes, no CGT does make it a pain, and for the future of the fund and serious investors I'd almost rather the CGT exemption not exist.   


With that said, IMO, it will pump again</body>
         </comment>
        </comment>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="toolman2019" created="2021-03-11 19:03:01+10:00">
         <body>See I like SOR double down Already. Just know what it is before you buy. Is it good or bad I don't know I just think it's cool what they are doing. I disagree that it was a P&amp;B. Was right after a big announcement. People didn't understand what proof of concept means.

Tip for a newbe don't buy after a announcement.</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-11 18:52:41+10:00">
  <body>I only have xst, I hope it comes out of trading halt tomorrow and really good news.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="madDcent" created="2021-03-11 19:12:06+10:00">
   <body>I reckon they would have hit the second pocket of gas. This will be good news but I don’t think it’s going to rocket the price tomorrow. It will keep climbing the further they drill and once they hit the mother load it will be happy days</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="fat-bIack-bitches" created="2021-03-11 19:43:08+10:00">
    <body>i recken 2c after ann if its gas. that 2c sell wall will be crazy tho</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="tbarbeast" created="2021-03-11 19:09:24+10:00">
  <body>DLC to 0.009 so I can get the fuck off this train</body>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 19:16:47+10:00">
   <body>They expect one of us in the wreckage brother</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-11 19:32:05+10:00">
   <body>Oh snap, i hope you didnt drop 77k in LOL😅</body>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="tbarbeast" created="2021-03-11 19:36:22+10:00">
    <body>Im at a certain level of downs but not that retarded</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-03-11 19:42:21+10:00">
  <body>Do you reckon I can ask Aussie Super to put it all on DW8?</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="theoriginaluser01" created="2021-03-11 20:02:44+10:00">
   <body>They won't. Fair chance you're limited to ASX300 companies, and if you wanted to do a self managed version they'd only allow something like a maximum of 20% on any individual stock.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-03-11 20:03:40+10:00">
    <body>That’s a lot more than I expected haha</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 20:06:09+10:00">
    <body>Boo! I wanna put everything in BPH, and sign up for all the bnpl services so I can live comfortably when I lose everything</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-03-11 17:38:57+10:00">
  <body>Not much on the radar. AVA still a good buy at the moment. Got into EGR earlier in the week which is looking promising so far. Halved my LRS holding. XST might open a little higher off good results, I suspect it will struggle to get past 2c anytime soon. Eyeing off JXT in vicinity of the 5cents mark over the coming months.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-03-11 19:15:42+10:00">
  <body>Bought more rnt because I enjoy it fucking me</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ChalkyAus" created="2021-03-11 19:26:49+10:00">
  <body>I've averaged down on either PEN, TLG and/or VUL the last 3 Fridays...please, no more, I'm not strong enough 😩</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-03-11 19:29:09+10:00">
   <body>Hahaha I need to be rich to be able to average down into all the bloody dips</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mothermarx" created="2021-03-11 19:44:03+10:00">
   <body>TLG has been a brutal tease. Surfing the 1.2-1.4 up and down the last few weeks.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Pricy2401" created="2021-03-11 17:49:32+10:00">
  <body>buying into FLT, hopefully it keeps going green. but other than that i think my portfolios stuffed. no tendies for me till IXR goes up.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 18:42:07+10:00">
   <body>Who uses flight centre to book domestic flights? Autists?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-11 18:03:07+10:00">
   <body>IXR will be going up at end of month. I’m enjoying all the paper hands selling to me at the moment unaware of what they are giving up 😂</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:31:31+10:00">
    <body>Topped up again today</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-11 18:34:13+10:00">
     <body>Yep I was trying to get some at 4.9. Didn’t quite hit it. Will be topping up some more tomorrow if it dips.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:42:42+10:00">
      <body>Yeah I was happy for 5.0 considering it’s just a top up</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Faulty_Vibrator" created="2021-03-11 18:27:20+10:00">
    <body>What is happening at the end of the month?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-11 18:33:29+10:00">
     <body>Scoping study for their major rare earths project will be released. MD has already hinted at the fact it will be a monster. And we know it’s complete because the consulting company that did it has posted that on linkedin. 

Backs up the resources estimate going up 3 fold 2 weeks ago. And they are still exploring. There is a view that the resource could be another 50% larger in the adjacent tenement.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-03-11 18:53:59+10:00">
   <body>I don't get why FLT over ALG. They already had massive dilution in mid-2020.

So much more value, but each their own.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-03-11 19:10:06+10:00">
  <body>a2m calls @ 8 buckerydoos. asx options seem pre shit but im bullish on milk and believe in boomers so here goes</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tbarbeast" created="2021-03-11 19:22:35+10:00">
   <body>When do they expire?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-03-11 19:34:24+10:00">
    <body>may 20</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="slipperygypsy92" created="2021-03-11 19:11:11+10:00">
  <body>Just heard us mentioned on equity mates, pretty funny conversation about iCandy and 🚀 rating system</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:00:58+10:00">
   <body>I really laughed at the REI = Rocket Emoji Indicator. Speccy McGee delivered the goods.

Honestly, a good podcast too, really enjoy those boys</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="slipperygypsy92" created="2021-03-11 20:04:08+10:00">
    <body>Same, Fucking hilarious. What about that one listener who dm’d them saying enough of this segment 🙄 boomers 🤦🏼‍♂️</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:08:03+10:00">
     <body>Haha 'you boys need to be more serious', fuck off with your Telstra and BHP shares</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:35:01+10:00">
  <body>So the ASX Sharemarket game is up, which is a thing my school is running where you can simulate investing with $50,000. The few winners take home a couple hundred bucks and it's statewide so some big competition.

[Here are the companies I can invest in.](https://www.reddit.com/user/Kriifrux/comments/lu20jm/list_of_all_asx_school_sharemarket_game_companies/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;context=3)

Let me know which ones are your top picks are what prices I should set my limit orders at.

So far I'm probably going to buy:

* A2M if it starts looking more promising
* AIA
* BRG
* CCP
* FLT as soon as it dips
* KGN
* LYC
* SFR if it dips
* SYD
* TCL
* WEB as soon as it dips
* WPL
* Z1P as soon as the dump is done

I'm likely to just split my money between all of them equally, or potentially more in one if yall are bullish on it. These are just based on suggestions of what people recommended when I asked around a week ago or so. Let me know if I should change or add some, or if I should even make a poll.

Side note: I have no idea what the fuck I'm doing. But since I won't be making any real losses, fire away with your suggestions.</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="jaamzzz" created="2021-03-11 19:46:11+10:00">
   <body>I find it hilarious how schools try to teach students about the sharemarket using that game. It teaches you the exact opposite lesson they'd want you to know. it goes for what? like 2 months? so how else are you gonna win without yeeting 10k+ into speccy penny stocks hoping it'll rocket.

When I did it at school, we were in the midst of the GFC, so everyone got fucked and all my mates are now scared of the stock market.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:48:36+10:00">
    <body>Hahaha yeah it is a bit silly especially with the fucking dividends. I think it runs for like maybe half a year? Maybe it was until May I think.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jaamzzz" created="2021-03-11 19:55:02+10:00">
     <body>I wish you all the best, and that your companies still exist 10 years later, unlike the ones my group chose.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-11 19:58:39+10:00">
   <body>Hey champ. [Here's](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/m090uk/best_yolo_for_asx_stock_market_game/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;utm_source=share) a link to the last person who asked, and there's a link in that to the one before 👍</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 20:12:31+10:00">
    <body>Thanks mate</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="UhOhNoOnion" created="2021-03-11 19:40:31+10:00">
   <body>Only buy the minimum number of shares if you want to win, I think I’ve heard people say it’s 4? Of those you’ve mentioned, LYC, KGN, FLT and Z1P would be my picks. You could either win convincingly or come dead last</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:41:16+10:00">
    <body>Yeah max is 25% portfolio diversification on 1 company.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 19:43:28+10:00">
    <body>Great picks though. What prices should I set my limit orders and should I just chuck them in now?
Your guess is as good as mine and since I won't lose anything, you don't have to worry about the financial advice crap.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="UhOhNoOnion" created="2021-03-11 20:17:38+10:00">
     <body>Market buy 3;45pm tomorrow 25% each</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 20:20:12+10:00">
      <body>Would it not be a good idea to consider some other companies like WEB, BHP or AIA for example? Maybe to allocate some percentage to them?

EDIT: What about Afterpay? They seem to be below their intrinsic value.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Nsj_1" created="2021-03-11 20:14:42+10:00">
   <body>Day trade APT and Z1P.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-11 20:30:37+10:00">
   <body>I would so love to help you buddy but damn....i have 20 stonks in my portfolio and the only one i matched with from your list is WEB - and youve missed the bottom for that and shouldn't go anywhere near it now.
Good luck !</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Kriifrux" created="2021-03-11 20:31:30+10:00">
    <body>Fair enough.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-11 19:54:11+10:00">
  <body>I'm seriously considering dumping my PEN @ -43% loss. I just don't see it getting any better in the next year. Thinking I'll dump it and some extra cash back into Z1P or RBL instead</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 20:02:46+10:00">
   <body>Fair enough.

My counter argument would be that PEN does not have any immediate obvious bad news, and that the market seems to have fully reacted to the last announcement now with us hovering around 0.1 

I think sentiment around Uranium is still shifting towards bullish, and the supply/demand thesis remains strong which will slowly rise the price of all Uranium miners, PEN included. I'm holding at ~30% loss on PEN right now but still remain hopeful, will probably downsize my overall position in PEN in favor of other miners if I get a good selling opportunity though.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Solid_Industry3484" created="2021-03-11 20:20:24+10:00">
    <body>doesnt Australia have 30% of the worlds uranium resources? Any companies taking advantage of this and exporting due to our dumb ass prime minister?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 20:28:22+10:00">
     <body>You're correct, Australia sits on the radioactive motherload of Uranium, but several states oppose the development of Uranium mines.

There's ~10 listed ASX Explorers/Miners of Uranium, I'll list a few players here with the mine location and stage

**DYL** - Developing mine in Namibia with other Namibian Explorations,

**PEN** - Developing mine in Wyoming USA, ASX_Bets favorite praying for Biden tendies but getting the CBT treatment lately

**LOT** - Own developed mine in Malawi

**BMN** - Developing a mine in Namibia

**VMY** - Explorer in NT and QLD, early stages

**PDN** - Own developed mine in Namibia, have two exploration sites in Australia and one in Canada

**BOE** - Own developed mine in SA, if you're looking for the Aus Uranium play, this could be the one</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-11 20:04:54+10:00">
   <body>How long were you expecting to hold PEN? If you did any DD you have seen they are still 6 months (at the time) away from production.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-11 20:09:14+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I did the DD and knew this, however I'm thinking I could put the money to better work elsewhere right now (bought 19/2 pre market correction)</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-11 20:19:36+10:00">
     <body>Yeah I know the feeling dude. Just that last time I tried chasing my losses it burnt me harder. Either way best of luck man 👍</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-11 20:10:51+10:00">
    <body>At the same time, I am reluctant to sell so soon after buying. feelsbadman.jpg</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="image_linker_bot" created="2021-03-11 20:11:05+10:00">
     <body>[feelsbadman.jpg](https://i.imgur.com/T0jNUbo.jpg)  


---
^(*Feedback welcome at /r/image_linker_bot* | )[^(Disable)](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose/?to=image_linker_bot&amp;subject=Ignore%20request&amp;message=ignore%20me)^( with "ignore me" via reply or PM)</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="theblueberryfarmer" created="2021-03-11 20:34:42+10:00">
    <body>I hold, but not as much as I did. I think the time frame is a lot longer than 6 months to be honest, they seem to have a pretty big hurdle to overcome.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 20:04:49+10:00">
   <body>I think we've reached a stable bottom.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="drat_the_luck" created="2021-03-11 20:24:46+10:00">
   <body>You wanted a PEN15 but you're getting a PEN05</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 20:02:29+10:00">
  <body>Swear to god I'm still getting market corrections on selfwealth.

Lost half my gains since 5pm</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whole_Use6763" created="2021-03-11 19:23:01+10:00">
  <body>NASDAQ UP 2%, hope it holds for tommorow</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="HeiPando" created="2021-03-11 19:24:20+10:00">
  <body>The plan is not to get salty over DW8 cause fuck me why couldn't it go over 10.5c yesterday. I was almost back in at 9.8c but pussied out cause to get that parcel it wiped 1.3m units at both 10c and 9.9c.  


Congrats to the actually holders of the share and not the trades cause fuck welcome to the 5% pip club!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-11 20:13:48+10:00">
  <body>Excited for tomorrow - should be a green Friday (for once...!!)

Oil booming, rare earths booming, iron ore booming, tin booming. Happy days at the start of this commodity super-cycle !!

SHE / SRK / IXR / TMZ 

🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 20:16:16+10:00">
  <body>Murdoch media, despite being a bunch of soul destroying boomer brain washing cunts, have started "programming" the idea of [Nuclear in Australia](https://www.skynews.com.au/details/_6238740620001)

This is good for the local projects like BOE</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="woodenlife" created="2021-03-11 20:21:07+10:00">
   <body>I love how he says Gas is there but we don’t have a lot of it 😂 you can’t make this shit up.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:32:11+10:00">
  <body>A small pump for BRN. Recent weeks have seen the SP drop (below what I've paid mind you), I do honestly feel it's a good purchasing opportunity as selection for phase 2 or their SBIR program takes place on the 18th of March, NASA have had access to Brainchip's Akida chip and I feel pretty comfortable that it'll make selection for phase 2. As far an on the Edge AI goes Brainchip is currently in a league of it's own, but because we all have too much time on our hands, feel free to look into it for yourself. Also with tech stocks making a slight comeback that'll also work in BRN's favour.

BUT what would I know I'm just a random reddit guy.

Oh wait I forgot  🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-11 17:10:15+10:00">
  <body>Back up to 6% + on my portfolio, ready for it to get back to 0% for red Friday woot</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="tomatowire" created="2021-03-11 17:13:50+10:00">
  <body>Might get rid of my IXR holdings and top up on DW8... IXR hasn't done much for me (buy in @ 0.052) but is it worth the longish hold?</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-11 17:25:36+10:00">
   <body>So u seen IXR go up so u bought into it.. now you see DW8 go up now u want in on that... this is why they say the majority of retail loose money.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:38:44+10:00">
    <body>Yeah this drives me crazy on this sub. People see a stock pump for a couple of days, THEN they decide to buy in, doesn’t make them instant tendies so they look elsewhere within a week, find another stock that’s pumping, sell their original stock at a loss to get in on that and the cycle repeats.</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-11 18:52:32+10:00">
     <body>Eventually..hopefully people learn that it's not a race.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-11 17:16:00+10:00">
   <body>Sure, just make sure you’re not FOMOing into it. DW8 is very hyped right now and as with all heavily hyped stock, there will be a pullback.

I’m gonna throw some money into DW8 but waiting for it to recede from its ATH, possibly after the next announcement.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="tomatowire" created="2021-03-11 17:22:05+10:00">
    <body>Yep definitely a good point, will be interesting to see what it does tomorrow (have a feeling it will pull back again as it did yesterday).</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Murakamo" created="2021-03-11 17:18:23+10:00">
    <body>Think it might dump after today's pump? Need another entry point to top up.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-11 17:28:37+10:00">
     <body>It could go up until the next announcement.

But the likely hood that when the positive announcement comes, it will already be priced in since we kind of know what it’s going to be about.

The hype of that next announcement is contributing to what we see now in the SP increase. People will sell on the announcement, take profit and we will see a decent pull back. Hence the saying that gets thrown around a lot “Buy the hype, sell the news”.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="pauliie123" created="2021-03-11 17:22:03+10:00">
     <body>Only up from here :)</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-03-11 17:22:02+10:00">
   <body>imagine selling IXR now considering the report is due at the end of the month? HODL phaggot and sell next month!</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-11 17:34:28+10:00">
    <body>Wine or Rare earths.... Which has a bigger boom coming i wonder....</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="unbent" created="2021-03-11 18:30:59+10:00">
     <body>But wine tastes better and you get tipsy</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-03-11 19:35:05+10:00">
      <body>Speak for yourself.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="GrAv1TyCaT" created="2021-03-11 17:16:49+10:00">
   <body>Dw8 is a coiled spring at the mo.... Im trying to trade the swings and build my holding, missed out on the P&amp;D today.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="upthebaggers" created="2021-03-11 18:25:10+10:00">
   <body>I'll buy your IXR bro</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:36:22+10:00">
    <body>Same</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-03-11 17:37:45+10:00">
  <body>Iron ore keeps taking a beating

Glad i got onto the gold train</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 17:56:26+10:00">
   <body>No. Iron ore is up today. It was down yesterday.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-03-11 18:35:26+10:00">
    <body>Yeah but I bought in 10 days ago so yeah...

I am not a smart man</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 19:03:23+10:00">
     <body>Fair enough man. What did you buy CIA or GRR or FMG?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-03-11 19:29:19+10:00">
      <body>Worse, boomer stocks  BHP and S32

They'll come good sooner or later and I can cover margin</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hanstarinoz" created="2021-03-11 17:50:51+10:00">
   <body>RMS</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-03-11 17:55:51+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I was in and out at 1.33 and 1.56

Might get back in if it drops</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-11 19:07:15+10:00">
     <body>Ahh RMS. Not sure why that went down today. FMG had a small pullback possibly oversold yesterday. Thats when I bought.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="shutterbug87" created="2021-03-11 18:01:57+10:00">
  <body>RNU had a good day, smashed a few sell walls. I wonder if it is getting close to another run??</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 18:40:42+10:00">
  <body>Any updates from a homegrown ASX bot yet? I wanna see how high DLC got today</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tbarbeast" created="2021-03-11 19:10:06+10:00">
   <body>Not high enough</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Yaals" created="2021-03-11 18:42:30+10:00">
  <body>IVZ did me a solid today</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BK1RW4N" created="2021-03-11 19:15:03+10:00">
   <body>Me too, I’m in at 155K shares @ 0.06: 75 % total profit so far even before any real action starts. Will keep it at that for now, you topping up all the time?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="zemadfrenchman" created="2021-03-11 19:33:14+10:00">
   <body>It's beginning.. either people wanting in before next news or.. 

Zimbabwe government could be a leaky ship and it's already decided??

Big volume today it looks good to me. IVZ looking solid AF</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="OggygonChill" created="2021-03-11 19:39:22+10:00">
    <body>Or next investors email went out</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-11 19:41:34+10:00">
     <body>Yeah it was a next investors email and maybe also a MF article. Not organic growth sadly, but I’ll take it.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="zemadfrenchman" created="2021-03-11 20:15:24+10:00">
      <body>Fair enough. Attention is good it will help the news when it arrives</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-03-11 20:36:39+10:00">
   <body>I sold my holding from 0.6 at profit but well below where it be now. 

Doh</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="PopGotcha44" created="2021-03-11 19:19:50+10:00">
  <body>Hope my horse cum order (MEM) fills and Dw8 keeps stable above 10c</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="dog_hole21" created="2021-03-11 20:24:43+10:00">
   <body>Bought MEM at 6c in late 2019 too stubborn to realise the peak and back to square 1 again, last ann killed it though.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 19:57:00+10:00">
  <body>Summoning /u/asxbot to see how far DLC managed to climb today in our rankings.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Wookiee81" created="2021-03-11 20:02:53+10:00">
   <body>Apparently you can check it at asxbot.io</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 20:04:04+10:00">
    <body>It doesn't update in live time, been refreshing as much as my portfolio today lmao</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Wookiee81" created="2021-03-11 20:06:49+10:00">
     <body>Going to laugh my ass off if this plan comes off.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-03-11 17:51:24+10:00">
  <body>Looking to get a bit more M7T if it dips down much more, thinking it’ll be close to having blown off its steam after the run up over $1.50.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 17:57:59+10:00">
   <body>Im in m7t and i think it's oversold</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-03-11 18:05:08+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I think the fundamentals are tight and it just got caught up in the small cap/tech/healthcare mess of the last few weeks. Annoying for sure but happy to accumulate more with the longer outlook</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 18:14:50+10:00">
     <body>AV1 ANP M7T are all overlooked in my opinion</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-03-11 18:23:04+10:00">
      <body>With you on AV1 too, ouch mate. Wanting an announcement for this one soon!</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-11 18:30:13+10:00">
       <body>Yeah i can see it rerating hard on a good announcement</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="LYC_97" created="2021-03-11 17:58:04+10:00">
  <body>Got 5k to drop what do i buy</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="throwaway8726529" created="2021-03-11 18:04:51+10:00">
   <body>LRS or RAC. Depends how big a gamble you wanna do.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Adrenaline06" created="2021-03-11 18:35:33+10:00">
   <body>LRS or PUR or EXR for some tendies (hopefully).

APX for a long term value hold.

ZIP if you want to age 20 years in 20 days</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:24:56+10:00">
   <body>DLC, closed 16% up on huge... volume.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-11 18:41:13+10:00">
    <body>😢</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-11 18:41:53+10:00">
     <body>You know I’m playing</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 18:41:31+10:00">
   <body>Rabbitohs to beat storm tonight 1.90</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="bnplstrategist" created="2021-03-11 18:46:50+10:00">
    <body>Alex Johnson first try scorer</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-03-11 19:10:51+10:00">
     <body>give me my money back</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-11 19:46:40+10:00">
    <body>I dare you to throw that down on the current odds</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Christiee28" created="2021-03-11 19:54:41+10:00">
    <body>Look for something with a money back special, not even the ASX can offer you that</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-11 17:59:15+10:00">
   <body>LRS</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SupLord" created="2021-03-11 18:11:10+10:00">
   <body>DW8</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Lkorjo" created="2021-03-11 18:40:52+10:00">
   <body>PUR VML or even NVA for a long term punt</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:49:46+10:00">
   <body>PUR, LRS, or LPD

Or DLC</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-11 18:48:55+10:00">
   <body>Ixr</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-11 18:13:32+10:00">
   <body>SRN</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="dahmachino" created="2021-03-11 19:06:38+10:00">
   <body>PRL</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-11 18:02:24+10:00">
   <body>CYM or MLX. They both going up till their joint announcement.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="willkds" created="2021-03-11 18:35:00+10:00">
   <body>ADN</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-11 19:12:02+10:00">
   <body>PUR / NVA / WWI [if it dips, near term most rewarding potentially]</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Ratsbox" created="2021-03-11 20:01:41+10:00">
   <body>PUR / LRS / PRL</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-11 20:11:58+10:00">
  <body>How do you track your portfolio compared to the ASX?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-03-11 20:19:30+10:00">
   <body>Sharesight</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-11 20:21:47+10:00">
    <body>Thanks dude</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Moxanz2" created="2021-03-11 20:15:37+10:00">
  <body>Looks like CI1 failed to raise funds from their capital raise. $4k I’m never gonna see again.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:33:38+10:00">
   <body>Can I ask what you bought in at? I was watching for months and months when they were at 3c, kicking myself for not buying in even though there were so many signals to buy. I wonder if it'll go back below 3c?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Moxanz2" created="2021-03-11 20:35:35+10:00">
    <body>This was my worst trade by far and I’m very embarrassed to say that I bought at bear ATH. 9.6c. I mean the company seemed good to me was reading up on it for about a week. Was having a shit day at work. FOMO kicked in and now here we are. 
So I get that they’re trying to expand but why not stop the dividend use those funds for expanding rather than diluting the hell out each time.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Sindragosaaa" created="2021-03-11 17:15:52+10:00">
  <body>Up 4.66% only 0.03% more to go.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ilestMYRON" created="2021-03-11 17:39:45+10:00">
   <body>Up 2.3% today, 19% more to go.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 17:59:27+10:00">
  <body>Gonna try and decide tonight between QPM, ROO or NC6 to dip toes in tomorrow while they’re cheap..</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-11 18:42:28+10:00">
   <body>Never heard of them. Must be good ones</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 20:25:39+10:00">
    <body>Feeling keen on sustainable stonks as I can understand their fundamentals. QPM is aiming to be a zero waste battery metals producer. NC6 is producing plant cellulose replacement for textile industries (including face masks) made use food waste. ROO is working on technology to improve water uptake efficiency in crops based on root temperature.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FebWolf" created="2021-03-11 18:47:52+10:00">
   <body>QPM would be my humble opinion. I'm not holding them either. Had a good look at them about a week ago but no free cash atm.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 20:19:31+10:00">
    <body>I’m torn. I love both NC6 and QPM boards and products. QPM has nearly 5 million more on the sell side than the buy, so I might wait and see if the price pushes down a bit more.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhee1980" created="2021-03-11 20:27:51+10:00">
    <body>Think I’m gonna go for NC6 this week. Love NC6 and QPM boards and products but NC6 is in a bigger dip and has higher insider ownership. QPM has 5mil more on the sell side than the buy so potential to dip further, will wait and see if I can get in lower next week.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PM_me_ur_bingo_nos" created="2021-03-11 17:59:37+10:00">
  <body>Fuck I wish I'd bought AVR when I spotted it at $4.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="diesal11" created="2021-03-11 18:25:15+10:00">
  <body>Fingers crossed for LGP shares tomorrow. A bit strange there's 0 correspondence with successful investors before shares appear in account and go live for trading, there's probably some letter in the mail i'll get late next week.

Or perhaps i just missed out entirely lololol.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="buffalo_bill27" created="2021-03-11 18:30:39+10:00">
   <body>Ahh yes the "special" deal of 65c shares</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nobolt2" created="2021-03-11 18:56:28+10:00">
    <body>Is it common when stockd do this for the share price to drop to the purchase offer amount ?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="madDcent" created="2021-03-11 19:01:26+10:00">
  <body>Not sure if I’ve seen this stock mentioned here lately but I’m looking at ASM.
They have signed a memorandum of understanding in Korea and are proposing a metal plant in the foreign investment zone. 
They plan to produce high purity neodymium iron boron powder and titanium powder. Manufacturing companies like LG chemical, Samsung SDI, SK Hynix and Hyundai are within close proximity of the proposed metal plant industrial area. 
The SP is $5.32 as of tonight so I’m wondering if I’ve missed the boat and should have bought when it was a lot lower.
Anyone invested in this company?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="peaandham610" created="2021-03-11 20:03:35+10:00">
   <body>That was my first share I invested in. In at 90c's, out at around $2.50. They just keep delivering the goods, I wouldn't put anything past them. They sort of sat under the radar so over on Hot Copper you didn't get much up or downrampers, just true investors, it was a relief to see.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="dahmachino" created="2021-03-11 19:05:17+10:00">
  <body>Anyone gonna mention the big arse elephant in the corner PRL?</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="OggygonChill" created="2021-03-11 19:38:38+10:00">
   <body>Curious how this goes for FMG? Surely positive?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-03-11 20:13:45+10:00">
   <body>Looked like FOMO buying into the end of the day. But there was also FOMO buying a few weeks back and it didn’t go so well for those who bought the FOMO.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Zealousideal_Oven_43" created="2021-03-11 19:42:21+10:00">
  <body>Anybody on ARE?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="LifeIsAStateOfFlux" created="2021-03-11 17:05:16+10:00">
  <body>FMG bounced back slightly today. So did RIO - Wonder if Red Friday will reign them back?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="toolman2019" created="2021-03-11 17:31:37+10:00">
  <body>BID. What the fuck your my only red today.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-11 20:08:06+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-11 20:08:07+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Murranji" created="2021-03-11 20:14:43+10:00">
  <body>Buy the next dip in AT1 hopefully, it might be setting up for a reversal.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Noideasx" created="2021-03-11 20:35:09+10:00">
  <body>CPH LGP</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-11 17:36:33+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="throwaway8726529" created="2021-03-11 17:37:11+10:00">
   <body>No crypto stuff here, sorry. Try the crypto subs.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mcfucking" created="2021-03-11 18:12:32+10:00">
    <body>👍</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-11 17:39:49+10:00">
    <body>Ok cheers</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="DabestInvests" created="2021-03-11 17:09:57+10:00">
  <body>BPH could explode tomorrow</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="sensitivetoredlogs" created="2021-03-11 17:34:48+10:00">
   <body>Will it be white fluid or red fluid?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snappo_B" created="2021-03-11 17:16:08+10:00">
   <body>What makes you think this?</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="nobolt2" created="2021-03-11 17:31:14+10:00">
    <body>Wanting to get his 20% back by pumping it to you</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="twoweekoldbread" created="2021-03-11 17:17:31+10:00">
    <body>Tea leaves</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-6" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-11 17:10:30+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-11 17:13:34+10:00">
   <body>Lol imagine trying to predict the ASX based on futures.

ASX doesn’t care, it does what it wants, whenever it wants.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-11 17:51:39+10:00">
    <body>Like a screaming monkey eating a banana with one hand and throwing it's shit all over the place with the other. That's the ASX on Fridays</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="simcityrefund1" created="2021-03-11 17:12:55+10:00">
   <body>It always like this green overnight then ASX fucks it up</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="GrAv1TyCaT" created="2021-03-11 17:17:27+10:00">
   <body>Friday is Cryday. Solid trend</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-50" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-03-11 17:02:47+10:00">
  <body>first reeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee</body>
  <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="ppleatingppl" created="2021-03-11 17:10:15+10:00">
   <body>There's always one retard.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-11 17:21:26+10:00">
    <body>These cunts should get banned</body>
    <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Qambi1" created="2021-03-11 17:23:41+10:00">
     <body>Ban for 765428976531 days</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
