<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-03-01 Monday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>LKE (7) HYPE=26</mention>
  <mention>PEN (7) HYPE=16</mention>
  <mention>RAC (6) HYPE=8</mention>
  <mention>LOT (6) HYPE=8</mention>
  <mention>VML (4) HYPE=10</mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="mo2704" created="2021-02-28 18:39:31+10:00">
   <body>Article in the AFR tonight about Mesoblast. Scary. 

Cash-strapped biotech Mesoblast is keeping brokers close for its last ditch capital raising.

Mesoblast shares went on a tear last year but have since come off, trading down 53 per cent to $2.46 over the past six months. 
Fund manager sources told Street Talk they expected brokers Bell Potter and Aitken Murray Capital Partners – which have worked for the company in the past – would be in Mesoblast’s corner for its private funding round.
The company has been working over the weekend to stitch together a private placement to a “targeted industry investor”, which is expected to come in around the $100 million mark. And it sounds like an all-or-nothing type deal.
Mesoblast went into a trading halt for the raising on Friday morning, and subsequently released its half year accounts to the market that evening.
In those accounts, the company’s auditor PwC said “the ability of the Group to continue as a going concern and realise its assets and discharge its liabilities in the normal course of business are dependent on cash inflows from successfully completing the private placement, as well as from existing strategic and financing partnerships which are subject to the Group meeting future milestones and other performance conditions”.

In other words, if this placement doesn’t get stitched up, Mesoblast is at risk of no longer being a going concern.
Cash-hungry
While it was unclear who the mystery investor would be, fund managers reckoned the money would be coming from offshore. If that was the case, it would signal the first time a major strategic backer had put money into the company since Israeli drug giant Teva sold out in 2017.
Funds also said it wasn’t clear if the entire placement would be going to the strategic, or if there’d be a chance institutions could get in on the action.
The cash-hungry regenerative medicine company has incurred losses from its operations since it started business in 2004, according to its half year accounts.
The company had accumulated a $US599 million deficit since inception as of December 31, 2020, and posted $US60.1 million net cash outflows for the first half of fiscal 2021.
Mesoblast shares went on a tear last year but have since come off, trading down 53 per cent to $2.46 over the past six months.
Jefferies Australia is in Mesoblast’s corner as defence adviser.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-28 18:51:58+10:00">
    <body>Destination fucked</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:44:24+10:00">
    <body>Still holding this in my Super at a decent loss but I'll be dammed if I will sell it as a loss was my first true FOMO and its there as a lesson... I'll go down with this ship if I gotta.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Arandomfitguy" created="2021-02-28 19:44:00+10:00">
     <body>Right there with you brother. Holding in super till they internally combust or actually do something. Last year was the turning point, they just turned the wrong way</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 19:45:28+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
      <body>Haha yes I hear you. I had two opportunities to sell even and in profit which I didn't so it's all on Me.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mo2704" created="2021-02-28 18:47:35+10:00">
     <body>As someone who lost money with VAH this rings alarm bells. I’d expect a sell off tomorrow and if and when the capital raising goes ahead the price may recover.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:49:21+10:00">
      <body>Yep it was my first big bad mistake, luckily I have other which cancel it out but it's a great 1st lesson.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Rob2moon" created="2021-02-28 18:45:56+10:00">
    <body>That’s a huge cash burn.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-02-28 19:36:00+10:00" sentiment="TIP 15">
    <body>So, are you saying we should buy the dip...</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-28 17:47:38+10:00" sentiment="TIP 8">
   <body>CHK - results any minute now. 

DSK - think people have been sleeping on this a bit. Though aint rocket type of stonk but just do a quick comparison of H1 results between DSK and LOV to see the value.

Other than that, Looking at GAL and IXR play this week.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MacchuWA" created="2021-02-28 19:20:59+10:00">
    <body>I've been telling anyone who'll listen, CHK have got nothing but the veins and halo coming off Oak Dam West. Clear from the geophysics, clear from the language they use in the announcements, clearer still from leaks from people in the know.

Hotcopper for CHK is a joke, everyone convincing themselves and each other that they're sitting on the next Carrapateena, going to be a cold hard reality check when those assays come in.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Elegantmango77" created="2021-02-28 18:24:19+10:00">
    <body>I got more GAL last week so glad too</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="WhiteChocoo" created="2021-02-28 17:13:36+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>What’s peoples thoughts on AUZ seems like it’s got massive potential from what I’ve seen, anyone read into it more?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 18:07:34+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Hoping for everyone’s sake tomorrow is green 🚀🚀🚀

My plan for this week is to follow VML very fucking closely and bring up my holding to 500,000 shares before production commences</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="velvet-skies" created="2021-02-28 19:27:55+10:00">
    <body>Aiming for that figure as well. Very bullish on 10c by the end of their summer. What price are you hoping to get them in at?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 19:36:59+10:00">
     <body>To be honest, I’d be prepared to pay 0.050 as I too am very bullish on 0.010 but if I can get a small discount I’ll take it!

The politics in the USA and EU are heating up fast in regards to REEs, with VML soon to be the only 2nd producer in North America things are looking up</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ziggyknars" created="2021-02-28 18:10:29+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>It's not about everyday being green, we cant have perpetual gains. It's about doing the research and investing in the company's long term potential or short term growth.</body>
    <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 18:15:18+10:00">
     <body>Sir this is a casino</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:22:14+10:00">
      <body>Dam straight give us our Greens... primarily for VML of course.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:55:29+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
     <body>Sir we are on asx bets. Our pennies can 🚀🚀🚀 regardless</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ausdeza" created="2021-02-28 19:22:13+10:00">
   <body>Anyone sitting on some PRL ? would be great if she stopped plummeting after the Credit Suisse pump and dump.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="methyl_violet" created="2021-02-28 19:31:44+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>Yeah, holding.  Still ahead on entry price.  Only saw one big plummet 10 days ago, been reasonably stable since.  Pretty speculative but I think there's big potential in a green hydrogen project so gonna hold</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ausdeza" created="2021-02-28 20:03:10+10:00">
     <body>Yea I didn't put much on, so not sweating but I did have my first bout of fomo and bought at 0.112 so don't have a choice but to hold hah.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="methyl_violet" created="2021-02-28 20:27:55+10:00">
      <body>.05 or .112,  It's either going nowhere,  or gonna rocket very high.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="-7" downs="0" author="falzenk" created="2021-02-28 19:56:42+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 20">
   <body>Anyone hold SHN? They reported great drilling finding last friday but only 3% up. I believe it will 🚀🚀🚀🌕🌕🌕 tomorrow.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-28 20:27:02+10:00">
    <body>SHN is more a of smart money gold play. Not a bad one either with Paul Chapman on the board. But there is a fuck ton of unlisted shares to come yet. 

Haven't checked yet but guessing your getting down voted because your new. But this is a stock I want cheaper</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-28 18:25:11+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 18">
   <body>Watch NZS and TNT and hope for them tendies, WEEK OF GREEN LETS GO!</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-02-28 18:36:51+10:00">
    <body>nzs, havent heard that name is a while!!</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-28 18:45:40+10:00">
     <body>There be many a bag holders hiding here I am sure, me I got back in a 2c, its been a ride thats for sure</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="CH3CKMT3" created="2021-02-28 17:33:27+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Green 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-28 17:33:27+10:00">
    <body>This isn't being deleted(yet), but we suggest trying harder next time.

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Gr8SevenLive" created="2021-02-28 18:51:31+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠

BRRRRRRAAAAAAAAIIIIIIIIINNNNNNNN

BRN 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-02-28 19:25:23+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>Lol, after their annual report saying there's a massive increase in operating costs, only a huge announcement will give us 🚀🚀🚀...

Until then we'll keep testing the 0.5 barrier</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="burnnttoast" created="2021-02-28 18:43:28+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Sold my Z1P last week but might buy back at current price! 
Also looking at LGP- unsure about buying yet 
Hoping a good Monday for all 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-28 18:50:35+10:00">
    <body>Buy the Z1p dip</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="slutinabutt" created="2021-02-28 19:15:09+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>Steer clear of LGP for now (my opinion). Why? There is a spp on at the moment for 65c a share. Basically 30m worth of shares at 65c a piece is going to hit the market, and that is why the price keeps going down. Not to mention all the other shares sold to the "profesionals" for the same price. Basically if you can get them cheaper than 65c go ahead, otherwise people will be holding it down for some time locking in profits from the SPP.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="35" downs="0" author="trashbets" created="2021-02-28 17:28:54+10:00">
  <body>I've decided I'm having a green day</body>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 17:30:10+10:00">
   <body>You have chosen... wisely</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:56:13+10:00">
   <body>Ez game</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="Snck_Pck" created="2021-02-28 19:21:12+10:00">
  <body>Fuck lads, a change is coming. People can mention ETFs here and no longer get downvoted. People are talking about long term holds regularly. People are being smart.

A change is coming.

And I dont like it.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:24:07+10:00">
   <body>This sub shouldn't be about dumb smart money, it should be about smart dumb money, think about it.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 19:32:53+10:00">
    <body>I think I know what you mean, but I'm still going to say please explain

Edit: Edited</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:42:16+10:00">
     <body>Any idiot can put money into an index fund and on average, over an extended period of time they will beat the average speculator. That's dumb smart money.


Smart dumb money is accepting that we're a bunch of idiots playing a game we'll most likely lose, but we can at least pool our resources together and be selective about where we place that dumb money. Even better, when these rockets implode crash we can shitpost on the way down.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="yonkapin" created="2021-02-28 19:44:33+10:00">
   <body>what the fuck is an etf?</body>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="unclepadrigo" created="2021-02-28 19:48:03+10:00">
    <body>Eternal tendies forever</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="MrMadamHoussain" created="2021-02-28 17:37:40+10:00">
  <body>BIG GREEN BEAN TOMORROW</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ohgoodonya" created="2021-02-28 18:47:50+10:00">
   <body>Lemme flick that all green bean</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="helmet_required" created="2021-02-28 19:33:59+10:00">
  <body>LKE Lithium purity results from NVX tomorrow cmon baby</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="d2blues" created="2021-02-28 19:54:54+10:00">
   <body>Lithium purity 420.69%</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="milovesit" created="2021-02-28 19:42:14+10:00">
   <body>You naughty Naughty ....you teasing me</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Fitzee92" created="2021-02-28 19:35:15+10:00">
   <body>Is it actually though?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-02-28 19:36:14+10:00">
   <body>Don't TEASE ME like that</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 18:07:34+10:00">
  <body>Hoping for everyone’s sake tomorrow is green 🚀🚀🚀

My plan for this week is to follow VML very fucking closely and bring up my holding to 500,000 shares before production commences</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="velvet-skies" created="2021-02-28 19:27:55+10:00">
   <body>Aiming for that figure as well. Very bullish on 10c by the end of their summer. What price are you hoping to get them in at?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 19:36:59+10:00">
    <body>To be honest, I’d be prepared to pay 0.050 as I too am very bullish on 0.010 but if I can get a small discount I’ll take it!

The politics in the USA and EU are heating up fast in regards to REEs, with VML soon to be the only 2nd producer in North America things are looking up</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ziggyknars" created="2021-02-28 18:10:29+10:00">
   <body>It's not about everyday being green, we cant have perpetual gains. It's about doing the research and investing in the company's long term potential or short term growth.</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 18:15:18+10:00">
    <body>Sir this is a casino</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:22:14+10:00">
     <body>Dam straight give us our Greens... primarily for VML of course.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:55:29+10:00">
    <body>Sir we are on asx bets. Our pennies can 🚀🚀🚀 regardless</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-02-28 17:07:18+10:00">
  <body>Will Biden's stimulus package have a positive impact on the ASX tomorrow? Will the US market finally stop repeatedly smashing its head against a wall for 5mins?</body>
  <comment ups="59" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-28 17:21:15+10:00">
   <body>Find out next time on dragon ball z</body>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Benny-Kenobii" created="2021-02-28 17:33:13+10:00">
    <body>So the last ten trading days have just been the ASX powering up the unleash a massive Kamehameha and shoot us all to the moon?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-02-28 18:03:41+10:00">
     <body>All leading up to a three month long Spirit Bomb where nothing happens but we watch anyway just in case something actually does.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="brayboy200" created="2021-02-28 17:18:13+10:00">
  <body>Hoping for some more positive LRS assay results and a positive movement in the SP

Also have a public holiday here in WA, so probs refresh every 5 seconds for 6 hours straight.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-28 17:24:58+10:00">
   <body>Positive news hasn't worked in our favour yet</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="brayboy200" created="2021-02-28 17:27:43+10:00">
    <body>Yeah tbf most of it was priced in. Still yet to have our thickest drill results come in. Also the JORC hopefully in March should reload the rocket</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Imthewifesboyfriend" created="2021-02-28 18:03:04+10:00">
   <body>I feel the PFS (pre-feasability study) is going to be the next big leg up. A lot of the positive results will have been priced in. Talk will shift to costs of getting the resource to market, which sounds like they are in a good spot to do with ease.
Can see this hovering around 10c prior to the PFS.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="brayboy200" created="2021-02-28 18:35:54+10:00">
    <body>Yeah i feel the same. Seems like it should simple enough to mine and get to the Port in Freo, and we can follow ADNs path

Should be a good long term hold atm especially with the potential in Argentina and with the gold projects too</body>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Arandomfitguy" created="2021-02-28 19:41:06+10:00">
     <body>ADNs path was to Rocket for a week before PfS then tank (sell the news) then hover at 5c for quite a few months before the intergalactic rocket teleporter really began.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="toolman2019" created="2021-02-28 17:11:55+10:00">
  <body>Fuck all west Aussie public holiday🖕🖕🖕</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="mo2704" created="2021-02-28 18:39:31+10:00">
  <body>Article in the AFR tonight about Mesoblast. Scary. 

Cash-strapped biotech Mesoblast is keeping brokers close for its last ditch capital raising.

Mesoblast shares went on a tear last year but have since come off, trading down 53 per cent to $2.46 over the past six months. 
Fund manager sources told Street Talk they expected brokers Bell Potter and Aitken Murray Capital Partners – which have worked for the company in the past – would be in Mesoblast’s corner for its private funding round.
The company has been working over the weekend to stitch together a private placement to a “targeted industry investor”, which is expected to come in around the $100 million mark. And it sounds like an all-or-nothing type deal.
Mesoblast went into a trading halt for the raising on Friday morning, and subsequently released its half year accounts to the market that evening.
In those accounts, the company’s auditor PwC said “the ability of the Group to continue as a going concern and realise its assets and discharge its liabilities in the normal course of business are dependent on cash inflows from successfully completing the private placement, as well as from existing strategic and financing partnerships which are subject to the Group meeting future milestones and other performance conditions”.

In other words, if this placement doesn’t get stitched up, Mesoblast is at risk of no longer being a going concern.
Cash-hungry
While it was unclear who the mystery investor would be, fund managers reckoned the money would be coming from offshore. If that was the case, it would signal the first time a major strategic backer had put money into the company since Israeli drug giant Teva sold out in 2017.
Funds also said it wasn’t clear if the entire placement would be going to the strategic, or if there’d be a chance institutions could get in on the action.
The cash-hungry regenerative medicine company has incurred losses from its operations since it started business in 2004, according to its half year accounts.
The company had accumulated a $US599 million deficit since inception as of December 31, 2020, and posted $US60.1 million net cash outflows for the first half of fiscal 2021.
Mesoblast shares went on a tear last year but have since come off, trading down 53 per cent to $2.46 over the past six months.
Jefferies Australia is in Mesoblast’s corner as defence adviser.</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-28 18:51:58+10:00">
   <body>Destination fucked</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:44:24+10:00">
   <body>Still holding this in my Super at a decent loss but I'll be dammed if I will sell it as a loss was my first true FOMO and its there as a lesson... I'll go down with this ship if I gotta.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Arandomfitguy" created="2021-02-28 19:44:00+10:00">
    <body>Right there with you brother. Holding in super till they internally combust or actually do something. Last year was the turning point, they just turned the wrong way</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 19:45:28+10:00">
     <body>Haha yes I hear you. I had two opportunities to sell even and in profit which I didn't so it's all on Me.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mo2704" created="2021-02-28 18:47:35+10:00">
    <body>As someone who lost money with VAH this rings alarm bells. I’d expect a sell off tomorrow and if and when the capital raising goes ahead the price may recover.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:49:21+10:00">
     <body>Yep it was my first big bad mistake, luckily I have other which cancel it out but it's a great 1st lesson.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Rob2moon" created="2021-02-28 18:45:56+10:00">
   <body>That’s a huge cash burn.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-02-28 19:36:00+10:00">
   <body>So, are you saying we should buy the dip...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-28 18:08:05+10:00">
  <body>Topping up the RAC baby!!</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="KIDNEYTHEIVES" created="2021-02-28 19:36:06+10:00">
   <body>RAC still shows no signs of stopping !</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 17:25:45+10:00">
  <body>Its the beginning of March, Winter has ended... just about time to enjoy more VML Ann's and movement.</body>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 18:05:23+10:00">
   <body>Coming from the UK most AU summers fuck me up, but this one's been surprisingly mild as it's a La-Nina year (http://www.bom.gov.au/climate/updates/articles/a020.shtml).

Interesting as a crop thing, because the next 3 years are likely to be slightly hotter and drier than this year. So what does that mean for various crops? SHV (almonds) for example, require a lot of water - and there's going to be less...  but what plants needs a lot of sun and not a lot of water? Cactii?! Long tequilla plantations? =P

Food for thought.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BTthePrettyGood" created="2021-02-28 18:44:52+10:00">
    <body>Water and farming will be a major issue for Australia going forward. I believe the only way we’ll be able to adapt will be to adopt more greenhouse\glasshouse farming on mass scales. Companies like Costa (CGC) will increase their glasshouse production and diversify into other crops (they’re already doing so - had a bumper few years with berries and this year with mushrooms while still pumping out tomatoes). But to do so will need governments to subsidise the outlay because it’s very expensive to set up but the yield is greater, uses far less water and far fewer chemicals. Don’t quote me but I think field tomatoes no longer exist in Australia because of glasshouse tomatoes. Could be wrong, though. 

For the record, I own CGC. Bought them at about $2.10 years ago for the tomatoes, basically. Definitely not the kind of stock someone around here would be looking at, I’d imagine, so not spruiking them. I would be happy/interested to find out about others like it, though.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-02-28 19:06:04+10:00">
     <body>I've had CGC on my watch list for ages but never but the bullet.

WOA is into regenerative farming.

I bought a small parcel of RGI a long time ago because they have vertical farming technology but they have been a dog for a long time and probably won't ever get things going.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BTthePrettyGood" created="2021-02-28 19:16:04+10:00">
     <body>Thanks mate. I’ve added WOA to the watch list. Am I correct in interpreting the loss for the year being 400% on last year? I’m a bit tired and not in the right headspace for financials.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:07:56+10:00">
    <body>Haha where are u in Aus? Even they mess me up mate especially up in Darwin/Cairns much prefer cooler climate.

Yeah farming is eventually going to have to adapt to the swings of temperature the world looks like it's going to.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 18:17:27+10:00">
     <body>Haha, only in rural Vic. Came here to live the dream - surprisingly, I genuinely believe that I am. Fucking love Australia, never going back =D</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 18:19:57+10:00">
      <body>Well done mate if you ever feel home sick come to WA Perth we have a fuck load of English haha.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-28 17:26:39+10:00">
  <body>Surely uranium is going up tomorrow... Right? PEN is starting to look a little nasty</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="protesttime" created="2021-02-28 17:28:34+10:00">
   <body>I'm still up 65%, foolish to double up but I might</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="EpicHamMan" created="2021-02-28 18:32:25+10:00">
  <body>you got this IHL</body>
  <comment ups="-6" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-02-28 18:37:11+10:00">
   <body>Sold half my stocks on IHL, just don't have faith in it anymore!</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Otherwise_Giraffe255" created="2021-02-28 18:47:56+10:00">
    <body>Why the loss of faith? No negative announcements recently</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-02-28 19:13:02+10:00">
    <body>...

You're bailing on a long term hold in the pharmaceutical industry before they even had finished a single trial?

Maybe stick to the Big 4 banks and Vanguard.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-02-28 20:03:39+10:00">
    <body>you are brain dead</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-02-28 19:37:43+10:00">
  <body>Just saw an ad on channel 7 for how kochie will tell me how to get in on the "surging" stock market. 

U wot m8 I've seen more red than my fiance's period</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-28 20:06:04+10:00">
   <body>Just saw it now “Kochie’s expert guide” hahahaha fuck off cunt</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-02-28 19:46:25+10:00">
   <body>If Kochie is selling that we are going red.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 20:20:19+10:00">
   <body>That guy is such an awful cunt - but I think we'd all be amazed at the number of clueless mom n' pop retails that smarmy twat can sway.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 20:21:17+10:00">
   <body>Diversify across the 4 major banks lel</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="rav103" created="2021-02-28 19:50:02+10:00">
  <body>The Australian sharemarket is *tipped* to *open* firmly *higher* on Monday despite lacklustre overseas leads, with the iron ore price expected to provide a degree of support as local players look ahead to the Reserve Bank's *policy meeting* on Tuesday. -   
Source **The Australian**</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:55:57+10:00">
   <body>Translation:

Some higher up newspaper cunt is sweating his balls off so he gets his editing room to pump out some confirmation bias. Eeny meeny miney, MINES, IRON YES that's why the entire market will be okay

Edit: had a read, that article might as well be replaced by [this classic](https://ei.marketwatch.com/Multimedia/2018/08/28/Photos/NS/MW-GP095_Screen_20180828120901_NS.png?uuid=adac9a4e-aadc-11e8-b64f-ac162d7bc1f7)</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 20:20:24+10:00">
    <body>Haha I swear a news article can give people confidence and completly change a market.
I won't complain 🥳</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 20:08:57+10:00">
   <body>I choose to believe this because I have $20K of T+2's due tomorrow.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 17:26:44+10:00">
  <body>Friday T+2'd $10K of NXL at $6.20 and another $10K of PEN @ 12c. Gonna be an interesting morning... should be able to skim a couple of hundred bucks off it, but we'll see.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ilestMYRON" created="2021-02-28 17:56:01+10:00">
   <body>I did the same with PEN. Hoping for a quick win to put on VMT.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 18:08:41+10:00">
    <body>Not RAC? Surprising.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ilestMYRON" created="2021-02-28 18:12:13+10:00">
     <body>My friend has RAC and has banned me from buying it. He knows my history of making things tank. 🤣</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:07:40+10:00">
   <body>Yikespp</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-28 18:25:11+10:00">
  <body>Watch NZS and TNT and hope for them tendies, WEEK OF GREEN LETS GO!</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-02-28 18:36:51+10:00">
   <body>nzs, havent heard that name is a while!!</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-28 18:45:40+10:00">
    <body>There be many a bag holders hiding here I am sure, me I got back in a 2c, its been a ride thats for sure</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="ToiIets" created="2021-02-28 19:17:25+10:00">
  <body>I read it as thoughts and prayers, not plans and thoughts. I need thoughts and prayers after the last couple of weeks.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-02-28 19:44:39+10:00">
   <body>Solid name my guy</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="stonkydonks" created="2021-02-28 19:27:22+10:00">
  <body>Up to my nuts in guts with XST. No choice but to hold now FS. Bring a green Monday!</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="d2blues" created="2021-02-28 19:59:08+10:00">
   <body>Fingers crossed for you brother</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 20:10:42+10:00">
   <body>I'm in for $14K @ 1.7c because I'm a complete fucking mug. Too late to bail now, holding 'dem bags.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-02-28 20:13:00+10:00">
    <body>Will you average down?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 20:14:02+10:00">
     <body>Nah, just wait and see now. Support is at 1c so it's unlikely to go any lower.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="CH3CKMT3" created="2021-02-28 17:33:27+10:00">
  <body>Green 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-28 17:33:27+10:00">
   <body>This isn't being deleted(yet), but we suggest trying harder next time.

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-02-28 18:33:27+10:00">
  <body>balls deep on TMR, IHL and LRSOC. Got 25k clearing up tuesday to double down on one of them or open a pos on NDQ depending on how risky im feeling</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="scorpio_" created="2021-02-28 17:22:04+10:00">
  <body>Hope a few more fundies got around to reading AVA's half yearly report this weekend and it starts heading back towards 60c.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jordyyp" created="2021-02-28 17:40:56+10:00">
   <body>I'm with you man, got a bright future hopefully</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Tacomaster33" created="2021-02-28 18:03:34+10:00">
  <body>Probably gonna double up on nxt

Unlikely I'll make a post about appen, results werent too bad and they looked good but I think management is trash so wont be touching. So if you're not worried about management they're worth a look into

A2m is dead in my opinion, wouldnt touch unless it hits $8 which it may never do</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="matt_step" created="2021-02-28 18:44:14+10:00">
   <body>I topped up on Friday mate (NXT). So much future excitement</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Tacomaster33" created="2021-02-28 18:58:23+10:00">
    <body>Results were good, outlook is straight forward and easy to understand. Only issue is that they arent making a profit</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-28 18:14:16+10:00">
  <body>Small parcel of Orica to assist in top up on Z1P to send me into heaven and 40 virgins.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 18:20:09+10:00">
   <body>Or is it raisins?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BLD88" created="2021-02-28 20:22:42+10:00">
   <body>Same with ORI. Should get the rebound next week.....but you know.......probably won’t</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Logicorluck" created="2021-02-28 18:34:34+10:00">
  <body>Setting a boundary with myself to take the screen refresh from 2 minute intervals to 30 minute intervals🤣. Oh...and hodl, hodl, hodl, no matter what happens!</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-02-28 18:49:41+10:00">
   <body>Tried this, I now just spam the refresh button every 15 sec, hit that data refresh point</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Gr8SevenLive" created="2021-02-28 18:51:31+10:00">
  <body>🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠🧠

BRRRRRRAAAAAAAAIIIIIIIIINNNNNNNN

BRN 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-02-28 19:08:13+10:00">
   <body>🧠🍟🧠🍟🧠🍟🧠🍟</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-02-28 19:25:23+10:00">
   <body>Lol, after their annual report saying there's a massive increase in operating costs, only a huge announcement will give us 🚀🚀🚀...

Until then we'll keep testing the 0.5 barrier</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="ozzie_soul" created="2021-02-28 19:13:17+10:00">
  <body>New to this. But doing DD on Red5. Will share it here, if worthwhile.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="MichaelRogers5" created="2021-02-28 19:17:18+10:00">
   <body>Yeh hit us up - worse that can happen is downvoted beyond oblivion</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ozzie_soul" created="2021-02-28 19:19:40+10:00">
    <body>Well what got my attention to put in the effort was Simply wall st. puts the value at 8x the current price. 
To the group how trustworthy is Simply wall st as a source</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-02-28 19:47:22+10:00">
     <body>Simply Wall St has AI sourced data. The valuations can be / often are wacky. 

Sometimes the metrics are good tho, well presented with a comparison to industry or sector averages. The useful bits of the company reports can be things like info on insider buying, top holders &amp; ownership info. I use it sometimes but treat it with caution. You can find the same info in other places, like the companies own reports.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ozzie_soul" created="2021-02-28 20:04:01+10:00">
      <body>Yeah makes sense. Hence I thought of capitalising on the groups wisdom. Thanks bud.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-28 19:32:46+10:00">
     <body>I got the free trial and I really like the way they summarise the info. I like seeing the ceo salary and management and risks etc at a glance. Not sure if I will sign up though. Don’t know about trustworthiness. Someone else can answer that.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Logicorluck" created="2021-02-28 19:50:04+10:00">
     <body>When MYD hit the charts last year at 1.80 they initially had it way undervalued and put a fair valuation at 7 and a bit of change, so I fell for that and bought in like the FOMO autist I am. The next day all of a sudden their valuation was sitting at 1.20 and we all know how the rest of the story panned out with MYD!</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ozzie_soul" created="2021-02-28 20:02:47+10:00">
      <body>True that. Hence for contingency I have assumed with the assumption it won’t peak pass $1.30 (by 2022). But fair point and thanks</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-28 19:31:04+10:00">
   <body>Yeah please do. A lot of us are still learning and it’s valuable to see what people do for their dd and the information that is relevant and see what is missed and especially what other people point out. I learn a lot from the comments on other people’s dd.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 18:13:25+10:00">
  <body>Want to see what 
KGN, ZIP, PBH,BET do.
Kgn seems to be fairly undervalued.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Mobile-Rice-8889" created="2021-02-28 18:27:25+10:00">
   <body>KGN still has a long way to fall that stock price is still over valued. People rushed to retail stocks during covid even if they were dud companies.</body>
   <comment ups="-6" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 18:44:49+10:00">
    <body>I appreciate you're opinion. But I strongly disagree. They're growth is impeccable.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Mobile-Rice-8889" created="2021-02-28 18:50:56+10:00">
     <body>Their grey imports are their only name brand items priced competively but Amazon is really starting to muscle in on this space with the ability to order from the US via the AU website. Give the choice between Amazon and Kogan i know where id spend my money everytime.

Their Kogan branded products are absolute crap. Their diversification efforts into things like credit cards, insurance and utlities are half baked at best, try applying for a Kogan credit card and you'll see what i mean.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 19:34:06+10:00">
      <body>You guys are missing the point. 
Numbers don't lie.
Kogan is garbage.
But this garbage makes money.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:54:33+10:00">
     <body>Yep agreed they becoming like ebay</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="PopGotcha44" created="2021-02-28 19:27:10+10:00">
   <body>Kogan as a company is straight garbage</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 19:44:33+10:00">
    <body>I agree. I don't like the company. But I can see if getting more profits.

Where do savvy poor people go to buy shit. They go online. They look at catch, my deal,  Kogan Amazon. 

Ruslan ain't gonna roll over he got 3 years left and bunch if stocks</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PopGotcha44" created="2021-02-28 19:53:06+10:00">
     <body>It's a shame though cause their own branded devices are so horrible, people just get attracted by the cheaper price. Low cost, low margin, high turnover</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 20:02:28+10:00">
      <body>I know if (he) ruslan decided to make better products that were a bit more expensive it may of left a better taste in people mouths. The thing I would never use Kogan. I would never use zip and Afterpay unless I seen their to be a benefit in it.

Like getting a shed installed at my house interest free. Before the price of steel goes up and labor and wages go up.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 20:03:06+10:00">
       <body>Most companies I would never use usually do well. I guess stupid always wins.</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PopGotcha44" created="2021-02-28 20:03:40+10:00">
       <body>Spot on!</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="burnnttoast" created="2021-02-28 18:43:28+10:00">
  <body>Sold my Z1P last week but might buy back at current price! 
Also looking at LGP- unsure about buying yet 
Hoping a good Monday for all 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-28 18:50:35+10:00">
   <body>Buy the Z1p dip</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="slutinabutt" created="2021-02-28 19:15:09+10:00">
   <body>Steer clear of LGP for now (my opinion). Why? There is a spp on at the moment for 65c a share. Basically 30m worth of shares at 65c a piece is going to hit the market, and that is why the price keeps going down. Not to mention all the other shares sold to the "profesionals" for the same price. Basically if you can get them cheaper than 65c go ahead, otherwise people will be holding it down for some time locking in profits from the SPP.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Carra23" created="2021-02-28 19:06:45+10:00">
  <body>Sell Monday buy Friday!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-02-28 19:51:58+10:00">
  <body>My butthole is ready for another week of red, just be gentle, and use lube.

Seriously though expecting an uptick in mining and gold.

PEN is a long hold - don't expect much movement any time soon.

Hopefully the LKE gang kicks it off, not in it, but hoping for wins cause I am not seeing any real profits any time soon.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-02-28 20:05:46+10:00">
   <body>Just forget you hold PEN for the next 6-12 months! If it dips under 10c ahort term buy up.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Wannaliveinpenthouse" created="2021-02-28 20:12:57+10:00">
  <body>Green Monday Pls</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mabarkerandher3sons" created="2021-02-28 18:16:17+10:00">
  <body>Tnr coming off share allocation and suspension from quotation 

Up 200% since September 

Jorc upgrade announcement in first quarter still to come

🚀🚀🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-02-28 18:35:24+10:00">
  <body>Has anyone had experience with long wait times for commsex to increase margin lending. i keep accidentally selling high and i need to leverage myself to max so i can go full retard.

Its been about a week and theres lots of dips i want to buy :(</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-02-28 19:54:37+10:00">
   <body>Don't do it.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="arrybags" created="2021-02-28 18:56:38+10:00">
  <body>While my PEN is limping, and IOU is placid, iam going to throw some more money into my account tonight, what should i top up on? RAC or LKE? I have made some tendies on both already, might just chuck some on both and let them ride bareback for a while?</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="yonkapin" created="2021-02-28 19:01:47+10:00">
   <body>i'm retarded so LKE</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-28 20:24:10+10:00">
   <body>Neither as they are bought over bought and you won't make mega tendies. Take a look into IXR, EXR, NVA and hold long for 5-10 baggers</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Almighti3" created="2021-02-28 18:59:36+10:00">
   <body>I would choose RAC but LKE is not a bad pick. Both expecting announcements soon. RAC announcement probably longer away, but I can’t see it dropping between now and then. Whereas LKE likes to jump around a bit.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="gboy333" created="2021-02-28 17:46:02+10:00">
  <body>Anyone stuck with the dud that is EOS. Painful😪</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-28 17:47:38+10:00">
  <body>CHK - results any minute now. 

DSK - think people have been sleeping on this a bit. Though aint rocket type of stonk but just do a quick comparison of H1 results between DSK and LOV to see the value.

Other than that, Looking at GAL and IXR play this week.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MacchuWA" created="2021-02-28 19:20:59+10:00">
   <body>I've been telling anyone who'll listen, CHK have got nothing but the veins and halo coming off Oak Dam West. Clear from the geophysics, clear from the language they use in the announcements, clearer still from leaks from people in the know.

Hotcopper for CHK is a joke, everyone convincing themselves and each other that they're sitting on the next Carrapateena, going to be a cold hard reality check when those assays come in.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Elegantmango77" created="2021-02-28 18:24:19+10:00">
   <body>I got more GAL last week so glad too</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-28 19:15:08+10:00">
  <body>IXR, XST.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="bshezza" created="2021-02-28 19:23:23+10:00">
  <body>TYR - will go upsies</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Odd_Potato_246" created="2021-02-28 20:13:11+10:00">
  <body>Some good news for AR9</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigDaveFromAus" created="2021-02-28 20:16:41+10:00">
   <body>Care to elaborate? Or just willing it on?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Apprehensive_Act2539" created="2021-02-28 20:15:46+10:00">
  <body>Honestly...with the whole BNPL regulations announced for march 1st (from what I read from someone on reddit... so taken with a shaker full of salt) I intend to dump half of my zip holdings or possibly more and jump onto credit intelligence (CI1) im assuming other people not unlike myself who actually have zippay accounts have somewhat tense anal passages. Diversifying is a must for me. My account with superheroe which is super small compared to commsec (which a homeless person could probably challenge...its shit too) is just zippay hahaha I went full on FOMO seeing as I wanted to buy in early jan but FU**ING CHRISTMAS PRESENTS for the ingrates i call my family is where my jan money went...yes I hate them even more now haha. 

What about you guys, are you you the dumping like diarrhoea type, turtle heading diamond hand manning it or straight up gripping on as if you are strapped into a skateboard with a rope attached to the back of a Bugatti? Not advice just what you're doing</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-28 20:18:14+10:00">
   <body>CI1 is solid - got a little run the other day but is destined for the moon!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="queens_third_corgi" created="2021-02-28 17:06:40+10:00">
  <body>Expect more red in my portfolio.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="QuirkyPee" created="2021-02-28 17:28:26+10:00">
  <body>Nuix please please bounce back.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 17:32:56+10:00">
   <body>I'd be very surprised if it doesn't make at least some semblance of a bounce - that 32.44% was unreal. I thought I was buying the bottom at $6.20 but it finished $6.06... wowsers</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="QuirkyPee" created="2021-02-28 19:52:18+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I bought more at -27% and again at -29%. Hopefully the US stimulus will helps tomorrow.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MadzDad87" created="2021-02-28 17:39:48+10:00">
  <body>Would love to see some green from SYA. Might have to buy s’more this week if it drops any further.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-28 17:42:09+10:00">
   <body>Been looking.

Any catalysts coming up for SYA? Is winning thr NAL bid really important? Isnt it just buying some old
Operations? Cheers</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Blisser_the_Sniff" created="2021-02-28 18:08:06+10:00">
    <body>I think the project is close to their mineral tenements offering efficiencies, also the delay submission of the bid was what held the price back for a couple of years. Look at the history where it bounced between .007 and .009.. each time the tender grew close the price went up, then tanked on delays. I wouldn’t want to be holding if they were unsuccessful. Their plan to be a part of end to end processing, in an area with Hydro electricity, offers them extra green credits and a competitive advantage. If successful I would expect a steady flow of news over a couple years to keep them moving. I bought and sold a few times now, originally in December at .07 and .09. Price look good now for another go! I couldn’t find anything on when the successful bidder will be announced? I’m keen to hear if you find something.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jockr64" created="2021-02-28 18:25:10+10:00">
     <body>Originally announced as around the 25th(?) of this month. 2 New bidders entered close to the original closing date, which pushed things back a bit. u/jooyaao, the NAL bid won't be the end of them if they don't get it, but it includes a whole processing plant (newish?) only 50Kms from there Authier(?)  location. Will keep CapEx lower, and expedite production a bit.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-28 18:33:02+10:00">
      <body>Thanks a lot. Well supposedly winner of the bid will paid the highest so even if win there could be a winner’s curse i.e. paid too much. Hopefully still a good deal. Like the stock but the some uncertainty around bidding situation. Might wait until the bidding finished even if i miss thr first rerate.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jockr64" created="2021-02-28 18:35:11+10:00">
       <body>I think it may drift upwards a bit between now and then. Already in for 100k shares @.05, and thinking about topping up on oppies, there almost giving them away😉</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-02-28 17:45:28+10:00">
  <body>Man fuck THC/EPN, just a constant tanking.

How can you go +50% revenue and end flat... I thought AC8 was a dogshit pot stock but this takes the cake</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:06:39+10:00">
   <body>You can pretty much assume all pot stocks are dogshit...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="dragonbrah" created="2021-02-28 18:46:26+10:00">
   <body>fmd been holding for so long and its just gone down... hoping it will go up once the world opens up again</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-02-28 19:17:26+10:00">
    <body>Thinking of eating the loss. Quicker to get it back rolling into something else.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-28 18:09:13+10:00">
  <body>Should be a quieter day tomorrow in terms of volume due to public holiday in WA
Futures ASX says green but obviously means jackshit currently
Not too much bear gang here yet.. just be careful!</body>
  <comment ups="29" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-28 18:18:55+10:00">
   <body>You guys get internet in WA?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jmuzz182" created="2021-02-28 20:24:13+10:00">
    <body>Yeh the exalted one, Dear Leader MarkyMac, got working internet for the first time in WA last week.

It's caused a bunch of problems though, no-one can get through to him on the landline any more.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="ProperField2596" created="2021-02-28 18:22:37+10:00">
   <body>WA public holiday will reduce asx volume tomorrow by no more than 1%</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-02-28 19:14:58+10:00">
    <body>WA always had an inflated sense of self importance.   

r/Perth got a rude shock when they locked themselves down (again) and Australia somehow survived.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="unclepadrigo" created="2021-02-28 19:38:31+10:00">
   <body>You mean the mining town?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="simcityrefund1" created="2021-02-28 18:55:46+10:00">
   <body>Where do U see futures?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Trixster_moon" created="2021-02-28 17:52:55+10:00">
  <body>Recently bought into GLN on friday and would like to hear your opinions on the company, I dont know if this ticker has been discussed here before. 

GLN, post CR, now has $15m cash, 

Its enterprise value is $110m, substantially lower than its peers.
Enterprise value over NPV: Most lithium stocks are valued at 20% - 70%
GLN: 8%
AGY: 32%
LKE: 20%

Lab results of purity expected this month. Also expected news on there Greenbushes mine exploration. 

With the recent CR oversubscribed @0.50c 
Is this tomorrows bargin @0.49c? 

Disclosure: HELD @0.45c 27/02</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Carra23" created="2021-02-28 19:05:16+10:00">
   <body>I also hold GLN. Bought in 2 weeks ago for .55 tho. Should have waited but holding for a year at least either way.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MacchuWA" created="2021-02-28 19:13:58+10:00">
   <body>Greenbushes is a risky play: people have been looking around there for awhile, they have an exploration model but still early stage. But it's their brines you hold Galan for though. They've got everything they need to be taken out or start producing sooner or later. If you believe in the long term fundamentals of lithium (and you probably should) then hold lithium companies, Galan among them.

Roughly speaking, we could turn on about a million TPA LCE from defined resources in a hurry if the price spikes (i.e. rough as guts, double or triple current production). Will we need more than that to feed the EV and microgrid markets? If you think yes, then lithium is in for a long price accumulation, and every lithium stock goes up. If not, then not. All depends on how bullish you are on the green transition.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-02-28 18:10:55+10:00">
  <body>NXL if it hits $5, TYR if I can get it at $2.70, NXT if it dips below $11 again.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-28 18:31:06+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-28 18:31:06+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="KIDNEYTHEIVES" created="2021-02-28 19:01:52+10:00">
  <body>PNV with some strong announcements last week. Feel like the b̶l̶o̶o̶d̶b̶a̶t̶h̶ market last week stole the good attention away. Hopefully see some reflection this week.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-28 19:07:11+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="MichaelRogers5" created="2021-02-28 19:17:42+10:00">
   <body>Fuck up cunt</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:24:49+10:00">
    <body>Well put sir</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Weekly_Flight5752" created="2021-02-28 19:08:43+10:00">
   <body>LKE🚀</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-02-28 19:11:33+10:00">
    <body>That's also on the top ten list</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 19:10:44+10:00">
   <body>Find a stock worth mentioning do a comprehensive DD on it and im sure attention will be drawn.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:09:08+10:00">
   <body>I'll do my part and switch from PEN to BOE ☢️☢️☢️</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-02-28 19:09:24+10:00">
   <body>Love my NTI - I’ve only seen it mentioned couple times</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 19:26:06+10:00">
   <body>I'm balls deep in MMI. No-one else here likes it, but I reckon it can perform. Also check out the recent "Invest for the Future" (YouTube) video about WGX - seems promising.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 20:24:42+10:00">
    <body>-2?

That's rookie numbers. I need to pump up those numbers, ya fucks lol</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ausdeza" created="2021-02-28 19:22:13+10:00">
  <body>Anyone sitting on some PRL ? would be great if she stopped plummeting after the Credit Suisse pump and dump.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="methyl_violet" created="2021-02-28 19:31:44+10:00">
   <body>Yeah, holding.  Still ahead on entry price.  Only saw one big plummet 10 days ago, been reasonably stable since.  Pretty speculative but I think there's big potential in a green hydrogen project so gonna hold</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ausdeza" created="2021-02-28 20:03:10+10:00">
    <body>Yea I didn't put much on, so not sweating but I did have my first bout of fomo and bought at 0.112 so don't have a choice but to hold hah.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="methyl_violet" created="2021-02-28 20:27:55+10:00">
     <body>.05 or .112,  It's either going nowhere,  or gonna rocket very high.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Fostered_meme" created="2021-02-28 19:38:29+10:00">
  <body>Guess I’ll be watching JXT to see if I’ll be making money or watching a bloke eat a hat in a few months.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-02-28 20:12:41+10:00">
   <body>Haha hope you’re not this premature in other areas.  Revenue starts April with lots of good press.  Hope you bought some to soften the loss.

Edit: PS welcome to the downvoted club, contrarian views aren’t welcome in this establishment.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-28 19:48:46+10:00">
  <body>Hoping CHK gets these assay results out and we see 2%+ Cu</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-28 20:05:09+10:00">
  <body>Doing some bag holding so hoping for a pick up
AC8, JXT, OPT, NVA, RBL &amp; PTF but don’t mind holding as all look good.

In the green (some by lots and some by cents) but looking for some upward movements - LIT, IOU, EPN, IHL, ROO, IMU, PPH, SOR, Z1P &amp; NVX.

Looking for something else to peak my interest!</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-28 20:19:30+10:00">
   <body>Forgot to mention a
My nice green for CI1</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Vrucaon" created="2021-02-28 20:21:00+10:00">
  <body>Does anyone know companies that produce lithium hydroxide and carbonate in Australia? Both private and public.

I know a lot of companies are building refineries now but how many exist so far?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="notasabretooth" created="2021-02-28 17:29:26+10:00">
  <body>Hopefully RBL bottomed out with the market sell-off and starts making it's way back up above $6. Either that, or another red day for me tomorrow.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Sea-Board108" created="2021-02-28 17:34:09+10:00">
  <body>Anyone feelin FLT or MYQ?</body>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 17:40:54+10:00">
   <body>Buy FLT. Hold 10 years. Win big. Nice one you in 10 years. Buy it for your kids.

But is it a rocket? Are we your kids? No / not / what? / Now I'm confused... lol

Never even heard of MYQ before you mentioned, but chart says up...</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 17:42:02+10:00">
    <body>Unless... COVID-22?</body>
    <comment ups="-2" downs="0" author="Sea-Board108" created="2021-02-28 17:45:05+10:00">
     <body>We all know WW3 is scheduled before the next COVID</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Sea-Board108" created="2021-02-28 17:45:25+10:00">
      <body>Wait crap! Is this public?</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 17:51:32+10:00">
       <body>Everybody wave at the nice man 👋</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Sea-Board108" created="2021-02-28 17:44:09+10:00">
    <body>Investments are for the future, no? Just here hoping us autistic sons of guns are around long enough to attempt procreation (successfully anyway)</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="Hammer_1213" created="2021-02-28 17:52:53+10:00">
   <body>If things go to plan FLT should be a good buy between now and October. I'm holding FLT at an average of $13.72</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="becify" created="2021-02-28 18:07:12+10:00">
  <body>Last day of trading for NSBO, will be interesting to see how much changes hands.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="WhiteChocoo" created="2021-02-28 17:13:36+10:00">
  <body>What’s peoples thoughts on AUZ seems like it’s got massive potential from what I’ve seen, anyone read into it more?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-28 20:14:10+10:00">
  <body>Hope my fellow autists have been preparing for the coming correction - hope to see some great buys in the next few months - be greedy when people are fearful and fearful when people are greedy</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-02-28 20:29:24+10:00">
   <body>Lol correction</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 17:25:04+10:00">
  <body>Hope everyone has a stocked up supply of lube</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="platypusreacharound" created="2021-02-28 19:47:14+10:00">
   <body>I don't see why this is getting down voted. This is good advice any day of the week.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:52:31+10:00">
    <body>It is blasphemy to suggest sometimes it do go down</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="Shitchat2021" created="2021-02-28 20:03:08+10:00">
  <body>BRV 👀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-5" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-02-28 19:08:43+10:00">
  <body>Anyone have a SMSF? 
What ETF/Stocks do you have in your portfolio?

Edit - stock suggestions for someone who has a smsf would be nice rather than having a ham about mentioning eft LOL</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:10:14+10:00">
   <body>Don't use the E-word here 
🤮</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 19:13:28+10:00">
    <body>Haha some good ones, I've mentioned REMX here before it's more than doubled in 6 months. That's pretty epic for a etf.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="-2" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-02-28 19:12:38+10:00">
    <body>Don’t need to be a dick about it - i don’t buy etf in my everyday portfolio</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Snck_Pck" created="2021-02-28 19:16:42+10:00">
     <body>You must be new here</body>
     <comment ups="-8" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-02-28 19:19:31+10:00">
      <body>Nope..... just can’t ask a question it seems</body>
      <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-28 19:22:20+10:00">
       <body>If you wanna discuss shit like V*nguard go back to the kiddie pool in ausfinance</body>
       <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-28 19:26:02+10:00">
        <body>Haha easy mate more out there than that Vanguard shite.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AntiCGT" created="2021-02-28 19:50:52+10:00">
   <body>IVV for growth and WHF/ AFI for the bonus share plan to dodge the divvy tax</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-02-28 20:01:00+10:00">
    <body>Thank you for some actual info!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-6" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-28 19:30:25+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-02-28 19:45:40+10:00">
   <body>Just had a look, if I was you I'd probably put them in the queue for 0.02c with a "until expiry" order (and update it every month). If you can manage to get out at 2 you're going to lose a third, but the MEB chart's not looking bright, is it? =/

Just looked up the strike in Appendix 2A and the MEBOB strike is 3c as well, eeeeeeek!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-7" downs="0" author="falzenk" created="2021-02-28 19:56:42+10:00">
  <body>Anyone hold SHN? They reported great drilling finding last friday but only 3% up. I believe it will 🚀🚀🚀🌕🌕🌕 tomorrow.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-28 20:27:02+10:00">
   <body>SHN is more a of smart money gold play. Not a bad one either with Paul Chapman on the board. But there is a fuck ton of unlisted shares to come yet. 

Haven't checked yet but guessing your getting down voted because your new. But this is a stock I want cheaper</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-16" downs="0" author="lovestospoog3" created="2021-02-28 17:11:28+10:00">
  <body>Expect some more red,
The market is turning</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-28 18:25:59+10:00">
   <body>After the US passed stimulus? Nil chance of red.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
