<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-01-06 Wednesday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>WBT (11) </mention>
  <mention>VUL (10) HYPE=10, TIP=10</mention>
  <mention>AVA (10) TIP=10</mention>
  <mention>LOT (9) </mention>
  <mention>ANP (8) </mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="SocialSelfSabotage" created="2021-01-05 18:21:23+10:00">
   <body>I could buy any stock on the ASX but I just keep buying more Z1P. I need help</body>
   <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-01-05 18:36:43+10:00">
    <body>Why are you selfharming. You need a counsellor.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="jolebu" created="2021-01-05 19:51:24+10:00" sentiment="TIP 10">
    <body>Z1P to $10 by Christmas 2021</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-05 18:01:08+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>Potential RMX entry tomorrow after their answered speeding ticket, we have until the 12th to sell the rumour lads.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="imiweli" created="2021-01-05 18:06:39+10:00">
    <body>Seemed like the insiders started buying up with results out next week.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-01-05 18:51:03+10:00">
     <body>That's illegal</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mechengguy93" created="2021-01-05 19:21:59+10:00">
      <body>When has that stopped people before?</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-01-05 21:33:20+10:00">
      <body>So is nose beer. Wa-hey! 🥴</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BatFluReturns" created="2021-01-05 21:35:53+10:00">
      <body>Not if you're already rich it's not</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-01-05 18:22:46+10:00">
    <body>up over 54% just today..... time to enter bit late or nah?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-05 18:26:59+10:00">
     <body>That’s what I’m trying to work out, have come to this forum for confirmation bias</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-01-05 19:25:17+10:00">
      <body>Take this or leave it but people have lined up to sell the news so although you may think you’re now gonna get in to do the same the risk is now greatly increased. As for the “leaky ship” claims that’s not how smart insiders do things. Insiders already hold and they drive down share prices to scare you off before announcements. The last time this thing announced gold results it started at 015 before the trading halt and due to dilution and pretty shit results only went a couple pips to 017.   Youre now experiencing fomo.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="mechengguy93" created="2021-01-05 19:21:41+10:00">
      <body>It is not too late comrade</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Louis989" created="2021-01-05 18:58:21+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>What do you guys see in Bph? I see massive potential in this year. Jump on before too late.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="kinky-penguin" created="2021-01-05 22:26:29+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>i was thinking about getting back into AVA but i just don’t think it’s going anywhere anytime soon. might bounce around 50-70c for a year unless they have a good amount of news

gotten myself into explorative mining stocks... 

PLY pulled back at last today

fuck z1p

still think APT could crack $150, just coz

hoping for some good publicity around PFT. they’ve got solid products, could be a company that just gobbles up other companies to make an empire. idk, but i reckon this ones a good longer term play. looking at WOA and MBH potentially but there’s probably more value just putting money in PFT anyway


looking forward to dw8’s christmas results</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-01-06 02:16:44+10:00">
    <body>AVA next quarterly result releasing within a month.

In their latest annual report, they mentioned an expected payment from the Aus DoD for a contract of $3.4mil by H1FY21.

Expected $2.6mil of payment made by IMOD by Q2FY21</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="WingsAndRuin001" created="2021-01-06 06:35:04+10:00">
    <body>Late last year MC said he wanted PFT be making around $500,000,000 revenue within 3-5 years. Should he successfully pull that off, it would make the SP around $20 (assuming no CR which I don't think there will be because they still have 2.5 mil from the IPO money left). 

Also, looking at the numbers of how many hot chickens are sold, if they sold 1/10 of the potato and gravy with every hot chicken, that alone would double their revenue currently. 

I'm very bullish on PFT and I can't wait to see their Annual Report this year with their audited numbers.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-01-05 22:55:02+10:00">
    <body>AVA is like an ETF in my eyes (safe bet) , you won't lose if buying in at the current prices . Should jump back to its former glory soon . I'll be happy at 70c</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="kinky-penguin" created="2021-01-05 23:04:30+10:00">
     <body>yeah absolutely. their financials are pretty sexy as is, just no pizazz at the moment</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-01-05 23:14:52+10:00">
      <body>I feel ya</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:37:11+10:00">
      <body>Its sexy but no pizazz? High standards! 😂</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Zomg_ks" created="2021-01-06 06:27:07+10:00">
    <body>I'm buying more pft and dw8 myself so reassuring to hear pengu prophet thinking along the same lines</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-05 23:24:52+10:00">
    <body>I have PFT and WOA. I love both companies and think they both have solid management. But I agree they are a similar bet.</body>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 01:56:35+10:00">
     <body>Sell PFT.</body>
     <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-06 02:26:39+10:00">
      <body>I might sell purely based on the fact that they put sultanas in their curried potatoes.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:39:44+10:00">
       <body>Do you like sultanas in your curried potatoes? Neither do I. 

Worst case PFT get REMOVED from (WW) shelves. True possibility.

I sold (@ 1.34), do what you want.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 10:10:24+10:00">
      <body>If PFT breaks below $1 again, then it could test support at 60c. I hope holders have some sort of stop in place. Resistance is around $1.20 so risk/reward is poor. What is it with food brands? Better off owning the supermarket/trading woollies.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 10:19:15+10:00">
    <body>WOA and PLY - no liquidity</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:34:28+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>BLY. Have a look at the chart. 1 yr and 5 yr. I will be on this tomorrow. They dropped 3rd qtr EBITDA 50% to $40Mill. MC is (was) $45Mill (now $60Mill after 30%+ rise today. No news the last 2 days but vol rocketed as has the share price. I haven't checked HC yet to see if it's just all HC smooth brained retard action, but even if this is the case, looks tradeable.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 15:45:41+10:00">
    <body>all in on borat</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:52:01+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
     <body>That does it. Borat to the moon.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="doubleknavery" created="2021-01-07 10:44:41+10:00">
    <body>Holy shit - it's up 36% today... mods, does this deserve flair</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-07 18:34:36+10:00">
     <body>It went past any price I thought it could reach (89c). Had an afternoon breakout and closed up 50%+. After all that, I got no idea anymore.It was an easy call at 69c.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="MC_llama" created="2021-01-05 18:24:49+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Bought in to NVA today...I was told there would be 🚀🚀🚀?</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Nocashgang" created="2021-01-05 19:15:52+10:00">
    <body>take your protein pills and put your helmet on</body>
    <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="blahyadablahyada" created="2021-01-05 19:44:14+10:00">
     <body>And pepper your angus.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:26:49+10:00">
      <body>This is peppered-steak to NVA - we really think you've made the grade!</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="cheyaboi" created="2021-01-05 21:51:07+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Last chance to jump on board the NVA train, results this month will tip it over 🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-01-06 00:25:52+10:00">
    <body>Back into 20s soon</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 10:15:41+10:00">
    <body>I removed NVA from my watchlist yesterday on under performance relative to the market. It has years of work ahead of it so it is a long term hold.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-01-06 07:04:47+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Check out the volume on RMX 😮🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 07:30:46+10:00">
    <body>Again?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 07:34:25+10:00">
     <body>Where do you find the volume before market opens? Is it in the buy sell area in comsec</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-01-06 07:58:23+10:00">
      <body>You find it in the depth tab and it gives you the volume and price</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nimrod123" created="2021-01-06 11:22:26+10:00">
    <body>i sold yesterday at .016... not feeling very smart</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:10:27+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Uranium Bull Gang where you at? 🚀 🚀 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Gooseburger1" created="2021-01-06 13:23:52+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>PEN up 13% is offseting the potential softening of my erection from AVA going red again.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Affectionate-Ad2294" created="2021-01-05 19:44:58+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>IHL 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="SlaughterRain" created="2021-01-05 19:24:39+10:00">
  <body>WBT.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-01-05 22:09:35+10:00">
   <body>You are reliable.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Kilo3407" created="2021-01-06 00:09:55+10:00">
   <body>You're not getting downvoted anymore 🤣</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SlaughterRain" created="2021-01-06 05:48:10+10:00">
    <body>I know, it might be a bad thing haha.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="seb_dm" created="2021-01-05 19:40:45+10:00">
   <body>Yes</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-05 18:38:28+10:00">
  <body>VUL CROSSED $3 TODAY MOTHER FUCKERS. 40 MORE CENTS AND I HAVE A 10 BAGGER.

SBW ended... flat???? [WTF?](https://i.imgflip.com/4slioe.jpg)

Stoplossed out of a stock for a $100 loss today but I ended up almost 2% so thats good.</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Biggunzmcgeee" created="2021-01-05 18:57:56+10:00">
   <body>Bruh how do you seem to constantly find these bags early enough for them to become bags. For real</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-05 21:00:32+10:00">
    <body>Research.

Conviction. 

Foresight.

LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCKLUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK LUCK</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:24:45+10:00">
     <body>So research, conviction, and foresight then? Nice!</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-06 06:43:33+10:00">
      <body>If i had of known VUL was going to do what it did i would  have thrown EVERYTHING i own at it.

I just thought it was a good investment not a potential 10 bagger.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 07:56:55+10:00">
       <body>That's it though, isn't it? You never know. I put into ARV yesterday - up 20% — could have been minus 20% for no rhyme or reason on the day.

P. S. Started watching Invest for the Future, he's alright 😁</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-01-06 03:52:53+10:00">
     <body>&gt;Research

What is your approach to research?</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-06 06:48:47+10:00">
      <body>I watched "invest for the future " on youtube and took a bastardized approach of his but with a greater risk tolerance. 

Then i just looked into green companies  that were related to battery materials. I got VUL EMN also not so green i got ARN. 

Made at least a bag off each of those.

Also MNS but they have do fuck all so far</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="WeeklyAppearance" created="2021-01-06 18:12:15+10:00">
       <body>I've seem some videos of his through recommendations on Reddit. Are you able to link us/PM me (not sure if your post will get removed) what video influenced you the most on your investing strategies?

&amp;#x200B;

Congratulations by the way.</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-07 07:29:58+10:00">
        <body>Just check out his negative 20 20 method. The way he uses his metrics to take emotion and over thinking out of trading. 

Also things like is it worth buying a house or investing in stocks, he goes through the maths.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-05 19:43:35+10:00">
   <body>Good stuff!!. Never had a 10 bagger and knowing my fucking stupid trades, probably never will.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-05 21:01:37+10:00">
    <body>BRN was technically my 1st but i didn't sell at 10 bags</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-05 21:07:01+10:00">
     <body>I reckon there's a few here who got 10 baggers out of ADV and ADN and made a mint... some might have held it ADV all the way back down though.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-06 06:41:08+10:00">
      <body>CHN might have some holders with more then 30 bags</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-06 07:01:54+10:00">
       <body>Fark... i think i saw on HC the other day a bloke has been holding WPL since .65c in the 80s.  

What's your thoughts on RLT to buy n' hold for the next 6 months?</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-06 07:31:17+10:00">
        <body>I have a package and i want some more. It's very hard to get much of it though as every time it gets sold down some there is a huge gap in the buy/sell list. 

I don't think it will go to $20  a share like some of the pumpers but i do think it should go above $2. So i am trying to get as much as i can close to $1 a share.</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-06 08:15:27+10:00">
         <body>Yeh it looks hard to get a decent amount of for sure. I think I'll dip my toes in if theres a slight pullback over the coming days/weeks.</body>
         <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-06 08:25:25+10:00">
          <body>Put in a buy order and hope it gets hits.</body>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="GeoSciFi" created="2021-01-06 11:11:57+10:00">
      <body>That'd be me on ADV.  Bought at $0.004, could've sold at $0.040 and rebought at \~$0.016 but after CGT I wouldn't be ahead by much, and who knew the SP was going to drop that low.  Still holding, as I'm hopeful they'll hit paydirt in the next 1\~2 years.  Tis an ASX bets punt after all.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-09 07:06:40+10:00">
       <body>I don't really hold enough to be concerned about whether ADV does any good. It was a calculated punt that backfired for me, bought in at 3.2c. At the time i thought it would keep running. So i guess I'll just hold and what happens.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-01-05 20:06:33+10:00">
    <body>Get on JXT bro and hold</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-05 20:38:44+10:00">
   <body>That's fucking sexy af. I need to find myself some bagss..... and a good stock too</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-05 21:02:53+10:00">
    <body>It's so so fucking hard.

I thought SBW was one. I think RLT is one. I think ANP could be one. But you need to find one before anyone else does.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-05 21:16:18+10:00">
     <body>I'm too much of a pussy to go into ANP after DXB and MSB last year. Might chuck a little parcel on tomorrow as it looks primed for a run up to 16c. 

Part of me thinks fish guts will return with a vengeance this year. A baseless call that one</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:23:15+10:00">
      <body>Fish guts will return.

Only idiots like me bought at ATH - but it will return.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-01-06 06:41:59+10:00">
      <body>Med stocks are hard. But not much harder then mining.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-05 21:18:51+10:00">
  <body>Keen for another day in Hotel Quarantine tomorrow smashing the refresh button on commsex every 5 seconds and ripping the head off it multiple times a day.

**ANP** 

**4DS**

**AVA**</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 16:54:02+10:00">
  <body>Frankly, if you come to this sub and put people down for trying to learn from their mistakes without giving any genuine input. You can go fuck yourself.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 17:30:52+10:00">
   <body>Noted. And apologies all around. I can be a real fucking arsehole sometimes</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 18:01:57+10:00">
    <body>The first step is admitting, well done! 

Haha but seriously not meant for you, not that I know of anyway.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="MC_llama" created="2021-01-05 18:24:49+10:00">
  <body>Bought in to NVA today...I was told there would be 🚀🚀🚀?</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Nocashgang" created="2021-01-05 19:15:52+10:00">
   <body>take your protein pills and put your helmet on</body>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="blahyadablahyada" created="2021-01-05 19:44:14+10:00">
    <body>And pepper your angus.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:26:49+10:00">
     <body>This is peppered-steak to NVA - we really think you've made the grade!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Scrofl" created="2021-01-05 20:36:26+10:00">
  <body>Literally my only green stonk today was TNT.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-01-05 21:12:58+10:00">
  <body>I'm planning on just checking my account come 4pm. Literally the best thing about my US stocks is that I'm not following the intra day price movements. Just wake up richer or poorer.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="autotom" created="2021-01-05 23:22:35+10:00">
   <body>poorer, always poorer.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-01-06 03:27:45+10:00">
   <body>GME, PLTR, TSLA</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 08:53:57+10:00">
  <body>Summary of yesterday's retard moves (just so you can mock me):

- Sold 3DP at 51.5c (buy in 49c, sold low, wanted money fast),

- Sold MSB for $2.28 (buy in 2.30, fuck it, wanted money fast),

- Sold TKL for 20c (buy in 23c, board spill, fuck it, wanted money fast)

Bought:

- ARV @ 13c (partial order filled [7K out of 13K], ended day 14.5c, looks like it's opening at 15c)
- A bottle of vodka and some kahlua to make white russians,
- Chips and gravy (priceless).</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Gooseburger1" created="2021-01-06 09:23:32+10:00">
  <body>I'm getting an erection just watching VUL from the sidelines.

Why didn't I buy in when I thought of doing it at 2.130, ah wait thats right, I'm autistic. 

Eagerly awaiting an eventual pullback before I FOMO in.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 09:32:00+10:00">
   <body>VUL going hard, oh why didn't I buy weeks ago....</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 09:26:59+10:00">
   <body>Only a 30 odd percent gain hop on when the dip.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="WasteMorning" created="2021-01-06 11:04:06+10:00">
   <body>I got on at 2.45.

VUL is the only company where I look at it and think to myself.. wow. This is going to seriously change the way we look at lithium extraction. It’s such a smart idea. If anyone hasn’t done a little digging into the company yet just look at the last AGM presentation. 

It’s frothy as fuck right now.. been on big gains since Monday so waiting on a temp pullback makes sense. But looking long term on this company if the site takes off in Europe it’s going to be a game changer.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Gooseburger1" created="2021-01-06 11:38:28+10:00">
    <body>My original plan this time around was wait till 2.30 but I think I might need to bump that up to 2.5-6 mark, yolo'ing into stocks coming off or at an ATH seem to be my downfall so trying to correct that habit.

Agreed though, long term I don't see any reason why this won't continue to accumulate multiple bags so getting in at any point may not be such a bad idea.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="chillinintheburn" created="2021-01-06 16:46:53+10:00">
  <body>Made $6.50 today. 6 pack of mcnuggets on me, I'll cut them up so we can all share.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="SocialSelfSabotage" created="2021-01-05 18:21:23+10:00">
  <body>I could buy any stock on the ASX but I just keep buying more Z1P. I need help</body>
  <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-01-05 18:36:43+10:00">
   <body>Why are you selfharming. You need a counsellor.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="jolebu" created="2021-01-05 19:51:24+10:00">
   <body>Z1P to $10 by Christmas 2021</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="kris_s14" created="2021-01-05 22:27:46+10:00">
  <body>Sold $27k worth of VGS and $5k worth of VGE today after the ex dividend date. Topping up my AfterPay, Polynovo and HACK holdings tomorrow. Pissing off my weak performers and going balls deep on the all stars. Also going to add some VUL to the mix.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 01:55:34+10:00">
   <body>Sold TKL, MSB and DRE today and dumped it into ARV @ 13c

Working out alright so far considering it's now 14.5c.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:35:38+10:00">
   <body>Pnv still a buy even after its big run?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kris_s14" created="2021-01-06 08:26:01+10:00">
    <body>I believe they are. They have recently added more countries in the last few months where their patented products will be used.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="wolololololololo" created="2021-01-06 08:42:34+10:00">
  <body>TSLA hits 750 in after hours trading on Morgan Stanley upgrade. That is a 25% loss on ataly's latest short position. Hope you're transferring to puts, bro.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-01-06 09:01:33+10:00">
   <body>TSLA is like bitcoin. No one cares what it's worth now, they just want to buy some and keep it for 5 years.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 09:26:31+10:00">
   <body>I'm actually preparing to short TSLA along side u/atayls timing is everything, waiting for the other car makers to start announcing EVs. It'll also make for a great hedge against an overall market dump which will come at some point this year</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-01-06 09:29:28+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I think we will be sweet in the long run, it’s just managing the volatility until it blows. 

But I expect to make at least 50x once it blows.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 09:52:33+10:00">
     <body>You using CFD? I've opened an IG account you reckon I should be using that or something on tastyworks?</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-01-06 09:56:10+10:00">
      <body>Yes sir. I’m not familiar with Tastyworks sorry mate.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 09:56:59+10:00">
       <body>Tastyworks have options and futures contracts. I haven't completed my account set-up yet to look through it because I'm lazy</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-01-06 09:57:57+10:00">
        <body>Yeah I’ve heard of them but haven’t used the platform myself.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="wolololololololo" created="2021-01-06 09:38:22+10:00">
    <body>I think it will eventually be a short, but maybe in like 5 years tbh. All depends on the execution of their other tech (FSD, energy, etc).</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 09:53:35+10:00">
     <body>The world is moving faster then you think, expect almost every car maker to release EVs this year</body>
     <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="wolololololololo" created="2021-01-06 09:59:03+10:00">
      <body>They all suck shit.</body>
      <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 10:02:48+10:00">
       <body>People buy porche 4WD's, I don't see your point people always buy shit. The better product means nothing. i.e I have a friend who is loyal to his power company even though he doesn't get the best deal as if the power company cares about him. 🤷‍♂️</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="wolololololololo" created="2021-01-06 10:06:04+10:00">
        <body>Yeah fair, I'd say more importantly its more the fact that Tesla will still be able to sell everything they produce because of the huge transition to EV's globally. Government policies and dropping cost of owning an EV will make more people transfer, so global market share will increase. 

Existing carmakers will probably just end up eating into their existing old combustion engine sales, rather than eating into the Tesla cult.</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 10:08:36+10:00">
         <body>That could be right, also keep in mind the US carmakers pay Tesla for carbon credits. That may kinda balance things out for them.</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AdditionalLawyers" created="2021-01-06 11:07:59+10:00">
    <body>You have to promise to show loss porn when it fails</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ramzataztaz" created="2021-01-06 11:12:09+10:00">
     <body>I promise to show any major losses I have. Luckily for me I use stops and know never to take a loss that's bigger then it needs to be.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-01-06 09:31:06+10:00">
   <body>I will be adding a put but I’m OK with the short at present. I’m still in holiday mode right now and will be until after my Bub comes later this month. So I probably won’t be able to do a deep dive into a put strategy until then.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="wolololololololo" created="2021-01-10 04:19:08+10:00">
    <body>880 on Friday. So you ignored your latest stop? I don't really get why you do this to yourself.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-01-10 07:13:49+10:00">
     <body>Haha I don’t “ignore” stops. Stop either get hit or gapped up/down and missed.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="wolololololololo" created="2021-01-10 23:49:53+10:00">
      <body>Cool, you gonna retry at 1000 I assume?</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="atayls" created="2021-01-11 05:55:41+10:00">
       <body>Nah whatever I can get on at come Tuesday.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="nizz94" created="2021-01-06 09:34:43+10:00">
  <body>SBW took a bigger dump then me post coffee and KFC</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ken_oath_cunce" created="2021-01-06 10:57:42+10:00">
   <body>or the impending dunny destroying torrent post-dinner of butter chicken and tikka masala, washed down with a litre of mango lassi.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="AdditionalLawyers" created="2021-01-06 11:04:42+10:00">
  <body>US has good day = ASX goes down. US has bad day = ASX goes down</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-01-06 17:58:42+10:00">
   <body>Yeah im over this shit lol</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-01-06 14:35:38+10:00">
  <body>Sitting around holding my dick all day trying to decide what to buy, but the market &amp; my portfolio has been all over the shop.

Jump aboard the uranium &amp; renewables bandwagon? Top up my red good performers? Grab some AVA while it's red?

But I'll continue hesitating until 4pm without doing anything because I'm an indecisive bitch and then no doubt regret it tomorrow</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DarceDarceRevolution" created="2021-01-06 14:42:36+10:00">
   <body>are you me?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-06 14:47:30+10:00">
    <body>I may also be guilty of this</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:48:29+10:00">
   <body>That's pretty stingy man. You could have at least flipped a few stocks just for brokerage. Those brokers gotta eat too.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="miggymaestro" created="2021-01-06 14:52:49+10:00">
   <body>Me aswell lol</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-05 19:29:33+10:00">
  <body>AFL - I posted a DD today but there's some fact checking I need to do. But put it on your watchlist and in 3 weeks, pat me on the back. 


9SP and AV1 - have half a mind to consolidate it all into these two. But too attached to the others. But I think about this daily.


ANP - can someone do TA on this? I feel like it's ready for 15c+


IHL - I'll take that green.


CDT - T2 play at 1c for it to go 10% down on open. I'm good at trading.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="landrarebothbad" created="2021-01-05 21:16:10+10:00">
   <body>Where’s the DD?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-05 21:41:02+10:00">
    <body>Gotta check some facts and redo</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="NocturneHS" created="2021-01-05 22:52:35+10:00">
     <body>Re: AFL - Ahem, can also check out my DD here: [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX\_Bets/comments/jtuede/time\_for\_some\_good\_oldfashioned\_dd\_af\_legal/](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/jtuede/time_for_some_good_oldfashioned_dd_af_legal/)</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-05 23:05:50+10:00">
      <body>Ah shit, forgot to mention this! Mine was more about why to expect rockets in a few weeks. Yours is why it's a long hold.</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="NocturneHS" created="2021-01-06 08:52:53+10:00">
       <body>Haha yeah I unashamedly do boring DD, you're the hype man!</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-06 09:46:21+10:00">
        <body>Yea but you're who we all should aspire to be. I'm a bit clueless so I need to add flavour.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="zxblood123" created="2021-01-06 10:56:40+10:00">
       <body>any DD yet?</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-06 13:54:58+10:00">
        <body>Haven't had time to cross reference but it's up 12% today. So dunno if it's worth doing anymore.</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="zxblood123" created="2021-01-06 20:45:05+10:00">
         <body>yes it is, worthy to see :)</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="username-taken82" created="2021-01-05 23:44:10+10:00">
      <body>I remember this post, was a good write up.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:41:16+10:00">
   <body>Whats your thoughts on whats going on with AV1? Struggle town on the surface....</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-06 10:02:03+10:00">
    <body>Saw broker data showing Wilsons bought 500k shares at 19c recently so I'm trying to figure out what to sell so I can load up.

The struggle is from impatient retail sellers I think. Just my guess.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="blahyadablahyada" created="2021-01-05 19:56:27+10:00">
   <body>Not liking HT8 anymore?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ricklepicklemydickle" created="2021-01-05 19:59:12+10:00">
    <body>Never had it. But heard good things (In this thread).</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="cheyaboi" created="2021-01-05 21:51:07+10:00">
  <body>Last chance to jump on board the NVA train, results this month will tip it over 🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-01-06 00:25:52+10:00">
   <body>Back into 20s soon</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 10:15:41+10:00">
   <body>I removed NVA from my watchlist yesterday on under performance relative to the market. It has years of work ahead of it so it is a long term hold.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-01-06 07:04:47+10:00">
  <body>Check out the volume on RMX 😮🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 07:30:46+10:00">
   <body>Again?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 07:34:25+10:00">
    <body>Where do you find the volume before market opens? Is it in the buy sell area in comsec</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-01-06 07:58:23+10:00">
     <body>You find it in the depth tab and it gives you the volume and price</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 08:22:20+10:00">
      <body>Thankyou</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nimrod123" created="2021-01-06 11:22:26+10:00">
   <body>i sold yesterday at .016... not feeling very smart</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-05 18:05:37+10:00">
  <body>Any reason AR9 up 14% today?</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-01-05 18:47:45+10:00">
   <body>Don't question, just enjoy</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="StonksHodler" created="2021-01-05 19:17:44+10:00">
    <body>This is the way</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Scrofl" created="2021-01-05 20:27:23+10:00">
   <body>And of course I sold out of it last week...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ada-95" created="2021-01-05 20:27:47+10:00">
   <body>Maybe same reason RHY is roaring.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-01-05 22:23:37+10:00">
  <body>Fuck it... I'm selling alll my BRN and getting more WBT</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-01-06 07:18:19+10:00">
   <body>Shit yeah, it's only gone \~900% since September, great idea</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Calculated-Punt" created="2021-01-06 01:23:29+10:00">
   <body>This is the way</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-01-06 03:26:19+10:00">
    <body>How much more do you think WBT can run?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pandibabi" created="2021-01-06 10:24:32+10:00">
     <body>Beyond the solar system</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="cossy10" created="2021-01-06 06:45:34+10:00">
  <body>TNT still a buy or should I wait for a pullback? Thoughts feelings comments pls</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="cheyaboi" created="2021-01-06 06:55:50+10:00">
   <body>Still a buy. Cyber security market only increasing in 2021, and TNT have the Aus Gov contracts which means a lot in terms of demonstrated capability and risk management.</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 08:40:55+10:00">
    <body>Was just wondering if HACK holds TNT - they do not... Hmmm

https://www.betashares.com.au/fund/global-cybersecurity-etf/#holdings</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="uaremumgei" created="2021-01-06 07:49:41+10:00">
   <body>TNT the most solid company in my portfolio. Great management and fundamentals. 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-01-06 08:36:53+10:00">
   <body>Devil's advocate. Not a buy, diluting the fuck out of shareholders at this point with not a whole lot to show for it as a ~$300M MC company. Y'all getting tripped up by how they peddle revenue run rate.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cossy10" created="2021-01-06 09:18:16+10:00">
   <body>Thanks for the advice legends</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-01-06 09:12:30+10:00">
  <body>CXO up 15% this morning.

Regret not getting on, heard several people call that. Lithium stocks just booming</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:10:27+10:00">
  <body>Uranium Bull Gang where you at? 🚀 🚀 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Gooseburger1" created="2021-01-06 13:23:52+10:00">
   <body>PEN up 13% is offseting the potential softening of my erection from AVA going red again.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-01-06 14:27:54+10:00">
  <body>Politics update:

Looks like the Dems have Georgia, lots of atlanta votes yet to be tallied and big city = blue votes. If Dems win both, then the US Senate will be 50/50 split between both parties and the Vice President is able to cast tie-breaking votes on senate matters. As a result, Democrats have the presidency, house and senate and will instantly give $2k stimulus out and work on passing their green(er) policy platform.

&amp;nbsp;

Fingers crossed for green dildo days this week</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-01-06 17:44:27+10:00">
   <body>[Decision Desk HQ has now called it. Dems to take control of the senate.](https://twitter.com/DecisionDeskHQ/status/1346717051314966528)</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-01-06 15:58:42+10:00">
   <body>Next few days is going to be interesting. 

Large bump for renewables and CBD/THC products and an absolute toddler style meltdown from Trump and his supporters would be a great way to wrap up the week.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-01-06 16:59:00+10:00">
    <body>I'm living for all the trump snowflake meltdowns</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="tao_of_bacon" created="2021-01-06 16:33:00+10:00">
   <body>Puts on Tiki Torches</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="AdditionalLawyers" created="2021-01-06 09:27:55+10:00">
  <body>Doesn't Warren Buffet know that it is impossible to beat VDHG?</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="9OOdollarydoos" created="2021-01-06 09:40:37+10:00">
   <body>Trust me, I can lose more than -0.14 today</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Crumpy88" created="2021-01-06 10:26:08+10:00">
  <body>I’m up $6k this year already. 

All I’ve done is sit at home playing monster hunter. 

I still can’t kill Alatreon. Been on this fucker for 3 days</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-06 11:29:36+10:00">
  <body>AVA - 700,000 shares at 55c, good risk / reward from here</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="NocturneHS" created="2021-01-06 13:53:34+10:00">
   <body>Do you think it's low risk/high reward? What's your target price? IMO it's more low-risk, low reward (not a bad thing, I'm just not expecting to multi-bag within 12 months).</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-06 14:36:42+10:00">
    <body>Yea agreed, more of a low risk / low reward. Something that I am happy to put 20k in and hold for a few months. The chances are they will have continued growth.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Affectionate-Ad2294" created="2021-01-05 19:44:58+10:00">
  <body>IHL 🚀🚀🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-05 20:14:37+10:00">
  <body>Oh CLT and HT8 / These are the stocks which I rate</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Nsj_1" created="2021-01-05 22:01:54+10:00">
  <body>Buying lithium for NIO day on the 9th :D</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="NocturneHS" created="2021-01-05 22:56:36+10:00">
  <body>CI1 is my next play gang, I'll be posting a DD tomorrow so watch this space. In the meantime, might fuck around and buy more HT8.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-01-06 00:14:43+10:00">
   <body>The way you say CI1 have my attention. Is this going to be a play along the story of oz economy going to have a dip soon? If so, what about a combination of CI1 CCR CCP CBA &amp; CASH?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="NocturneHS" created="2021-01-06 08:56:54+10:00">
    <body>I'll post it this arvo when I get home, but yes COVID repercussions can only be positive for them. No jobs = more insolvency, the kind of money you feel a bit icky about making.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="-2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:08:36+10:00">
    <body>HT8 is rubbish - but good luck!</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-01-06 02:11:46+10:00">
     <body>I didn't mention HT8 m8</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:30:44+10:00">
      <body>Sorry, I'm drunk lol</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="NonUser73" created="2021-01-06 06:56:46+10:00">
       <body>This is the way</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="NocturneHS" created="2021-01-06 08:58:09+10:00">
     <body>Thank you sir, I am currently up 40% and agree that's rubbish - should be 200%!!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 09:43:36+10:00">
  <body>Proof that even a retard can make money in a bull market. RHY. 

[https://imgur.com/jNLn8F6](https://imgur.com/jNLn8F6)</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 09:50:57+10:00">
   <body>Well played</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Ad4nothing" created="2021-01-06 10:14:34+10:00">
  <body>VR1 run up beginning again as expected. Going to continue to rise until the much anticipated revenue is announced. imo if you aren’t in it for the long term sell before the revenue announcements</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-01-06 10:40:07+10:00">
   <body>I'm in it and have been for a while but you're saying the revenue announcements will be disappointing?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Ad4nothing" created="2021-01-06 10:49:52+10:00">
    <body>I hope not and I don’t believe they will but it’s always the same story with revenue. [Silicon Valley Russ Hanneman] (https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=BzAdXyPYKQo)</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-01-06 10:59:31+10:00">
     <body>lol after watching the video, all makes sense now.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Ad4nothing" created="2021-01-06 11:03:17+10:00">
      <body>I got in very early so can take profits at anytime but I think we are one big announcement away from ath :)</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Dangerman1967" created="2021-01-06 10:37:59+10:00">
  <body>As one of about three LOT holders on this sub I’m 50% in 4 months or so. 

Giddy the fuck up!</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="fatmeatychudd" created="2021-01-06 10:40:47+10:00">
   <body>Gonna be my first double bagger :)</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Dangerman1967" created="2021-01-06 11:13:06+10:00">
    <body>Got way more to go imo. That’s news that had a few weeks back about extra sites very nearby their main mine didn’t budge them. 

I’m no expert bug basically suggested they’ve got lots more good grade uranium. 

And I accidentally doubled my buy coz didn’t think the first order filled!!!</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="fatmeatychudd" created="2021-01-06 11:19:18+10:00">
     <body>Yeah couldn't agree more. Gonna do the same  at some point this month. My stiffy won't go away</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Dangerman1967" created="2021-01-06 11:23:32+10:00">
      <body>Lol. Yep! Same. And at my age it’s not as easy lol.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 11:48:14+10:00">
     <body>Nice. One of my best trades ever was an accidental double buy.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-06 10:42:52+10:00">
    <body>Is it too late to get on?</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="fatmeatychudd" created="2021-01-06 10:47:01+10:00">
     <body>I'd say no, uranium is just getting started. A pullback is coming soon so jump in on that</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-06 11:58:56+10:00">
  <body>Can anyone get around this paywall and list the tickers mentioned? Last year Meilin Chew put me onto WOA which has gone on to be my biggest gainer.

https://thewest.com.au/business/startup/the-wa-start-ups-to-watch-in-2021-ng-b881741373z</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Frozen-Idjit" created="2021-01-06 16:16:40+10:00">
   <body>https://u.teknik.io/YoU5J.jpg
Is this what you were after?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-06 17:05:56+10:00">
    <body>Nice! Thanks. For those wondering, the companies mentioned are Functionally, LiveMine, Switch Batteries, Climate Clever, KIXXFIT, and Litt. 

None are on the ASX though I don't think.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 14:25:48+10:00">
   <body>You know that articles like that (and every article) is to steer some of the sheep, right? Read it, use it to understand how the herd is steered but don't believe it. They get you believing these are the best stocks ever and once you believe, you are more likely to hold a shit stock as it falls.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-06 14:38:23+10:00">
    <body>I just use them to learn about new stocks. WOA was the only one I went in last year from the article after doing further research. I'm up over 500% so I'm interested to see what they mention this year</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:57:34+10:00">
     <body>Fair enough - they will hit some good stocks from time to time, but it's all click bait to shift the herd.If you try to be a wolf and you watch from outside the herd, you can see it. Ask retail trader why they decided on a particular stock or sector. Then ask a trader on the desk at Morgan Stanley.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-06 12:02:19+10:00">
  <body>Caught bagholding RMX at 2.2c, I feel like an idiot</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-01-06 12:59:39+10:00">
   <body>Plenty of announcements in the next few weeks. Hopefully that gives it more momentum.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-01-06 13:07:49+10:00">
   <body>Dude fomo much?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-06 13:10:24+10:00">
    <body>100%</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="1kurousagi" created="2021-01-06 15:53:05+10:00">
   <body>Average it down. Plenty Ann in the coming week</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-06 16:09:01+10:00">
    <body>I have no doubt they’ve already been priced in. Fuck it, I have 2k in yolo</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="mechengguy93" created="2021-01-06 12:36:51+10:00">
   <body>Heaps more to go man!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 13:09:44+10:00">
  <body>Dems got this, time to pump renewables. Green Revolution incoming hard</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nikoel" created="2021-01-06 13:43:17+10:00">
   <body>Agreed. 2k stim checks? Yes please! We got an other pump on our hands

What other stonks should we be looking at?</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:45:12+10:00">
    <body>[deleted]</body>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 13:53:35+10:00">
     <body>Most of the remaining votes to be democrats, bookmark it. Few journos calling it already.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Residual_spark" created="2021-01-06 13:58:39+10:00">
      <body>where?</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 13:59:06+10:00">
       <body>What do you mean where? Most of Atlanta has not been counted.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Reggie_Wilde" created="2021-01-06 13:35:29+10:00">
  <body>HT8 on sale 👀</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mercuryingatoraade" created="2021-01-06 13:47:39+10:00">
   <body>Yeah wtf</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Reggie_Wilde" created="2021-01-06 15:06:56+10:00">
    <body>Time to average down</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="t20joel" created="2021-01-06 16:15:08+10:00">
     <body>Anyone topping up</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 14:38:31+10:00">
  <body>Lithium stocks up. PLS has broken up thru $1 level. GXY going vertical. Other smaller companies in the sector moving higher. For those ready to FOMO in, maybe buy half now and half on any pull back?</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="CaseExtension2609" created="2021-01-06 14:41:43+10:00">
   <body>What’re your thoughts on PLS? Got in at 0.40c not sure whether to hold or sell.</body>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="tokenofficeblackguy" created="2021-01-06 14:48:12+10:00">
    <body>Hold any lithium, and buy any extra you can. 60x current LI production output needed by 2060. Zero cars sold in Europe after 2025 that are petrol/diesel.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:45:50+10:00">
     <body>Yep, listen to this. You are on a great stock with heaps of liquidity that is on an uptrend after years of hard slog. Should be way easier from here for tendies. If you really gotta sell (because you hate money) don't sell them all or you will be another one of those - "I sold at $1 and now it's XXX$$"</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CaseExtension2609" created="2021-01-06 16:07:20+10:00">
      <body>Very true. Will probably buy more and go for the long term. See what happens</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-01-06 15:57:47+10:00">
     <body>You do realise lithium won't be used in EV batteries before too long. Have a look at Toyota solid state battery compared to Tesla's Lithium battery.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tokenofficeblackguy" created="2021-01-06 16:07:04+10:00">
      <body>lol, yeh they "potentially might have a prototype by mid 2021". Global LI investment @ 2019 was 109Bil, id say it would be double that now, if not more. Solid states maybe a thing in 5-10 years, but the economics and scale of li-batteries are tried and tested and already competitive in pricing for BEVs sales.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 16:54:54+10:00">
      <body>Until the day comes where a new technology is not only invented but also taken up by battery producers in the form of re tooling their entire production lines, LiPO4 batteries are here to stay. Like NiMH batteries and Alkaline and Lead acid, they will be around for a while yet.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-01-06 16:58:28+10:00">
       <body>Isn't that what solid state is though new technology and it's being implemented in the Toyota lines. 
Anyways I still hold some lithium INR but it's always good to look at both sides so far the solid state looks like it will out perform Lithium but we shall see.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 16:02:09+10:00">
    <body>The company looks like its in with a good chance to be the global lithium major out of australia , if it looks juicy at 40c with a world class resource than its extra juicy with 2 right next door to eachother at 1.00</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-05 18:01:08+10:00">
  <body>Potential RMX entry tomorrow after their answered speeding ticket, we have until the 12th to sell the rumour lads.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="imiweli" created="2021-01-05 18:06:39+10:00">
   <body>Seemed like the insiders started buying up with results out next week.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-01-05 18:51:03+10:00">
    <body>That's illegal</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mechengguy93" created="2021-01-05 19:21:59+10:00">
     <body>When has that stopped people before?</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-01-05 21:33:20+10:00">
     <body>So is nose beer. Wa-hey! 🥴</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BatFluReturns" created="2021-01-05 21:35:53+10:00">
     <body>Not if you're already rich it's not</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-01-05 18:22:46+10:00">
   <body>up over 54% just today..... time to enter bit late or nah?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jobanbeugs" created="2021-01-05 18:26:59+10:00">
    <body>That’s what I’m trying to work out, have come to this forum for confirmation bias</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-01-05 19:25:17+10:00">
     <body>Take this or leave it but people have lined up to sell the news so although you may think you’re now gonna get in to do the same the risk is now greatly increased. As for the “leaky ship” claims that’s not how smart insiders do things. Insiders already hold and they drive down share prices to scare you off before announcements. The last time this thing announced gold results it started at 015 before the trading halt and due to dilution and pretty shit results only went a couple pips to 017.   Youre now experiencing fomo.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="mechengguy93" created="2021-01-05 19:21:41+10:00">
     <body>It is not too late comrade</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="DontExpectmuchxD" created="2021-01-05 18:21:06+10:00">
  <body>Imagine not owning wbt haha</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="hairoidz" created="2021-01-05 18:57:50+10:00">
   <body>Man, gotta love weebit. Makes this investing seem easy. Starting investing 3 months ago and am up 60% overall. Exciting times ahead.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-01-05 18:26:12+10:00">
   <body>Laugh now cry later</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DontExpectmuchxD" created="2021-01-05 18:29:01+10:00">
    <body>my average is $1 so i won't complin if it drops, 5 year hold anyways</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hairoidz" created="2021-01-05 18:58:51+10:00">
     <body>You'll be sweet mate. 5 years that $1 will be worth a hundy</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Louis989" created="2021-01-05 18:58:21+10:00">
  <body>What do you guys see in Bph? I see massive potential in this year. Jump on before too late.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mercuryingatoraade" created="2021-01-05 19:47:08+10:00">
  <body>Is it too late for WBT? I just feel so left out.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Scrofl" created="2021-01-05 20:34:30+10:00">
   <body>don't fomo brah. if you're set on buying WBT, maybe wait for a bit of a pullback before you buy.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hairoidz" created="2021-01-05 22:04:57+10:00">
    <body>A positive announcement on a Fab deal will send this past $5 overnight. Limited time offer imo</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:00:12+10:00">
     <body>Dream on dreamer (disc: held)</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mercuryingatoraade" created="2021-01-05 20:39:05+10:00">
    <body>I’m keen as a bean. Will keep watching though, cheers!</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Calculated-Punt" created="2021-01-06 01:25:48+10:00">
     <body>Buy half tomorrow or this week to appease the fomo the  buy half if there is an opportunity of a pullback</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Qambi1" created="2021-01-05 19:59:10+10:00">
   <body>IMO - long term no but it had a strong run recently so would probably wait for a pullback</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="hairoidz" created="2021-01-05 22:03:02+10:00">
   <body>WBT is just getting started. I plan on holding until the SP blasts through the $100. This is a unicorn 🦄 operated by a superstar team 🤩</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="landrarebothbad" created="2021-01-05 21:14:27+10:00">
   <body>I’m probably gonna sell my remaining tomorrow</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="theoriginaluser01" created="2021-01-05 20:30:43+10:00">
  <body>Buying some more PBH tomorrow so I can gamble while I gamble.

Side note can you legends also please take three seconds to upvote my submissions [here](https://woobox.com/sxjxok/gallery/Hjgy3BjIDY4), [here](https://woobox.com/sxjxok/gallery/Gb54_i8z1OA) and [here](https://woobox.com/sxjxok/gallery/eWUNTeQsn_s) for memes I've submitted to ASX_Bets this year. Cheers cunts!</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Guy-Incogneto" created="2021-01-05 20:56:43+10:00">
   <body>Solid memes 👍</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-01-05 21:31:40+10:00">
   <body>Billy Maddison one has me howling</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-01-05 21:34:43+10:00">
  <body>My meme stonks kept my portfolio green 🤣</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="kinky-penguin" created="2021-01-05 22:26:29+10:00">
  <body>i was thinking about getting back into AVA but i just don’t think it’s going anywhere anytime soon. might bounce around 50-70c for a year unless they have a good amount of news

gotten myself into explorative mining stocks... 

PLY pulled back at last today

fuck z1p

still think APT could crack $150, just coz

hoping for some good publicity around PFT. they’ve got solid products, could be a company that just gobbles up other companies to make an empire. idk, but i reckon this ones a good longer term play. looking at WOA and MBH potentially but there’s probably more value just putting money in PFT anyway


looking forward to dw8’s christmas results</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-01-06 02:16:44+10:00">
   <body>AVA next quarterly result releasing within a month.

In their latest annual report, they mentioned an expected payment from the Aus DoD for a contract of $3.4mil by H1FY21.

Expected $2.6mil of payment made by IMOD by Q2FY21</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="WingsAndRuin001" created="2021-01-06 06:35:04+10:00">
   <body>Late last year MC said he wanted PFT be making around $500,000,000 revenue within 3-5 years. Should he successfully pull that off, it would make the SP around $20 (assuming no CR which I don't think there will be because they still have 2.5 mil from the IPO money left). 

Also, looking at the numbers of how many hot chickens are sold, if they sold 1/10 of the potato and gravy with every hot chicken, that alone would double their revenue currently. 

I'm very bullish on PFT and I can't wait to see their Annual Report this year with their audited numbers.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-01-05 22:55:02+10:00">
   <body>AVA is like an ETF in my eyes (safe bet) , you won't lose if buying in at the current prices . Should jump back to its former glory soon . I'll be happy at 70c</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="kinky-penguin" created="2021-01-05 23:04:30+10:00">
    <body>yeah absolutely. their financials are pretty sexy as is, just no pizazz at the moment</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-01-05 23:14:52+10:00">
     <body>I feel ya</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:37:11+10:00">
     <body>Its sexy but no pizazz? High standards! 😂</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Zomg_ks" created="2021-01-06 06:27:07+10:00">
   <body>I'm buying more pft and dw8 myself so reassuring to hear pengu prophet thinking along the same lines</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-05 23:24:52+10:00">
   <body>I have PFT and WOA. I love both companies and think they both have solid management. But I agree they are a similar bet.</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 01:56:35+10:00">
    <body>Sell PFT.</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="PimentoSandwich" created="2021-01-06 02:26:39+10:00">
     <body>I might sell purely based on the fact that they put sultanas in their curried potatoes.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:39:44+10:00">
      <body>Do you like sultanas in your curried potatoes? Neither do I. 

Worst case PFT get REMOVED from (WW) shelves. True possibility.

I sold (@ 1.34), do what you want.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 10:10:24+10:00">
     <body>If PFT breaks below $1 again, then it could test support at 60c. I hope holders have some sort of stop in place. Resistance is around $1.20 so risk/reward is poor. What is it with food brands? Better off owning the supermarket/trading woollies.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 10:19:15+10:00">
   <body>WOA and PLY - no liquidity</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-01-05 22:42:18+10:00">
  <body>Gonna feed the asx pokie machine another 100 pineapples tomorrow and go hunting for a lithium feature. 

Looking for the following entry’s before the end of the week:

CXO - 0.18
LTR - 0.39
PLS - 0.86</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="tokenofficeblackguy" created="2021-01-06 07:34:41+10:00">
  <body>Hope everyone is noticing the shift and higher frequency of posting about Lithium stocks. The cycle is just starting its 3rd wave. Global X LIT ETF was up 7% overnight...AVZ, get on board!</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 11:02:12+10:00">
   <body>Damm, I keep forgetting to add LIT to my overseas watch list and go long. Lithium, Rare earths, Uranium, metals/miners. The expected infrastructure builds and global changes about to start, as Gov's start paying attention to Global Waffle and saving the environment, should mean commodity super cycle narrative will build. Buying any dips on good companies in these spaces will do well. A lot of dog shit will rise too.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-01-06 07:53:32+10:00">
   <body>Big couple of weeks ahead for weed and renewables if Dems look close to winning the Georgia run off and Biden inauguration!</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mercuryingatoraade" created="2021-01-06 10:03:43+10:00">
    <body>I’ve been thinking about this for a while... would you go CAN or THC? Any others?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Softpilloww" created="2021-01-06 07:57:31+10:00">
  <body>RNX volume tho..</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mightyminers" created="2021-01-06 16:30:49+10:00">
   <body>Today and Yesterday...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 09:26:27+10:00">
  <body>Just bought 10,000 AVZ</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 09:33:29+10:00">
   <body>Mining in the democratic republic of Congo? What could possibly go wrong? Good luck tho!</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 09:44:04+10:00">
    <body>Give me that lithium baby.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tokenofficeblackguy" created="2021-01-06 10:07:10+10:00">
     <body>Holding 1mil+ units. I couldnt be anymore bullish on this stock!! Largest and best Li resource in the world cant be denied. Youll do well holding this!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tokenofficeblackguy" created="2021-01-06 10:08:32+10:00">
    <body>If its good enough for Glencore and Ivanhoe, its good enough for me!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="GeoSciFi" created="2021-01-06 10:45:22+10:00">
    <body>exactly...</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Justlookingforadate" created="2021-01-06 09:39:25+10:00">
  <body>My brother in law told me to put money on RHY last month when it was at 40 cents. Eating my dick now.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 09:39:25+10:00">
  <body>WBT at 3.08? Only bought it on Monday for 2.58,  lol.

Go you good thing!</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Pandibabi" created="2021-01-06 10:37:18+10:00">
   <body>$3.17 crazy mofo</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mercuryingatoraade" created="2021-01-06 10:04:53+10:00">
  <body>Holy CXO 🔥 burning brighter than a fucking Tesla battery fire</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Technology-Alarmed" created="2021-01-06 10:14:41+10:00">
   <body>Bought 25000 units just now. Dont let me down</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="DizzyPerception" created="2021-01-06 10:12:37+10:00">
  <body>SOR and RMX</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-01-06 10:31:08+10:00">
  <body>DW8 is breaking out, the options can only hold it down for so long.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-01-05 18:18:33+10:00">
  <body>HT8 🚀🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="DesperateSwimming9" created="2021-01-05 19:14:34+10:00">
   <body>I’m ready.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-01-05 21:46:36+10:00">
   <body>When Suge?! When!!!!!! Ive been waiting!!!!111oneeleven</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-01-05 21:52:36+10:00">
    <body>Soon my friend , very soon</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="gusssssy" created="2021-01-05 19:31:27+10:00">
  <body>Get on CXO ASAP, it’s going to explode</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tokenofficeblackguy" created="2021-01-05 19:45:35+10:00">
   <body>TBH most lithium is about to explode.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-05 19:39:39+10:00">
   <body>I've had a mate harping on about it for atleast a year and i just ignored him. Even up to a few weeks ago... It's gonna rocket i think, but i feel like I've missed the biggest chunk of gain so I'll be on the sidelines cheering it on.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gusssssy" created="2021-01-08 20:36:04+10:00">
    <body>Same with me. He got on at something silly, like 0.03. My average is about 0.08 I think</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SnooJokes9630" created="2021-01-05 20:14:54+10:00">
  <body>how high do we think CXO is going?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="krank2862" created="2021-01-05 20:46:35+10:00">
   <body>Debating about jumping on too?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SnooJokes9630" created="2021-01-05 21:10:05+10:00">
    <body>in and excited</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 02:05:59+10:00">
  <body>IBX plans:
For the day    : Tease up 0.5c. end the day flat.
For tomorrow: Tease up 0.5c. end the day flat.
All week         : Tease up 0.5c. end the day flat.
All next week  :Tease up 0.5c. end the day flat.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="kinky-penguin" created="2021-01-06 09:08:05+10:00">
  <body>rmx and dw8 may just have another run</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="GL1001" created="2021-01-06 09:36:58+10:00">
   <body>RMX volume looks good. Getting in now before it moons</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Arbitation" created="2021-01-06 09:37:37+10:00">
   <body>rmx was my 'throw 1k at a mining spec to see how it feels' intro to pennies. It's interesting watching it go from .11 to .19 like hurdles in a race. I also have no idea what to make of it... The volume traded last 24h is just insane.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Nocashgang" created="2021-01-06 09:36:52+10:00">
  <body>sneaky punt on SOR this morning in at 35c i'm hard  


edit: flaccid</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-01-06 10:31:02+10:00">
   <body>After yesterday, this will go backwards until the next announcement.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Nocashgang" created="2021-01-06 10:39:35+10:00">
    <body>Should've taken profit, sometimes you just get caught watching it go up ended up selling for a small loss</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="prestiCH" created="2021-01-06 12:02:45+10:00">
  <body>Hedging my portfolio by betting on the Democrats.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="nikoel" created="2021-01-06 14:36:19+10:00">
   <body>Hedging is for hogs

Balls to the wall; here we come!!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-01-06 12:24:21+10:00">
  <body>Really strong morning but heaps of red now. People reckon it's because of the runoffs? What's the theory that big money is shifting out of existing stock and into renewables?</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-01-06 12:26:32+10:00">
   <body>A blue sweep seems likely. Dems are pro renewables, weed, green energy, etc.

That's probably the gambit going on right now.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="hades086" created="2021-01-06 12:28:46+10:00">
    <body>Loeffer/Warnock looks like it'll go right down to the wire. Wouldn't bank on it deciding the market yet.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-01-06 12:41:59+10:00">
     <body>You're right but I didn't say I'm invested in that way. Just that a lot of people are making the blue sweep gamble based on Georgia results previously.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rexpimpwagen" created="2021-01-06 13:05:03+10:00">
     <body>Was watching destiny's stream says its basicly impossible for a republican win at this point.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Snck_Pck" created="2021-01-06 13:11:40+10:00">
  <body>FFX couldn't wait until payday tomorrow  &gt;=[</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="9OOdollarydoos" created="2021-01-06 14:39:13+10:00">
  <body>WBT starting to feel a little like BRN. +50% in one week is huge</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="hairoidz" created="2021-01-08 06:52:35+10:00">
   <body>The big difference is the have the bod to execute and grow exponentially.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 14:52:06+10:00">
  <body>Dems in the lead so lets all long:
yellow rock
Lithium
Nuclear 
Fngu because why the fuck not

In LTR PLS WCN PEKOC LYC TSO RVR BMN 
Thinking of playing ASN and FFX</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:42:21+10:00">
   <body>Don't do ASN without DD - If at all. ANything in that 1st group is way better.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 15:47:47+10:00">
    <body>been doing some looking , the company has a great gold project near chalice and a lithium brine play in the U.S along with a U308 resource thats under permitting review . However i cant pull the trigger for some reason. do  you have any idea on the company?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:51:16+10:00">
     <body>I held it from 7c to 31c a few years back when the last Lithium rush was on. Since then, they have fallen to 2c ish levels where most Lifestyle companies end up. They don't have enough Lithium and now they are also on the U308 band wagon? ROFLMAO.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 15:55:39+10:00">
      <body>Super helpful thanks . i was thinking about moving down to a more leveraged play than ltr but havent found any that really substantial resources or in solid jurisdictions</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-01-06 15:56:43+10:00">
   <body>Which Uranium stock is the most closely tied to the US market? PEN?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 16:00:40+10:00">
    <body>URA uranium trust . 

then you can move down the leverage curve to Cameco or any of the TSX listed mines  in Australia theres a basket between BMN LOT BOE DYL and others . 

Theres that uranium guy hanging around here if you want proper info</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-01-06 17:00:40+10:00">
     <body>Awesome - cheers for the info mate.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tao_of_bacon" created="2021-01-06 16:28:13+10:00">
    <body>On the ASX it's **PEN or** maybe Laramide LAM which operates in Canada and Aus but I don't know if they're dual listed because LAM has like no liquidity.

On NYSE I like **URNM** which is an ETF with a couple dozen U miners in Canada, US and Australia incl. PEN LOT DYL etc. [https://urnmetf.com/urnm](https://urnmetf.com/urnm)</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="flatman_88" created="2021-01-06 17:01:01+10:00">
     <body>Super - cheers mate!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 14:52:46+10:00">
  <body>AfterPay dip ~4.6% could be ripe for a bit of T+2 action. In for $10K at $113.52. Anything $116-ish tomoz appreciated 👍😁</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 14:58:34+10:00">
   <body>Good luck bro</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="scyllallycs" created="2021-01-06 15:19:03+10:00">
   <body>Not bad. Daily equilibrium. Daily support at 109.53. Hourly touched oversold this morning, first time since the last move up- usually good for a bounce. Hourly support at 112.07. GLTAH</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-01-06 16:38:37+10:00">
  <body>AFL up 18% today. Whoever dropped that DD recently well done! Hope you whacked it</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="bigfootbjornsen56" created="2021-01-05 18:28:40+10:00">
  <body>Got a buy order at 0.105 for CLT, but I doubt it will get filled. Caught in the grips of FOMO</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="PleasantBirthdays" created="2021-01-05 18:45:20+10:00">
  <body>If you want to lose money, just go to ausfinance and ask them for financial advice.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Hasra23" created="2021-01-05 18:50:00+10:00">
  <body>It's JXTs day tomorrow I can feel it</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Hasra23" created="2021-01-06 13:33:44+10:00">
   <body>Dammit JXT just another day of disappointment and wasted potential, now I know how my parents feel.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-05 20:37:49+10:00">
   <body>JXT order book is too spooky for me</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SerbianWolf1389" created="2021-01-05 19:50:07+10:00">
  <body>Who else is enjoying the quiet WCG rocket</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Arbitation" created="2021-01-05 20:54:04+10:00">
  <body>Got snaggas from TLT's run to throw at GNX. Anyone else looking to pump hydro to the moon?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:38:51+10:00">
   <body>Yeah, waiting for cash to clear. Was looking at it last month but everything of mine was red and didnt feel like liquidating.  Storage is the future of the aussie grid (actually, every grid)!</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Arbitation" created="2021-01-06 09:47:11+10:00">
    <body>Yeah lots of talk of renewable + storage. Not really new tech but seems like there's plenty of appetite for it. Hopefully their projects don't shit the bed lol</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 11:53:35+10:00">
     <body>Not new tech, but increasing renewables on the grid are making storage so much more important</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-01-05 22:54:46+10:00">
  <body>However is pumping 4DS, what’s the play with it? Holding until someone tries to take over? Are they just going to constantly CR to invest in R&amp;D? Sounds like a gamble</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="derroleekd" created="2021-01-05 22:59:53+10:00">
   <body>If you've got paper hands, sell off when she hits 20-30cents.


Most holders are waiting for the acquisition mid-late 2021. HC predicted price is &gt;=60c, but personally I'm holding out for that $4.


The consensus is they've brought in some cunt who's good with wrapping paper and ribbons to get 4ds ready for a buyer, so they really shouldn't need to cap raise anymore... as long as shit gets finalised this year.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 07:11:17+10:00">
  <body>Too late for VUL or she got legs???</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:33:44+10:00">
   <body>Pfs in 2-4 weeks! If its good 🚀🚀🚀🚀

But yeah, bit of a gamble in the short term. Long terms, if they can truly be the first emissions free lithium source in europe, they will be worth shedloads.

Maybe just dip ya toe in?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 07:34:28+10:00">
    <body>Yeah considering buying a few thousand initially.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Esquatcho_Mundo" created="2021-01-06 07:51:55+10:00">
     <body>Always a good idea. Was a big day today. Imo coin flip if it pushes further or if we see a minipullback</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cheyaboi" created="2021-01-06 08:16:59+10:00">
      <body>I want the pullback selfishly just to double down.
As mentioned above, if they pull it off they will be bathing in gold scrooge mcduck style</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-01-06 07:19:23+10:00">
  <body>Market open yet???</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AgnosticIce6482" created="2021-01-06 07:25:39+10:00">
  <body>SOR up 50% yesterday. In my opinion, I expect it to get to at least 45c (maybe 50c, but that’s pushing it) by the end of week, then will start dipping come Friday afternoon/Monday morning</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ASXg0d" created="2021-01-06 10:22:38+10:00">
  <body>The ETF ASIA with 50 big Asian tech companies (ex Jap) is up 4% today, 62% in a year, 135% in 2y. 
Nice play.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 10:44:25+10:00">
   <body>Up 11% since October. Not bad for one of my safer plays. Can see it only continuing upwards.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 10:23:51+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mRPerfect12" created="2021-01-06 10:48:22+10:00">
   <body>&gt;CXO

Think VUL will keep going.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:13:03+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:17:58+10:00">
   <body>/r/ausfinance 

Cuck house is that way</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:19:49+10:00">
    <body>[deleted]</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:21:44+10:00">
     <body>This year since March has been insane for meme stocks, I think there's gonna be a lot of learning the hard way in 2021 though</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Scomosbuttpirate" created="2021-01-06 14:05:00+10:00">
      <body>I already learned a lesson in Nov/Dec last year I'm sick of learning lessons</body>
      <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 14:08:01+10:00">
       <body>Lesson #1: Everyone is a genius in a bull market

Lesson #2: When the tide goes out you find out who's been swimming naked</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 16:57:32+10:00">
   <body>100% invested in VDHG? What have those r/ausfinance smooth brains done to you?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="sneakpeekbot" created="2021-01-06 16:57:50+10:00">
    <body>Here's a sneak peek of /r/AusFinance using the [top posts](https://np.reddit.com/r/AusFinance/top/?sort=top&amp;t=year) of the year!

\#1: [I just hit 5 digits in savings for the first time in my life](https://np.reddit.com/r/AusFinance/comments/igqass/i_just_hit_5_digits_in_savings_for_the_first_time/)  
\#2: [Almost went bankrupt building my first house. sharing the lessons learnt](https://np.reddit.com/r/AusFinance/comments/iuu7bu/almost_went_bankrupt_building_my_first_house/)  
\#3: [I recently started searching for my first home and holy hell it must be one of the most frustrating unfair purchases I have planned in my life, lets start with Agents listing huge inflated prices during good times and almost the entire REA/DOMAIN listings now being "Price on request"](https://np.reddit.com/r/AusFinance/comments/hhr8d0/i_recently_started_searching_for_my_first_home/)

----
^^I'm ^^a ^^bot, ^^beep ^^boop ^^| ^^Downvote ^^to ^^remove ^^| [^^Contact ^^me](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose/?to=sneakpeekbot) ^^| [^^Info](https://np.reddit.com/r/sneakpeekbot/) ^^| [^^Opt-out](https://np.reddit.com/r/sneakpeekbot/comments/joo7mb/blacklist_viii/)</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="HailTheOgreLord" created="2021-01-06 13:40:03+10:00">
  <body>Buy in price for SYA on Friday?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="prestiCH" created="2021-01-06 15:13:10+10:00">
  <body>Dems = TSLA TSLA TSLA</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="t20joel" created="2021-01-06 15:52:21+10:00">
  <body>Ht8 is on sale</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="DesperateSwimming9" created="2021-01-06 16:18:50+10:00">
   <body>Permanently on sale like zip</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="telf24" created="2021-01-06 16:29:50+10:00">
    <body>🌈🐻</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SerbianWolf1389" created="2021-01-06 16:42:40+10:00">
  <body>Just quietly enjoying my 38% gains on my WCG holding, after already taking a profit on its last run, and re-entering at 41 cents</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="GeologyGang" created="2021-01-06 16:49:33+10:00">
  <body>Ty VUL baby 🤑

Also there's been a surprising amount of green tickers and 🚀's here recently. Y'all keep making that money 🙏

Seriously, there's been a shocking amount of good DD here. This could be the top</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-01-05 18:52:05+10:00">
  <body>DRX chugging along nicely. Bought a lil bit of ANP see where that takes me</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="too_many_wines_" created="2021-01-05 19:35:00+10:00">
   <body>Nice, same here for both.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-01-05 19:43:16+10:00">
    <body>Nice one! Still trying to understand ANP, Bio scares the fuck outta me</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="too_many_wines_" created="2021-01-05 20:10:56+10:00">
     <body>Yeah I'm probably least familiar with this area but I'm giving it a go. I started reading about ANP shortly before xmas when it first hit 15c. Seems like there's lots of interest in it so I thought I'd jump in.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-01-05 20:31:49+10:00">
      <body>Yeah I've seen it floating around the threads. A lot interest! Would be amazing if it worked out for everyone!</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-05 20:37:20+10:00">
   <body>DRX is heading back to 1.6c-1.8c. Unless an offscreen buyer wipes over 4million shares at 2c. I think it is fair value at these levels. Keep in mind at 8c this will have a similar to MC of VRX trading at 40c lol. 

ANP looks likes a solid pick short term</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-01-05 20:42:29+10:00">
    <body>Yeah man it’s hard to watch VRX rocket everyday Hahaha shits gone up like 50% since I bought DRX fuck me right hahaha</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Marvo13" created="2021-01-05 18:59:50+10:00">
  <body>SOR just got a speeding ticket. Will retrace after a 50% gain today! Should watch it closely!</body>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="w-j1m" created="2021-01-05 21:54:01+10:00">
   <body>Still fucking crying over my soggy tissue paper handed sor trade (buy $15k @ 12c sold at 14c)</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Rum-Ham-Jabroni" created="2021-01-06 06:27:30+10:00">
    <body>You and me both</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="San_Marzano" created="2021-01-05 19:15:59+10:00">
  <body>Another great day for CDX 😍 this feels too good to be true though</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-05 19:52:16+10:00">
  <body>I'm out of ideas lads and ladettes. What should my next bet be?</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="blahyadablahyada" created="2021-01-05 19:55:58+10:00">
   <body>IHL. Dyor etc etc</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Exalted_HC" created="2021-01-05 21:05:47+10:00">
    <body>Name checks out.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nikoel" created="2021-01-05 20:03:33+10:00">
  <body>My portfolio looks way more green than it deserves to be

Got out of MEM at 25% yesterday when I got in at .10 last week. Caught the knife with a 23 day at limit order. Patience and resistance lines are a wonderful thing 

Got out of Nova with 10%

Got out of Nitro with 3%

Went into BPH already up

Went into LRSOC already up

Best invalid paper gains are from DDDOA. A cool 50% from a retard who went in at market and got what they deserved. Funny thing is that my order at 0.002 is half filled so if it goes down I will be the one who ends up buying them</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-01-06 09:15:17+10:00">
  <body>rip when commsec keeps cancelling my rmxoi buys. im too retarded to even know why</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 09:45:07+10:00">
   <body>Are you allowed to trade options? You have to click a box somewhere?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-01-06 10:01:43+10:00">
    <body>idk i tried from my options account and margin loan to no avail.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-01-06 09:53:40+10:00">
  <body>Hold a small $500 parcel of SWF. Trying not to rage trade it this morning purely on the basis it takes way too long for funds to land in my SelfWealth trading account. So many missed gains</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="NonUser73" created="2021-01-06 11:30:33+10:00">
  <body>DSK up again</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="NotTheTomatoHead" created="2021-01-06 12:18:32+10:00">
   <body>Easy 12% in a few days</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Noideasx" created="2021-01-06 13:10:02+10:00">
  <body>Waiting on AR9 💩</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:14:53+10:00">
   <body>I find your lack of faith in TNT disturbing</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Noideasx" created="2021-01-06 13:16:17+10:00">
    <body>😅😅</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 13:19:37+10:00">
     <body>TBH I can't talk too much shit, I went 50/50 into VOR and TNT five months ago, up 95% on TNT and down 40% because I bought the fucking top on VOR just before they decided they'd rather be an Indian ATM company than a cybersecurity one</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Noideasx" created="2021-01-06 13:23:38+10:00">
      <body>I’m the king of buy high sell low</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Noideasx" created="2021-01-06 13:23:08+10:00">
      <body>impatience got the best of me. Minimal profit. Should of held but ugh, it’s always a “should of” moment for me haha</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="twoweekoldbread" created="2021-01-05 18:52:50+10:00">
  <body>I'm late to the BRN train, should I buy now or gamble for it to drop back down around .45? New to all this bullshit.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="AdditionalLawyers" created="2021-01-05 18:59:24+10:00">
   <body>The gamble is in putting your money in this dog shit stock at all</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Jbent09" created="2021-01-05 21:44:23+10:00">
    <body>We will throw hands</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pleb617" created="2021-01-05 19:44:31+10:00">
    <body>Buying ATH is pretty dogshit.</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="nsjmas" created="2021-01-05 20:16:41+10:00">
     <body>Take it back</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Nsj_1" created="2021-01-05 22:03:24+10:00">
   <body>Dafuck it when back up to 46c? lol</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SouthWinter9462" created="2021-01-05 23:42:46+10:00">
   <body>I think if you do you dd and understand the tech then it is a good buy. Apparently there are supposed to be more deals in the pipeline for this quarter. If we do see more do these deals then expect to see a higher share price. If not then the share price should stay here or become a little cheaper. Today it went up a few percent so it may retrace back a little tomorrow. Don’t buy at open wait till around 12 - 2 pm tomorrow and then make a decision. Again I believe because of my independent research that it is a good stock especially because of the recent announcements.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Gooseburger1" created="2021-01-05 19:10:58+10:00">
   <body>I don't see a reason why it won't drop back to sub .40 given enough time unless they post more promising announcements.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="derverdwerb" created="2021-01-05 21:17:43+10:00">
  <body>MYD on the way up. The lowball sell orders are drying up and it’s had a few straight days of gains against the market while people wait for the market update after Christmas.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jazzladd" created="2021-01-05 21:31:01+10:00">
  <body>NTO 📈📈📈</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-01-05 22:00:35+10:00">
  <body>LTR is breaking new records. 

Starting 2021 with a proper bang!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Jezz0014k" created="2021-01-06 06:42:39+10:00">
  <body>I'm broke DO SOMETHING PFT AND CNEW AND QANNYTUS, SELL THOSE TICKETS AND NO REFUNDS TOO!</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ASXg0d" created="2021-01-06 07:08:11+10:00">
   <body>Tickets to the moon and no refund?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 09:55:34+10:00">
   <body>I have met a number of people over the last 6 months that have said they will fly any other airline than QAN after failing to give cash refunds on tickets that QAN cancelled. They offer credits on future tickets as their refund where they can get away with it. Then they jacked up prices to the hilt and slashed staff. I could go on. Any competition to QAN should do well when air travel is back up in a few years time. Alan Joyce is probably one of the best business operators in the world. Shrewd and merciless. Unfortunately, in a time like this, we needed compassion and support.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Jezz0014k" created="2021-01-06 11:32:40+10:00">
    <body>I read that as.

"I have murdered a number of people over the last 6 months" holy shit. DUDE YOU'RE RIGHT. YOU'RE RIGHT, JUST DON'T COME FOR ME, IT MAY NOT BE PERFECT BUT IT'S MY LIFE.

I don't know where you're at man. I hate Joyce too, literally hate the Leprechaun and his agendas but he has used the pandemic to gut Aussie workers, wages and hopefully lead to even more profitability in the future, which is all I care about for a share purchase.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 14:19:09+10:00">
     <body>Nah I got no hard feelings either way. Just calling it how I see it. AJ is good for QAN and shareholders.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Jezz0014k" created="2021-01-07 07:20:07+10:00">
      <body>Yep, but his a dog carnt of a human</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SpagOCE" created="2021-01-06 09:43:54+10:00">
  <body>If you’re looking for buying opportunities on a day like today you’re blessed for the opportunity to get in to TPW and RBL before they attempt ATHs.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="bigfootbjornsen56" created="2021-01-06 10:53:09+10:00">
  <body>i'm the numpty who sold KRM for 0.038 yesterday...</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="t20joel" created="2021-01-06 11:10:57+10:00">
  <body>Ava in the red again</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-06 13:56:53+10:00">
   <body>Red day generally means ava is red from what i've seen.

What is good though is the amount of buyers providing support at 55c with a thin sell side</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="prestiCH" created="2021-01-06 11:16:00+10:00">
  <body>Anyone else got a bet on Georgia run offs</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-01-06 11:25:24+10:00">
   <body>Damn, placing a bet didn't even come to mind. Bets on Ossoff and Warnock are free money after all the trump and Republican shenanigans.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Big-Charity4463" created="2021-01-06 11:47:49+10:00">
    <body>After they fucked everyone out of $2k it should have been a lock to go big on the Dems</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mike_hunt1986" created="2021-01-06 11:26:22+10:00">
  <body>STX about to releeeeeeeeease 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="RocketEmojis" created="2021-01-06 11:29:57+10:00">
   <body>I just bitched out of STX lmao, what a reversal from 2 days ago</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-06 14:51:37+10:00">
   <body>Broken resistance now. Lets see where it runs!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PleasantBirthdays" created="2021-01-06 11:29:27+10:00">
  <body>Ok we are going deep red because of the democrats looking like getting in</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-01-06 11:43:38+10:00">
   <body>Haven't US markets historically done better under democrat control in both house, senate and house and senate combined?

I dont really see how thats bad for us</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ken_oath_cunce" created="2021-01-06 11:50:41+10:00">
    <body>Democrats haven't typically been too business friendly with their policies, which the GOP is better known for being better bedpartners. Having control of both houses leaves the Dems open to pushing through their agenda unchecked.

Having a moderating force in the form of an opposition keeps the government of the day honest</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Big-Charity4463" created="2021-01-06 11:47:11+10:00">
    <body>The narrative was a Democrat house and president with a Republican senate was best, don't ask me why - All I know is this is good af for gold, Dems going to hit the money printer dial to 11</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ASXg0d" created="2021-01-06 11:56:09+10:00">
     <body>Because it blocks everything, no new law for 4 years. The expected stability gives confidence to the market.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-01-06 11:49:36+10:00">
     <body>Think youre right. Bought into GDX pretty hard the last few months. Its pre much just there as a hedge for the next month or two but i'll see how it goes</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="AdditionalLawyers" created="2021-01-06 11:52:22+10:00">
     <body>Yes because a gridlock senate means no controversial laws and tax changes can pass, if dems have free reign it will be a sh\*t show</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Drswing69" created="2021-01-06 11:47:30+10:00">
    <body>I think it's more about the tax reform for big companies that the democrats are likely to initiate - this should'nt impact our 'penny punt' stocks thought. Happy 🚀 hunting.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-01-06 11:47:43+10:00">
    <body>not 100% on the combined, for some reason i keep thinking its performed best on a split house/senate.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ASisko" created="2021-01-06 15:09:01+10:00">
   <body>I think we are red just because it is yet to be decided, people are 'risk off', the same thing happened prior to the presidential election.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="brewbenbrook" created="2021-01-06 13:41:50+10:00">
  <body>CDX Keeping my portfolio green in the green today</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kervio" created="2021-01-06 15:16:44+10:00">
  <body>In on RDH today... such an illiquid stock, I feel like I could personally shift the share price 5% and I'm no big boy with a big horse and fancy big boy boots!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:34:28+10:00">
  <body>BLY. Have a look at the chart. 1 yr and 5 yr. I will be on this tomorrow. They dropped 3rd qtr EBITDA 50% to $40Mill. MC is (was) $45Mill (now $60Mill after 30%+ rise today. No news the last 2 days but vol rocketed as has the share price. I haven't checked HC yet to see if it's just all HC smooth brained retard action, but even if this is the case, looks tradeable.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Green-Paramedic1266" created="2021-01-06 15:45:41+10:00">
   <body>all in on borat</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 15:52:01+10:00">
    <body>That does it. Borat to the moon.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="doubleknavery" created="2021-01-07 10:44:41+10:00">
   <body>Holy shit - it's up 36% today... mods, does this deserve flair</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-07 18:34:36+10:00">
    <body>It went past any price I thought it could reach (89c). Had an afternoon breakout and closed up 50%+. After all that, I got no idea anymore.It was an easy call at 69c.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Super_Fisherman" created="2021-01-06 15:49:06+10:00">
  <body>Oil was juicy today, STO and OSH among many others doing well from Saudi cuts.  Crystal was to take out US Shale then pump prices, vaccine is a handy bonus.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="KebAb4TW" created="2021-01-06 17:12:33+10:00">
  <body>I fucking sold LPD two weeks ago fuck my fucking life.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="megadrive65" created="2021-01-06 17:21:57+10:00">
  <body>Mexican greyhounds bringing me tendies this week!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="prestiCH" created="2021-01-06 17:54:10+10:00">
  <body>Sportsbet hurry the fuck up and pay warnock</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="destined2bepoor" created="2021-01-06 09:39:26+10:00">
  <body>Everything is GREEN!!! Except banks it seems.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="t20joel" created="2021-01-06 16:03:47+10:00">
   <body>And fucken Ava</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Understandinganxious" created="2021-01-06 11:17:24+10:00">
  <body>what do people think about $FEX?</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 11:35:42+10:00">
   <body>Nice DD. Close to production of high grade iron ore. Small output/scale but should be very profitable at current iron ore prices. Has finally broken out of sideways range today. Lots of people will be flipping it for pips but it's probably a solid hold until I/O prices shit the bed which could be some time to come.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="VB_by_IV" created="2021-01-06 13:59:26+10:00">
  <body>Weighing up an entry point for NXT, likelihood it will dip below $11?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-01-06 17:01:13+10:00">
  <body>Anyone gonna make the obligatory BTC remark?  New ATH bitches!!! Even with a mooning AUD!!</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 18:01:24+10:00">
   <body>Crypto is a different strain of autism than the one we're cultivating here</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="Xenphenik" created="2021-01-06 10:54:51+10:00">
  <body>Dsiclosure: I am a holder of WBT.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-01-06 11:04:52+10:00">
   <body>Is this the new "oh btw I'm vegan" of ASX bets?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-01-06 11:14:46+10:00">
   <body>WBT is the new BRN</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-10" downs="0" author="Jezz0014k" created="2021-01-06 07:58:02+10:00">
  <body>Morningstar's analysts just endorsed Qannytus! (QAN). Compared it to the 2001 situation after September 11 and said travel will rebound strongly.</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 08:19:46+10:00">
   <body>Dude don't trust them</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="nextFloat" created="2021-01-06 08:38:15+10:00">
    <body>Flights aint doing FK for at least another year. Might be a nice time to get into airports tho while they're smashed to shit - "Invest for the Future" bloke likes Auckland International Airport (ASX:AIA) and who am I to argue?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="DrizzyDradle" created="2021-01-06 08:45:31+10:00">
   <body>2001 downturn was based on consumer sentiment. People were scared to fly so they didn't. Eventually they got over their somewhat irrational fear and started flying again.

2020-21 downturn is based on international borders being closed and legal directives to quarantine for 2 weeks upon arriving in destination and returning home. Flying won't be feasible for most people until vaccine rollout achieves herd immunity in their own country + the country they want to fly to.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Jezz0014k" created="2021-01-06 11:34:23+10:00">
    <body>That's still only two years to hold, roaring 20s much? I meant I bought at $3.80 and sold off 5k profit and $5.60 or something when we were covid free.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-01-06 09:11:50+10:00">
   <body>We're only looking out for you. We're in this together 💪</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-01-06 08:29:40+10:00">
   <body>The only good news I see here is for FLT</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-01-06 08:40:33+10:00">
   <body>Even if there’s a rebound, travel is capital intensive and when you combine that with all the competition and lower margins it starts to make less sense. Better gamble is oil but you’ve missed that one</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Jezz0014k" created="2021-01-06 11:35:18+10:00">
    <body>I am in short term to make a buck. Already made some and want to ride the wave of whenever it happens for borders and travel reopen and that pent up demand.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-28" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-01-05 18:08:30+10:00">
  <body>JXT

Edit: keep down voting it worked today cucks</body>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
