<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-03-04 Thursday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>VML (13) HYPE=8</mention>
  <mention>NVA (8) HYPE=16</mention>
  <mention>TOP (7) HYPE=8</mention>
  <mention>IHL (7) GAMBLE=0</mention>
  <mention>IXR (7) HYPE=18</mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-03 18:47:39+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>I'm actually taking a very close look at ASB at the moment. Could be a good value medium term investment?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="cnik03" created="2021-03-03 17:39:13+10:00">
   <body>I'm surprised PDN doesn't get much attention here... one of my consistently green stocks</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 18:03:27+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>Its the boomer Uranium miner, much larger MC so presumably less rocket potential, has been a quiet performer for me too though.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-03-03 18:07:59+10:00">
    <body>I’m hearing there is a cap raise coming!</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 20:19:36+10:00">
     <body>I'll raise my hat to that!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:32:15+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
   <body>Great day with the VML, BRK and IXR trifecta. Took some profit and did some portfolio rebalancing and went on a shopping spree.

PLL &amp; RAC - broke almost every rule I have for myself buying these two. FOMO and YOLO wins in the end.

TNT, AVA, NVA - all look reasonably cheap to me. If not at the bottom, must be close to it.

4DS, IBX - don’t love these 2 as much as I did a few months ago but still like their story and look to be getting back in at a pretty good price.

CRO - not sure if I’m having a blonde moment here but currently 10% cheaper than recent CR price of 9c?? 🤔

SRK - 3rd time lucky. Will probably just hold this now unless it breaks support. Please don’t.

PEN - feels like I’ve been missing out on all the fun so bought my way into the PEN15 gang. Lubed up and ready to go.

VMS - one of my first babies, sitting at it’s CR price and theoretical bottom of 5.5c (recent low was 5.2c). Cashed up and then some. Not long until the wet screen plant is complete and first shipment.

A1G - an out and out gamble. Very curious spike and candle yesterday. Got my seat at the table, interested to see where it goes.

Feels like I’ve now got the ASX_Bets starter pack, albeit a year late.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-03 18:39:52+10:00">
    <body>Too many stocks don't you think? Each to their own but I feel like holding lots of stonks sorta negate each other.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 18:46:30+10:00">
     <body>I hold 25 🤷‍♂️</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:55:05+10:00">
      <body>Haha well there you go. I’ll ordinarily hold anywhere between 5-20 but currently sitting at around 20. Could end up at 10 tomorrow just as easily. I don’t get too attached to what I’m holding.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:46:07+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
     <body>Yes and no. I’m a bit of a hybrid swing trader/investor. Generally buy the swing lows and sell the highs, keep some skin in the game, so essentially free carrying a lot of the stuff I hold.

I only buy stuff I think is ready to be bought, not buying for the sake of buying (except with RAC and PLL lol).

It’s not for everyone but it forces me to take profit and helps reduce downside risk.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:25:07+10:00">
     <body>Seems to be true. I feel constantly neutral but if I look carefully it's pretty much everything is doing ok, and too much investment in XST is constantly killing me.

That and the resent pen massacre</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 19:01:40+10:00">
    <body>SRK is testing my patience, but I have ultimate faith in this one.

If you look closely into the ownership structure of the top shareholders (follow the rabbit hole) you will get a sense for what they’re trying to do here and how to ultimately extract true shareholder value...(hint - it’s not pip trading it!)

This is truely the only penny stock in my portfolio that I would be completely comfortable to close my eyes on and check it in 12 months time. And I never say that!!</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 19:07:20+10:00">
     <body>I haven’t looked into them in depth but your bullishness was what got me first interested. Did some digging and their story checks out. 

Undoubtedly a good long term play but I hate seeing red haha. I follow the ‘keep your losses small’ mantra so get myself out sometimes when I probably don’t need to. Has worked for me to date (more than it hasn’t I hope) but have no issues getting back into stocks and this was one I was always getting back into; SHE another but unfortunately it ran today 🤦‍♂️</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 19:12:03+10:00">
      <body>I’m lucky on SHE - I sat at the front of the buy queue at 1.9c for WEEKS...and just got filled for a big parcel on Monday.

Going to hold this one til 5c now</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 19:24:01+10:00">
       <body>Happy days I had it in my head it was going below 1.9 for some reason so wouldnt pull the trigger at 2c even though it was on offer many a time!</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 19:33:57+10:00">
        <body>Yeah, was super interesting trading today. I saw BRK do huge volume from open and hit new highs, so I knew SHE was going to follow. Could have line wiped 2.0c on open 

You get about a 4 minute glimpse into the future trading SHE...good tip for players!!</body>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 19:51:12+10:00">
         <body>Nice tip! I used to do that when I would day trade the big 4 banks which almost always follow each other’s lead.</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-03 19:41:49+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
     <body>I think if they go through with another CR I'll look at jumping in after that</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 20:00:05+10:00">
      <body>Yep, I’m sure they will do another CR pre-production to raise the capex for mine start. 

I’m obviously hoping they do it at a much higher level than where they’re currently sitting, and also they only need $15m to get up a cashflowing...so minimal dilution.

It ran pretty hard from their last raise of $4m at 10c, so they have track record of doing things tight👌</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Chief_wigam" created="2021-03-03 20:11:27+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
      <body>I think if they do another CR, I’ll look at jumping off the cliff</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-03 18:28:50+10:00">
   <body>Would be nice if EGR would stop sliding. Otherwise, enjoying my boomer stonk portfolio built with a core of RAC and orbited by DW8, BD1, AV1 and EGR.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="I_P_L" created="2021-03-03 18:33:30+10:00">
    <body>BD1 is bagheld as fuck now tho</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-03 18:42:27+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
     <body>I bought in at $1.37 and am free carrying now so I'm cool with that. The company has enormous potential!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-03 20:02:33+10:00">
    <body>Bagholding AV1 or feeling optimistic?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-03 20:13:53+10:00">
     <body>Bought in at .18 - so down a little change but not bag holding. It’s been hovering at that mark for a while now, but it’s only a couple of announced partners away from rocketing.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 17:06:01+10:00">
   <body>Eager to see why VML traded so highly today has to be some news surely.  2643 Trades/240 mil shares traded got to be a reason there me thinks.

As far as MC goes we are now on Par or slightly above other explorers.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="No-Knee-4576" created="2021-03-03 17:10:22+10:00">
    <body>Also looking forward to seeing how VML travel
Current position with them is 32% up
Keen to see them him 10 cents.</body>
    <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 17:11:56+10:00">
     <body>Double digits would be a dream this fast, I was expecting it to much much later in the year.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mobile-Rice-8889" created="2021-03-03 18:07:28+10:00">
      <body>Got an exit price or date in mind?</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:09:23+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
       <body>1st target 2025 then see how it's going and if positive 2030 is my exit time. Much longer than anyone here will look at.</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-03 18:19:45+10:00">
        <body>Dayuum! Diamond lord here, paper hand bitches take note 📝</body>
        <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:20:50+10:00">
         <body>I have enough shares to make me a multi millionaire so I have that to lean on haha.</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="No-Knee-4576" created="2021-03-03 18:28:00+10:00">
        <body>What would you expect the price this far out to be?
In line with a LYC ?
$6 bucks ?</body>
        <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:29:53+10:00">
         <body>By then lynas should be alot higher, if VML can get 3-4 bil MC by 2030 I'm happy with that. That's a good $1+ but I'm hoping for close to $2+ come 2030</body>
         <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="No-Knee-4576" created="2021-03-03 18:36:10+10:00">
          <body>Interesting thought. 
You just don’t know could be the next VUL
My mate brought at $0.40 then 6-8 months hit a max of $14.00
Currently about $6.50 high for a company that’s not in production.</body>
          <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:37:37+10:00">
           <body>It would need a share consolidation for that far too many on the registry. But it does have the chance of being a multi billion dollar company and that is enough for me.</body>
          </comment>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="35" downs="0" author="Rosencrantz1710" created="2021-03-03 18:44:28+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Hey I just wanted to give you madlads and lasses a shout-out just for sharing your knowledge and answering various silly questions. I haven’t asked too many myself but just in reading other discussions I’ve learned heaps. The ASX has gone from being something I understood at a basic level to something I now feel I have a more in-depth grasp of.

Thanks to you guys I now have just enough knowledge to do something truly dangerous! 😂 🚀 

But seriously - thanks!</body>
   <comment ups="46" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-03 18:49:55+10:00">
    <body>Sir, this is a yoghurt shop</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="AttitudeAlexander" created="2021-03-03 19:32:40+10:00">
     <body>Mango yoghurt with peanuts and whipped cream please</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 20:18:43+10:00">
    <body>Be free my child</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="31" downs="0" author="MichaelRogers5" created="2021-03-03 17:23:15+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>This 🚀place was a lot more fun when I was making bank 🏦. Now I’ve turned into those sad fucks waiting for meme stocks to rocket again.</body>
   <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-03-03 17:39:36+10:00">
    <body>This place was a lot more fun before we all started bagholding meme stonks.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 17:39:55+10:00">
    <body>Fucken amen to that brother</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Outside_Marionberry4" created="2021-03-03 19:04:03+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>I think market is breaking out of a downtrend tommorow or friday imo 🚀🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 19:19:28+10:00">
    <body>Probably break out tomorrow just in time for the usual Friday crash :P</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Wookiee81" created="2021-03-03 19:18:59+10:00">
    <body>Not now that you have said it out loud.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:19:21+10:00">
    <body>Do I smell hope?</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 20:29:33+10:00">
    <body>US futs are mega green. Looks like peeps are still BTFD's. Zig zag but trend is still up.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 18:14:02+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Gonna stick with my tried and proven commodity favourites - IXR, SHE, TMZ


Super excited to see what TMZ come out with tomorrow on the M&amp;A front, and also fully expect both SHE and IXR to carry on with today’s strength and volumes.

Honestly just loving the market right now 💕🚀</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:36:29+10:00">
    <body>Where do you place fair value for IXR based off today’s announcement? I was thinking 7c but way off the mark. I know there were a few short term holders waiting for this announcement but thought we’d finish a good amount higher.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 18:42:20+10:00">
     <body>I think the next couple days will see IXR establish value a fair bit higher than here. Going into a TH for announcement (rather than just releasing) caught a few T+2 traders off guard and they needed to bail today. 

IXR has never been a meme/rocket share, simply because it’s the real deal! Watch it over the next 3-4weeks, and I think your 7c target will look way too cheap 😉</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:53:00+10:00">
      <body>Good call regarding the T2 traders. I was expecting us to pump back past the open price but never happened. Guess some of the announcement was already priced in</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="k0tassium" created="2021-03-03 19:29:40+10:00">
       <body>The announcement was expected so I think it was priced in for the most part.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-03-03 20:09:15+10:00">
      <body>Checking in...  would consider going in again for long term but need some real $ !</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="chaddownunder_" created="2021-03-03 19:41:05+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>What do we reckon - has the RAC 🚀 launched or still time for me to load up on more tomorrow?</body>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="43" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 18:55:20+10:00">
  <body>I spoke to my bank teller today. Early 40's I think, Male. I went in to start on applying for a loan to buy a block of land coz all the mexicans have moved up here and bought nearly everything for sale in the last 6 months. He asked how much I had and why it's not all in cash in my account earning 0.1% interest. I told him it's all in the stockmarket. He asked if I had heard of GME:US!! Should have seen the look on his face when I told him I traded it twice for profit and gave what I made on the 2nd trade away to some rando on the net. Fuck I live for this shit. Told him I don't usually YOLO full retard but GME was free money and most of my cash is in FMG. The chick next to him wet herself. When I left, the entire branch looked like it was in a huddle. Going back next week to show them my 3219 trades for the last 12 months.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-03-03 19:38:51+10:00">
   <body>And then everyone clapped and the entire banking system collapsed?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="agree-with-you" created="2021-03-03 19:39:02+10:00">
    <body>Can confirm this is true. I was also applauding.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:41:26+10:00">
    <body>Profits up but they can only give savers 0.1%? Debt rulez.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 20:18:22+10:00">
    <body>Can confirm, I am Bear Sterns</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-03 19:28:40+10:00">
   <body>Nice</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="the_arkane_one" created="2021-03-03 19:39:26+10:00">
   <body>And then everyone clapped and cheered</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Voldemortina" created="2021-03-03 20:22:03+10:00">
    <body>And the bank teller? Obama.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="boy_pikoy" created="2021-03-03 19:38:18+10:00">
   <body>give this man a beer. 🍻🍺</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="41" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-03 17:22:06+10:00">
  <body>LRS better have an announcement tomorrow and rocket or else I'm going to get pissed off and do nothing.</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="cheebaihai" created="2021-03-03 17:57:43+10:00">
   <body>Alright tough guy, relax, we got kids over here man you’re scaring them off</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-03-03 18:01:48+10:00">
    <body>haha</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="35" downs="0" author="Rosencrantz1710" created="2021-03-03 18:44:28+10:00">
  <body>Hey I just wanted to give you madlads and lasses a shout-out just for sharing your knowledge and answering various silly questions. I haven’t asked too many myself but just in reading other discussions I’ve learned heaps. The ASX has gone from being something I understood at a basic level to something I now feel I have a more in-depth grasp of.

Thanks to you guys I now have just enough knowledge to do something truly dangerous! 😂 🚀 

But seriously - thanks!</body>
  <comment ups="46" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-03 18:49:55+10:00">
   <body>Sir, this is a yoghurt shop</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="AttitudeAlexander" created="2021-03-03 19:32:40+10:00">
    <body>Mango yoghurt with peanuts and whipped cream please</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 20:18:43+10:00">
   <body>Be free my child</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="31" downs="0" author="MichaelRogers5" created="2021-03-03 17:23:15+10:00">
  <body>This 🚀place was a lot more fun when I was making bank 🏦. Now I’ve turned into those sad fucks waiting for meme stocks to rocket again.</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-03-03 17:39:36+10:00">
   <body>This place was a lot more fun before we all started bagholding meme stonks.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Smokeybear1337" created="2021-03-03 17:57:25+10:00">
    <body>r/ASX_bagholders</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 17:39:55+10:00">
   <body>Fucken amen to that brother</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-03 18:08:19+10:00">
  <body>Working my raggedy arsehole raw and losing more money on the stock market each day then im making each month. 

This feels like March 2020 all over again... lol jokes I'm not 50% down and panic selling at the bottom.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Goody55" created="2021-03-03 18:38:12+10:00">
   <body>Im starting to grow fur and claws though...</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-03-03 18:44:11+10:00">
    <body>Fancy some salmon and honey?</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Goody55" created="2021-03-03 18:49:53+10:00">
     <body>Yolo PFT and MBH, got it</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="Moxanz2" created="2021-03-03 18:35:41+10:00">
  <body>Guys. The bankruptcy advice thread is trending in ausfinance. I think that advice will be very useful for most of us soon.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="glueckskind11" created="2021-03-03 19:11:20+10:00">
   <body>CI1 making a comeback then?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="85maveric" created="2021-03-03 17:18:00+10:00">
  <body>IOU better sort it's shit out tomorrow</body>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-03-03 18:47:26+10:00">
   <body>Seconded</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-03 19:51:49+10:00">
  <body>Watching ABC NEWS, some hot chick talking about Aus economy. And saying things are good, but my stocks are down, what gives?!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-03 17:15:15+10:00">
  <body>IOU please go up, I don't need this in my life right now.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="dhking71" created="2021-03-03 17:18:20+10:00">
   <body>I just bought another 1000 if that might make you feel better</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Hammer_1213" created="2021-03-03 18:14:49+10:00">
   <body>Yer I topped up today in the low 50s, moved my average up to about $0.38ish.
Turns out it could go lower then when I said to myself there's no way this could go any lower...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-03-03 18:40:52+10:00">
  <body>Can gold and silver fucking go the other way now? Meet me in the wildy ya dog</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-03 19:51:35+10:00">
   <body>I would prefer a tin shortage</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 20:03:11+10:00">
    <body>There’s already one of those.


TMZ for the win!! 🚀🚀</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-03 20:09:13+10:00">
     <body>I wish you a wonderful opening. SRZ/MLX plz</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="oldmanhocus" created="2021-03-03 18:18:27+10:00">
  <body>Gonna top up on NVA and IHL tomorrow. Otherwise I'll be watching my BD1 and LRS positions and seeing if IBG keeps a good thing going. AV1 can eat a bag of hell.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-03 18:44:19+10:00">
   <body>Had my order in for a top up on IHL at .19 but got unlucky didn't go through.

Lots of ifs and buts BUT, I think Av1 needs time as they are still in the early stages of making real money. They have an actual product and once companies are over the 'freemium' stage and become real customers (assuming they like what they see), we will see the SP actually move. An announcement about a partnership with google (soon) is on the cards too so that will be a good boost too.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cornpizza" created="2021-03-03 20:16:23+10:00">
   <body>I loaded up on NVA today.  It has the feeling it's about to go.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="I_P_L" created="2021-03-03 18:32:55+10:00">
  <body>Congratulations guys you're mainstream enough to infiltrate [my university lecture](https://i.imgur.com/nzcj5ax.png).</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Supraga70" created="2021-03-03 19:27:32+10:00">
  <body>LRS when lambo?</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:35:39+10:00">
   <body>Uhhh $3.80 for me... So.......

April?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 19:29:25+10:00">
  <body>https://www.euractiv.com/section/circular-economy/news/eu-plotting-ban-on-internal-combustion-engine-as-of-2025-industry/

Ah that escalated quickly it was meant to be by 2030.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:34:34+10:00">
   <body>Fuck off surely.. there goes my hopes for a zx14r revival</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-03 19:49:46+10:00">
    <body>They revived the busa so why not the zx14r .</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-03 19:51:10+10:00">
   <body>I got 4 years to make enough gainz to buy a proper lambo</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Ok-Penalty-7046" created="2021-03-03 19:53:54+10:00">
   <body>Guess that means EV related stocks must go up? Lithium?</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 19:54:34+10:00">
    <body>Lithium,RE,Cobalt( for now),Copper</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-03 19:33:33+10:00">
   <body>Huge.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 19:34:44+10:00">
    <body>Don't know how they can do it in 5 years honestly though its pretty big leap.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:50:25+10:00">
     <body>That was always happening. Aust is 20 years behind Europe. They just ban ICE and everyone gotta change over or conversion. It helps when the gov is actually willing to support EV industry. The oil industry is destroying the world and have fought every step of the way to stop change for decades. Hopefully they do the same with plastics. It is actually too little too late, but the boomers in charge will all be dead before it matters so - carry on.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 19:51:31+10:00">
      <body>From my reading by 2030 No more Combustion engines would be sold in Europe, this looks to bring it  further in by 5 years.

I know that cause 2030 was my exit time for VML when Europe went full EV.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:32:15+10:00">
  <body>Great day with the VML, BRK and IXR trifecta. Took some profit and did some portfolio rebalancing and went on a shopping spree.

PLL &amp; RAC - broke almost every rule I have for myself buying these two. FOMO and YOLO wins in the end.

TNT, AVA, NVA - all look reasonably cheap to me. If not at the bottom, must be close to it.

4DS, IBX - don’t love these 2 as much as I did a few months ago but still like their story and look to be getting back in at a pretty good price.

CRO - not sure if I’m having a blonde moment here but currently 10% cheaper than recent CR price of 9c?? 🤔

SRK - 3rd time lucky. Will probably just hold this now unless it breaks support. Please don’t.

PEN - feels like I’ve been missing out on all the fun so bought my way into the PEN15 gang. Lubed up and ready to go.

VMS - one of my first babies, sitting at it’s CR price and theoretical bottom of 5.5c (recent low was 5.2c). Cashed up and then some. Not long until the wet screen plant is complete and first shipment.

A1G - an out and out gamble. Very curious spike and candle yesterday. Got my seat at the table, interested to see where it goes.

Feels like I’ve now got the ASX_Bets starter pack, albeit a year late.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-03 18:39:52+10:00">
   <body>Too many stocks don't you think? Each to their own but I feel like holding lots of stonks sorta negate each other.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 18:46:30+10:00">
    <body>I hold 25 🤷‍♂️</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:55:05+10:00">
     <body>Haha well there you go. I’ll ordinarily hold anywhere between 5-20 but currently sitting at around 20. Could end up at 10 tomorrow just as easily. I don’t get too attached to what I’m holding.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:46:07+10:00">
    <body>Yes and no. I’m a bit of a hybrid swing trader/investor. Generally buy the swing lows and sell the highs, keep some skin in the game, so essentially free carrying a lot of the stuff I hold.

I only buy stuff I think is ready to be bought, not buying for the sake of buying (except with RAC and PLL lol).

It’s not for everyone but it forces me to take profit and helps reduce downside risk.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:25:07+10:00">
    <body>Seems to be true. I feel constantly neutral but if I look carefully it's pretty much everything is doing ok, and too much investment in XST is constantly killing me.

That and the resent pen massacre</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 19:01:40+10:00">
   <body>SRK is testing my patience, but I have ultimate faith in this one.

If you look closely into the ownership structure of the top shareholders (follow the rabbit hole) you will get a sense for what they’re trying to do here and how to ultimately extract true shareholder value...(hint - it’s not pip trading it!)

This is truely the only penny stock in my portfolio that I would be completely comfortable to close my eyes on and check it in 12 months time. And I never say that!!</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 19:07:20+10:00">
    <body>I haven’t looked into them in depth but your bullishness was what got me first interested. Did some digging and their story checks out. 

Undoubtedly a good long term play but I hate seeing red haha. I follow the ‘keep your losses small’ mantra so get myself out sometimes when I probably don’t need to. Has worked for me to date (more than it hasn’t I hope) but have no issues getting back into stocks and this was one I was always getting back into; SHE another but unfortunately it ran today 🤦‍♂️</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 19:12:03+10:00">
     <body>I’m lucky on SHE - I sat at the front of the buy queue at 1.9c for WEEKS...and just got filled for a big parcel on Monday.

Going to hold this one til 5c now</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 19:24:01+10:00">
      <body>Happy days I had it in my head it was going below 1.9 for some reason so wouldnt pull the trigger at 2c even though it was on offer many a time!</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 19:33:57+10:00">
       <body>Yeah, was super interesting trading today. I saw BRK do huge volume from open and hit new highs, so I knew SHE was going to follow. Could have line wiped 2.0c on open 

You get about a 4 minute glimpse into the future trading SHE...good tip for players!!</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 19:51:12+10:00">
        <body>Nice tip! I used to do that when I would day trade the big 4 banks which almost always follow each other’s lead.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-03 19:41:49+10:00">
    <body>I think if they go through with another CR I'll look at jumping in after that</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 20:00:05+10:00">
     <body>Yep, I’m sure they will do another CR pre-production to raise the capex for mine start. 

I’m obviously hoping they do it at a much higher level than where they’re currently sitting, and also they only need $15m to get up a cashflowing...so minimal dilution.

It ran pretty hard from their last raise of $4m at 10c, so they have track record of doing things tight👌</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Chief_wigam" created="2021-03-03 20:11:27+10:00">
     <body>I think if they do another CR, I’ll look at jumping off the cliff</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="k0tassium" created="2021-03-03 17:16:43+10:00">
  <body>Last week I chose IXR instead of VML kind of regretting it seeing how VML is taking off but I still think IXar is a good pick.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 17:18:02+10:00">
   <body>IXR is still a amazing pick. Loose that FOMO track and stick to ur guns, IXR had a monster upgrade today and don't be fooled it will run very hard soon.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="k0tassium" created="2021-03-03 17:20:02+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I know I'm not gonna sell IXR to fomo into something that's already gone up so much. Would have been nice to but VML then sell soon then buy IXR though lol.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 17:40:24+10:00">
   <body>Exactly this. Nearly picked up VML at 4.5c
Was hoping to buy into VML today at yesterday’s close, but got rekt</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-03 18:02:53+10:00">
   <body>you chose correct</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-03 18:04:45+10:00">
  <body>cause i'm T.N.T. i'm dynamite</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-03 18:05:30+10:00">
   <body>acdc not the etf the band if you did not get the reference</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-03 18:13:16+10:00">
   <body>TNT is terrible, such a shame! I thought I was onto a good thing as it went up.But now.!!! :(</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-03 18:17:16+10:00">
    <body>It'll be fine long term</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Quorts_" created="2021-03-03 18:28:11+10:00">
     <body>Yes I think it will rebound. I don’t think it’s going to go anywhere very quickly though.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-03 18:48:33+10:00">
     <body>How so? The lightning fast sell-off yesterday (or the day before?) wasn't a good sign, almost felt like someone knew something about the company that we don't yet.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-03 19:14:16+10:00">
      <body>Cybersecurity is going to be one of the largest growing industries in the future. TNT is well positioned to take advantage of large government and commercial contracts in the next few years. Just Google 'cyber hacks in australia' and you'll see why I'm not worried long term.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Forumbane" created="2021-03-03 18:19:34+10:00">
  <body>So never planned to swing trade but after riding a bunch of stocks up hard through Jan and back down through Feb I couldn't resist selling 2/3rds of my VML holdings at 7.9c today (bought at 3.2c).

Hoping I can get back in around low 6c but holding if it keeps going up I'll be fine with that too.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Android515" created="2021-03-03 18:26:10+10:00">
   <body>Nothing wrong with taking your earnings.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:37:13+10:00">
   <body>At these levels I think it’s a sound strategy. You smooth out those bumps doing that and that’s not a bad thing.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Church_of_FootStool" created="2021-03-03 18:51:28+10:00">
   <body>Grats on the win!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 17:06:01+10:00">
  <body>Eager to see why VML traded so highly today has to be some news surely.  2643 Trades/240 mil shares traded got to be a reason there me thinks.

As far as MC goes we are now on Par or slightly above other explorers.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="No-Knee-4576" created="2021-03-03 17:10:22+10:00">
   <body>Also looking forward to seeing how VML travel
Current position with them is 32% up
Keen to see them him 10 cents.</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 17:11:56+10:00">
    <body>Double digits would be a dream this fast, I was expecting it to much much later in the year.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mobile-Rice-8889" created="2021-03-03 18:07:28+10:00">
     <body>Got an exit price or date in mind?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:09:23+10:00">
      <body>1st target 2025 then see how it's going and if positive 2030 is my exit time. Much longer than anyone here will look at.</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-03 18:19:45+10:00">
       <body>Dayuum! Diamond lord here, paper hand bitches take note 📝</body>
       <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:20:50+10:00">
        <body>I have enough shares to make me a multi millionaire so I have that to lean on haha.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="No-Knee-4576" created="2021-03-03 18:28:00+10:00">
       <body>What would you expect the price this far out to be?
In line with a LYC ?
$6 bucks ?</body>
       <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:29:53+10:00">
        <body>By then lynas should be alot higher, if VML can get 3-4 bil MC by 2030 I'm happy with that. That's a good $1+ but I'm hoping for close to $2+ come 2030</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="No-Knee-4576" created="2021-03-03 18:36:10+10:00">
         <body>Interesting thought. 
You just don’t know could be the next VUL
My mate brought at $0.40 then 6-8 months hit a max of $14.00
Currently about $6.50 high for a company that’s not in production.</body>
         <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 18:37:37+10:00">
          <body>It would need a share consolidation for that far too many on the registry. But it does have the chance of being a multi billion dollar company and that is enough for me.</body>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="TheAscenseur" created="2021-03-03 17:13:30+10:00">
  <body>I know no one wants to talk about XST and SGC anymore, but do we have an estimated timeline on the next results? I assume mid-Q2</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Possible_Ice882" created="2021-03-03 17:18:43+10:00">
   <body>expect an update next week</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="bhavdabeast" created="2021-03-03 19:50:33+10:00">
    <body>yeah my guess is update in next 1-2 weeks should boost price to 17-18. But then again my diamond hands could be guessing wrong</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ecl_u" created="2021-03-03 19:02:20+10:00">
    <body>Can't wait</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Wookiee81" created="2021-03-03 19:22:52+10:00">
    <body>This will probably be a mention of cracking that first layer.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Goody55" created="2021-03-03 17:21:17+10:00">
   <body>They've been releasing updates almost weekly. Almost 2 weeks ago confirmed first well to be complete in 25-35 days. so could hear some more definitive news in 2-3 weeks</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-03-03 17:23:14+10:00">
  <body>Fuck sakes tnt</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="jordyyp" created="2021-03-03 17:35:58+10:00">
   <body>Being such a dog</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ken_oath_cunce" created="2021-03-03 18:26:29+10:00">
    <body>Fucken dog cunt</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-03 18:28:50+10:00">
  <body>Would be nice if EGR would stop sliding. Otherwise, enjoying my boomer stonk portfolio built with a core of RAC and orbited by DW8, BD1, AV1 and EGR.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="I_P_L" created="2021-03-03 18:33:30+10:00">
   <body>BD1 is bagheld as fuck now tho</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-03 18:42:27+10:00">
    <body>I bought in at $1.37 and am free carrying now so I'm cool with that. The company has enormous potential!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-03 20:02:33+10:00">
   <body>Bagholding AV1 or feeling optimistic?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-03-03 20:13:53+10:00">
    <body>Bought in at .18 - so down a little change but not bag holding. It’s been hovering at that mark for a while now, but it’s only a couple of announced partners away from rocketing.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Outside_Marionberry4" created="2021-03-03 19:04:03+10:00">
  <body>I think market is breaking out of a downtrend tommorow or friday imo 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 19:19:28+10:00">
   <body>Probably break out tomorrow just in time for the usual Friday crash :P</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Wookiee81" created="2021-03-03 19:18:59+10:00">
   <body>Not now that you have said it out loud.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:19:21+10:00">
   <body>Do I smell hope?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 20:29:33+10:00">
   <body>US futs are mega green. Looks like peeps are still BTFD's. Zig zag but trend is still up.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="cnik03" created="2021-03-03 17:39:13+10:00">
  <body>I'm surprised PDN doesn't get much attention here... one of my consistently green stocks</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 18:03:27+10:00">
   <body>Its the boomer Uranium miner, much larger MC so presumably less rocket potential, has been a quiet performer for me too though.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-03-03 18:07:59+10:00">
   <body>I’m hearing there is a cap raise coming!</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-03 20:19:36+10:00">
    <body>I'll raise my hat to that!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ilestMYRON" created="2021-03-03 19:45:56+10:00">
  <body>Stuck in a holding pattern currently but if PEN happens up, I'll take a quick win and then double down on IHL.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-03 19:48:53+10:00">
   <body>Had same thought but after the dive in IHL was kinda glad I tanked on uranium instead maybe I’m just a special type of autist</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-03 20:02:21+10:00">
  <body>I was looking to top up on PLL, VML and AIS but since they have all rocketed looks like I’ll have to settle for NVA, accumulate now and wait for the resource update 

Is it me or does it feel like it’s getting harder to find viable rockets and not just piece of shit dog stocks?</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 20:15:49+10:00">
   <body>I'd be careful with NVA. If it had legs, it should have bounced off 14.5c weeks ago. Viable stocks are going up. Plenty of stocks are better than NVA.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-03-03 20:19:46+10:00">
    <body>Yeah that’s been playing on my mind, volume was very low today</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-03 20:03:31+10:00">
  <body>How much longer will I be “Pen”Ed down . I only got that much cash to average down with. May the gods look kindly on my pen. 

IBX looking like some accumulation happening . 

Wbt looking like it’s found at least a temporary resistance 

Will see weather or not NXT solidifies at the 11$ resistance for re entry or weather it shits it’s pants further 

Goodday lads</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="CJghetto" created="2021-03-03 20:06:34+10:00">
  <body>If TNT ends green tomorrow, i'll buy myself a burrito. That's a bet.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Hypertrollz" created="2021-03-03 20:18:40+10:00">
   <body>Sounds like a plan!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kooksy_monster" created="2021-03-03 20:23:33+10:00">
   <body>I'll complete the prophecy and go get some nachos. Porque no los dos?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="is2017goingtobebad" created="2021-03-03 17:27:21+10:00">
  <body>Minutes silence for VR1 . Went from promising to now under 10c.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SouthWinter9462" created="2021-03-03 17:30:45+10:00">
   <body>:(</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Pristine_Willow6173" created="2021-03-03 18:22:31+10:00">
    <body>I believe people here when they say vr1 is a shit company but there were also a lot writing off nvx under a dollar too</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:20:43+10:00">
     <body>Even shit companies can rise in a bull market. Wait till the bear market. It will go back to being priced at what it is worth.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pristine_Willow6173" created="2021-03-03 19:31:05+10:00">
      <body>Yeh true. Mainly thanks to some info from this place i only took a small loss on my third trade from them. Still made a dollar so im happy.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:39:17+10:00">
       <body>The BOD are making the real money on this one.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-03 17:57:55+10:00">
   <body>It’s run up entirely on pump announcements since September. Eventually they have to produce results ie contracts and cash. “Partnerships” and “MOUs” won’t support a $100M market cap. I’m surprised it’s lasted this long but then I guess the latest financial report revealed how little progress they have made.

Never mind the EM1 links - bad vibes.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:18:49+10:00">
   <body>It's dog shit - I keep saying so and I will never stop.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-03-03 20:11:26+10:00">
   <body>I’m bag holding this piece of shit long-term. They’ll either strike it lucky, or I’ll lose it all. I’m half way there now, what’s a bit more rough sex.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 18:14:02+10:00">
  <body>Gonna stick with my tried and proven commodity favourites - IXR, SHE, TMZ


Super excited to see what TMZ come out with tomorrow on the M&amp;A front, and also fully expect both SHE and IXR to carry on with today’s strength and volumes.

Honestly just loving the market right now 💕🚀</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:36:29+10:00">
   <body>Where do you place fair value for IXR based off today’s announcement? I was thinking 7c but way off the mark. I know there were a few short term holders waiting for this announcement but thought we’d finish a good amount higher.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-03 18:42:20+10:00">
    <body>I think the next couple days will see IXR establish value a fair bit higher than here. Going into a TH for announcement (rather than just releasing) caught a few T+2 traders off guard and they needed to bail today. 

IXR has never been a meme/rocket share, simply because it’s the real deal! Watch it over the next 3-4weeks, and I think your 7c target will look way too cheap 😉</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-03 18:53:00+10:00">
     <body>Good call regarding the T2 traders. I was expecting us to pump back past the open price but never happened. Guess some of the announcement was already priced in</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="k0tassium" created="2021-03-03 19:29:40+10:00">
      <body>The announcement was expected so I think it was priced in for the most part.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-03-03 20:09:15+10:00">
     <body>Checking in...  would consider going in again for long term but need some real $ !</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Salty-Ant-8567" created="2021-03-03 18:24:12+10:00">
  <body>My ASX\_Bets portfolio result today: -$1,271.45 (-3.72%). Green: LRS, RAC, WWG, Z1P. Red: IOU, IBG, LKE.  LKE, my heaviest investment ($16k), held the fort yesterday, sank the portfolio today with  -$1,025.88.  
Overall, still confident with the portfolio for a hold till Easter (LKE minimum 8-12 months, they seem poised for a slow but steady advance).  
 IBG is the only stock I bought purely based on rockets seen in posts (for the rest I did click on links people provided in comments and looked at the company websites - what a deep DD, I know). Is IBG good for a long hold?  
Any other changes you guys recommend? Next window for change I've given myself is after Easter, not touching portfolio till then.  
Good luck for tomorrow everyone!</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-03 18:53:20+10:00">
   <body>I admire your discipline to hold that long. Easter's what, weeks away!</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Salty-Ant-8567" created="2021-03-03 19:38:37+10:00">
    <body>E.A.S.T.E.R = Easy and Steady, Tendies Eat when Ready</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="joneseph" created="2021-03-03 19:22:45+10:00">
    <body>Weeks I tells ya!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:32:49+10:00">
   <body>IBG was chuzwuzzled?

It's been doing nice this week, it was overall green for me today, but the final drop back to 0% for the day puts it $56 under for me. 

My portfolio looks quite alright. Exactly half red and green. LRS has become green parity of XST (my heaviest, 8k), up and down 2.5k respectively. Most other things are less than $80 in red, with the exception of LGP which had me down 500. BPH used to keep that balanced but as of today BPH has dropped back to my buy in price.

Most stocks have hopefully near term announcements, though honestly I have no idea what's going on with LGP</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Zyphier7" created="2021-03-03 19:19:01+10:00">
  <body>Might regret it but sold my initial investment on PLL and LKE. Letting the profits run care free. Will be holding some cash for now. Tempted to top up on NVA and TLG if they drop a bit more. LPD fucking me hard but got a buy order at 0.02, hope it triggers. Another one catching my eye is CRO and VUL since the recent drop.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-03 19:40:29+10:00">
   <body>NVA is a relativity solid bet with the resource upgrade in April. LKE won’t move for a couple of months so can always get back in. Personally struggling to decide between topping up NVA or LKE with the next comms pay check</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-03 19:34:52+10:00">
   <body>Free carrying is a bitch when you do it, but when you don't do it you get fucked.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kooksy_monster" created="2021-03-03 19:50:17+10:00">
   <body>Also might top up on NVA as well but at this point I could take my pick of my whole folder and average down on any of my picks 🤷‍♂️💀 so much red.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="chaddownunder_" created="2021-03-03 19:41:05+10:00">
  <body>What do we reckon - has the RAC 🚀 launched or still time for me to load up on more tomorrow?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="justplaino" created="2021-03-03 17:06:14+10:00">
  <body>Will REE stop being my meme stock? Currently keeping my portfolio afloat.  Time will tell</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Youii00" created="2021-03-03 17:07:39+10:00">
  <body>OCC gets a good announcement today (Inclusion on Prostheses List here in AU) for their FDA approved product yet they only move up 1%. Can’t wait till instos get a hold of this company. Only need to report massive increases in revenue from the product first for this to happen then it’s history.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-03-03 17:12:42+10:00">
   <body>It Needs a leg up</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Scrapthepolltax" created="2021-03-03 17:56:31+10:00">
    <body>I held OCC for well over a year. Got out recently for a piss poor 5% gain. Great company but think 70% of stock is held by retail so fails to get good runs on good news. Management comms are shit and poor revenue on the products they have in market - need a new sales team</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Youii00" created="2021-03-03 18:09:51+10:00">
     <body>I do honestly believe that next year will be the year Orthocell makes some significant move due to the high possibility of partnerships and further product approval which would assist in the commercialisation of their products. I 100% agree that the company needs to improve their marketing and KoL’s need to be doing a better job with this. In the meantime I’ll be quietly accumulating at these levels in hope it’ll boom one day.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Scrapthepolltax" created="2021-03-03 18:50:36+10:00">
      <body>Good luck mate, I may get back in at some point. You need everything lined up super tight as a micro biotech and these guys don’t have that yet.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="gc8cp9a" created="2021-03-03 18:18:21+10:00">
  <body>Me yesterday: I'll pick up VML at 0.61

Me today: I'll get EZZ at 0.60

Me now after none of my orders got filled: 🤡</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 18:48:19+10:00">
   <body>Fucking same boat. I had an order in for VML at 0.061 and now it’s sitting in the dust. Hoping for some pullback to be able to buy in</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gc8cp9a" created="2021-03-03 19:06:33+10:00">
    <body>Just realised I wrote 0.61 for VML, oops. Meant 0.061. Yeah, I'm probably just gonna leave it. I do this all the time though, the amount of stocks I consider buying but don't or just miss with an order too low pisses me off. And it's always when I YOLO into something trying to avoid a situation like that that it goes bad.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 19:18:34+10:00">
     <body>Better to miss a rocket taking off than chase it and end up holding a bag</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Church_of_FootStool" created="2021-03-03 18:49:36+10:00">
  <body>Gonna top up on IHL if it hits 0.15 or IOU if it really really sinks like 0.3.</body>
  <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-03 18:57:09+10:00">
   <body>And I'll buy afterpay if it hits $5 or Z1p if really really sinks like $1</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Tranquilbull" created="2021-03-03 19:26:19+10:00">
    <body>😂😂😂</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Church_of_FootStool" created="2021-03-03 19:20:39+10:00">
    <body>Sounds like a plan</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-03 19:21:30+10:00">
   <body>Big wall around 18c you’d have to get through first for IHL</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 17:03:54+10:00">
  <body>So... Can LGP get around to selling weed better? Seems to be 5% down, but I thought I saw almost 8% up at lunch.

Fuck, I'm better off selling it myself.

Edit: holy fuck tomorrow is Thursday. I thought today was Tuesday... I'm forgetting something important....</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-03-03 17:40:57+10:00">
   <body>Lame Fuck. Fucking username gives people OCD</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:36:57+10:00">
   <body>I asked one of my customers what day it was today. Twice.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="vadsamoht3" created="2021-03-03 18:13:31+10:00">
  <body>Got a bit free in my account for tomorrow, but I've no idea if I want to add something new to the portfolio or buy something I already hold on sale (which, let's be honest, is everything).</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-03-03 19:28:28+10:00">
  <body>Stopped out of IHL this morning. Wanted to keep with it but have launched into BET for a punt instead</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-03 19:33:54+10:00">
   <body>:'( RIP dude</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Silver-68" created="2021-03-03 17:10:32+10:00">
  <body>ABR had a huge spike today anyone on the Boric Acid with me?</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Graange" created="2021-03-03 17:41:51+10:00">
   <body>From what i understand borates are used in anything and everything but mainly fertilisers, have also heard the above (from a friend that works in the perth office) that they will be part of the EV market in the near future, in at $1.13 long term play</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-03-03 17:14:01+10:00">
   <body>Give some DD? What is boric acid even used for?</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Huwiej" created="2021-03-03 17:21:26+10:00">
    <body>For make benefit great nation Kazakhstan</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="permacolour" created="2021-03-03 18:23:36+10:00">
     <body>My stonk, she is red. Is ok, I have new stonk! Great success!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:27:40+10:00">
    <body>Google knows. ABR rocks. Been on my watchlist for months and been watching it steadily make holders rich without me.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Silver-68" created="2021-03-03 17:20:19+10:00">
    <body>no real DD, did get sent a write up from a friend saying the company will have a huge market in producing products for Electric vehicles and green energy. Stock is only really in a Stage 1 start up, hoping that the mines they've found could hold up over time but could easily turn south. Really is one of the those heard through a friend stocks but something i jumped on</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Beneficial-Silver-68" created="2021-03-03 17:24:08+10:00">
     <body>Borates is the mineral they are looking for the most, but from what ive seen from the presentations posted on their websites they are mining for more then just 1 mineral</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Vivalagloria733" created="2021-03-03 17:23:57+10:00">
  <body>TBR 💩</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-03 17:42:34+10:00">
  <body>I'll probably get shot for saying this but I'm liking pilbara minerals. Has a good support at $1 and obviously they produce and sell lithium.

Another stock I like is CIA they are a iron ore producer. Have a very strong balance sheet.


Food for thought.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-03 17:48:14+10:00">
   <body>The poor buggers who bought in at $1.30 have a long way to wait though.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-03 17:53:08+10:00">
    <body>Fukn fomos</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-03 17:48:50+10:00">
   <body>I think PLS may already be correctly priced. might be a good long termer tho? I always TRY finding them undervalued.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-03-03 17:51:17+10:00">
    <body>Yeah, that's what I was thinking. They'll have a tonne of experience and I'm sure there are other projects, that they can expand on once cash flow positive.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-03 18:00:10+10:00">
     <body>If was gonna try for it id be at 95-100</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:17:34+10:00">
    <body>PLS is a traders dream. I traded it 99.5c to $1.025c 6 times then got bored.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-03 18:28:11+10:00">
   <body>I've been shilling for CIA on here for nearly a year now, people rather ride the autistic Z1P train than companies that print money and return over 100% because they're "boomer" 🤷‍♂️</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-03-03 20:14:04+10:00">
   <body>I missed PLS at .3 and was waiting for it to come back... I don’t think it’s coming back. Luckily I invested in some other tax deductions instead!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="digitalpho3nix" created="2021-03-03 18:47:39+10:00">
  <body>I'm actually taking a very close look at ASB at the moment. Could be a good value medium term investment?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snck_Pck" created="2021-03-03 19:58:52+10:00">
  <body>SRN and 88E are my "poke with a stick and hope they're still alive" stocks atm...</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Suchisthe007life" created="2021-03-03 20:18:21+10:00">
  <body>3DP dropped below strong .8 support today. I think this is a long term hold, with growth to at least $2B market cap in the next 18-months.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="78thusername" created="2021-03-03 20:28:57+10:00">
   <body>Ooo</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="lokkel_18" created="2021-03-03 20:19:47+10:00">
  <body>What's everyone's take on the pending CXO announcement?</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-03-03 20:27:03+10:00">
   <body>They found tendies</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Lonbridge" created="2021-03-03 17:06:47+10:00">
  <body>EPN volume picking up today. In the marijuana space which is starting to heat up. If volume picks up again tomorrow might be a 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-03-03 18:06:10+10:00">
   <body>Hey just saw this
I have had THC now EPN for over 12 months and watched it grow, go through a p&amp;d and now creeping up with official name change and more diverse options. They have connections with the Canadian cannabis market - it’s only a matter of time!</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-03-03 18:11:49+10:00">
    <body>That’s a very good pick up! New name, new team, I picked some up last week when they took
A hit and again this week.  I’m thinking EPN will be the next unicorn in the cannabis sector once the new team executes their business plan!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Lonbridge" created="2021-03-03 18:16:43+10:00">
    <body>Didnt realise so many people on here knew of it. Good to see its getting a bit of coverage.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 17:08:57+10:00">
   <body>I don't think any chuzwuzzas are incoming in marijuana until another big country opens up more to it. Honestly I think we're months away from weed snags</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-03 17:13:24+10:00">
    <body>So dont bother getting into LGP?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 17:20:23+10:00">
     <body>Not for short term trading. Great long term hold though. I don't plan on selling my shares this year</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-03 17:23:15+10:00">
      <body>Ive got an order in at 65. Good price if i get on? What did u pay?</body>
      <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 17:36:13+10:00">
       <body>Haha great price.
I got it in 98, so it's been shit for me. Just a waiting game</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-03-03 17:27:19+10:00">
  <body>Hope RMS continues its run, might break even</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-03-03 18:08:22+10:00">
   <body>This has been such a fking dog of late....</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-03-03 18:18:45+10:00">
    <body>I bought in at 1.43 and it tanked the next day.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-03-03 18:21:48+10:00">
     <body>$1.80 for me, though it ranking from the $2 range was enough, clearly not!!!</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-03-03 18:30:37+10:00">
      <body>Damn</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-03 19:23:10+10:00">
   <body>Pick SLR over all the other goldies except maybe NST. I owned SLR from 97c to $2 something when gold was rising. I think they have had their day but are oversold at current levels. Recent highs will be hard to see again unless gold can get above $2k/oz.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-03 17:49:38+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-03 17:49:38+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-03 19:10:48+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-03 19:10:48+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="JustARandomMoniker" created="2021-03-03 20:05:13+10:00">
  <body>So I cancelled a couple of good for day sell orders at 4:05 or something in commsex and they got status of 'pending cancel' as expected and holdings appeared back in portfolio. 

Checked again now and the share qty has doubled...both actually in profit too so screenshotted as doubt I'll ever get there legitimately.

This happened to anyone else? Is it likely to resolve itself overnight or I am going to waste 40 minutes of tomorrow morning on the phone?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Chief_wigam" created="2021-03-03 20:15:53+10:00">
  <body>Looking at MSB as it seems to have found a bottom with recent CR and new strategic investor. Also HUM technically has bounced off its support at $1</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Chief_wigam" created="2021-03-03 20:18:18+10:00">
  <body>Anyone else holding MGX? Loads of cash in bank earning not much interest for them. Could use the cash in better ways. Share buy back? Good alternative stock to BHP and FMG if you are bullish on iron ore prices and want a producer rather than an explorer</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="78thusername" created="2021-03-03 20:28:32+10:00">
  <body>HAS, ARU, NTU, PEK

Rare earth mining go kaboomboom.

Australia is on track to become a heavy hitter in that area. People want to separate from China.

I’m going to just dump money into this shit until I’m broke or rich AF.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="lokkel_18" created="2021-03-03 20:29:40+10:00">
  <body>May it mean tendies for us all!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-5" downs="0" author="smudgygecko" created="2021-03-03 17:36:40+10:00">
  <body>Discovered se1 today. Looks alright IMO. But DYOR</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-5" downs="0" author="pattymacpatpat" created="2021-03-03 19:16:42+10:00">
  <body>surely flight center will be taking off soon?</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-03-03 19:41:21+10:00">
   <body>Why? International travel is ages away and domestic flights will never get back to old levels now people have spent a year doing business remotely</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="pattymacpatpat" created="2021-03-03 19:58:28+10:00">
    <body>we all make bad choices some times, 1800 shares at $16.687.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-03 19:19:00+10:00">
   <body>You mean webjet?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-7" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-03 18:57:19+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="ninenet909" created="2021-03-03 19:02:37+10:00">
   <body>New account, pump comment</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-11" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-03 19:21:50+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Pure_Beautiful_395" created="2021-03-03 19:36:13+10:00">
   <body>Sorry?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
