<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-02-22 Monday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>LKE (26) HYPE=30</mention>
  <mention>LOT (21) HYPE=10</mention>
  <mention>LRS (20) HYPE=10, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>XST (18) TIP=20, HYPE=8</mention>
  <mention>BIT (14) </mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 20:52:28+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Repost from weekend thread since I put at least 5 mins effort into this: 

Hopefully some bounce on EV plays early next week!

LKE looks poised - may look to grab some more with the market continuing to anticipate the NVX test announcement. Still huge volume on the ASX and on the OTC markets - love this bad boy.

CXO could really use a bounce - can’t see it below the cap raise price (25c) for much longer. It should have some support here (hopefully) - doubling down could be on the cards for me.

Considering consolidating my manganese plays into just E25 - their latest presso looks absolutely prime

On a non EV front - DW8 saved me from big blushes late last week and hopefully it can continue. Probably my favourite growth stonk

PEN bouncing violently off 14 on Fri arvo was a thing of beauty - hopefully we get some tailwind from the new OTC listing and spring to a higher high. Nice volume on it so far on the new OTC listing - ASX investors are still frothing it too which is nice to see.

I was bringing people’s attention to it a couple weeks ago but now it’s for real - tin prices are mooning with futures up 11% last week. With the upcoming electronics boom, Myanmar coup (3rd largest tin producer) and current tiny supply levels - it would be an absolute travesty if we didn’t see some significant pump on some ASX tin plays. SRZ and VMS worth a look imo for speccy big upside. Will be slapping the ask on Mon.

RBL - get me the fuck out hahaha. MS established a sub holding at high $5s late last week post the results dump so I’m hanging my hat on that for now. Need the volume to sustain into next week and hopefully cash out toward mid-6s.

BOL DYOR etc. Moon soon 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Atmo_" created="2021-02-21 21:21:31+10:00">
    <body>Why are you bearish on RBL? Last results looked good plus Biden stimulus in coming soon which means more money for consumers to spend on e-commerce sites. Plus a positive buy rating from GS. What am I missing?</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:29:43+10:00">
     <body>Results are fine - they don’t justify soaring to new heights though by any means in my opinion.  I don’t see this next half being close to this - results seemed bloated with high margin mask sales in Q1. Personally was hoping for 55ish million EBIT. Q2 being lower than Q1 despite Halloween, Cyber Monday and Christmas was pretty disappointing I gotta say. The 12 month $7.11 price target from GS seems extremely reasonable. Wouldn’t say I’m bearish - I think you can make money by buying around here but I’m not optimistic about pumping anywhere near as hard as last year</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 21:59:08+10:00">
      <body>Mmmmm thats what people keep saying but it went from $1 to $7. I thought the results were great and bought on the weakness.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BeagleJools" created="2021-02-21 21:41:42+10:00">
    <body>E25 is solid. Been slowly adding since December.

Basically;
-starting production next few weeks
-great growth plan- plenty of upside with high purity manganese (green thanks to CSIRO and long term renewable power plans)
-low SOI- through low dilution and some shrewd investments.
-Low MC v stage 2 NPV.

They've gone from explorer to producer inside 12 months. I was fairly skeptical after watching their earlier Crux interviews but they've delivered.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Forumbane" created="2021-02-21 22:24:03+10:00">
     <body>Yep I researched E25 over the weekend and gonna grab some next week</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 23:20:34+10:00">
     <body>Just looked at E25. Very interesting but i dont have to time to plow through all info atm. 
Stage 1 is going to be completed in Q1 this year and i believe already has offtake for 100%. The npv is 500m for just stage 1 but MC does not seem to reflect this even though project is heavily derisked, what is suppressing the SP?

What is the ebit that will be generated from stage 1?

How likely can they produce high purity Manganese for battery use?</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BeagleJools" created="2021-02-22 02:28:34+10:00">
      <body>Not sure why the sp is suppressed. As for the ebit, we'll find out over the next two quarters. It'll supposedly pay for stage 2.
They've stated in interviews that high purity manganese can be generated more environmentally friendly and cheaper than China. They're really starting to push their green credentials now and there will be a PFS out for this later this year. I'm optimistic given what they've achieved so far.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:53:29+10:00">
    <body>MLX is my current DD win going forward from this week. Tin is about to be big</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:28:17+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>VMS is due to run but looks like it’s potentially drifting back to CR price of 5.5. Market is being impatient with quite a few CR shares still to go through from memory, maybe 1-2 weeks worth at least. 

I made the mistake of not buying enough below 5.5 last dip. I won’t be making that same mistake again.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:32:33+10:00">
     <body>Yeah I’ll be watching closely - more interested in adding to my SRZ holding as of right now with a nice dip on Fri.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:37:02+10:00">
      <body>Not familiar with SRZ but looking at its chart, it’s a volatile fucker lots of big red candles but still trending up. 

Currently sitting on the EMA which it’s bounced off each and every time since it started running. Could be a good spot for an entry/top up.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:40:27+10:00">
       <body>Definitely a big speccy play - some salty legacy holders are suppressing what feels like an inevitable pump. If it opens 26/27 tomorrow I’ll be throwing the dice (again)</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:45:24+10:00">
        <body>I might do some digging and join you.</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:47:12+10:00">
         <body>Best of luck if you take the plunge - of course DYOR</body>
         <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:48:05+10:00">
          <body>You too mate. Always do 👍</body>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-22 07:02:25+10:00" sentiment="TIP 13">
    <body>Do you think AVZ gets overlooked as a tin speccie? Potentially 3rd largest Tin resource in the world and currently being confirmed with drill assays.

AVZ major resource and future revenue will mainly come from lithium (spodumene) and may pose a socioeconomic risk as the mine will be built in the DRC. 

Once Tin offtakes and future lithium offtakes are announced, this will signifcantly derisk the projects and with AVZ being in a great position purely based on having both tin and lithium prices flying-to me it seems there is alot of money to be made.

Not sure if people are sleeping on this company or if investors are waiting for signifcant derisking announcements like offtake ane final investment decisions.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 21:24:23+10:00" sentiment="TIP 10">
   <body>XST/SGC -

Either I'm missing something or people are misunderstanding what is happening with XST/SGC. The Borba 1-7 well is not the end of the story, its the start and we haven't even started drilling yet. It was always intended that Borba 1-7 would "open-up" a greater TCF play. I don't think a multi tcf single well was ever on the cards. If you look at the earlier Dempsey prospect, it was always touted as a 1+TCF play and they ended up spudding multiple wells.

You'll note that the resource report (which is usually conservative in its numbers) shows a 70% chance of success with the company indicating it expects an 80% chance of development - these numbers are high. 

Going off what the company director is saying there will be more spuds happening after this one (which we're still yet to get results from). From here there should be plenty of announcements coming through in the next 30 days or so from actual drilling results. 

Now, I'm always hesitant to try to calculate the worth of something like a natural gas well as I'm not a geologist and there's probably more to it than just taking the amount of gas and multiplying it by the price of gas, but doing so gives the below results: 

Gas price avg = A$5/Mcf (thousand cubic feet) 

XST/SGC split = 38/75 Bcf  

XST share in $ = A$190 million (MC of 32 mil) 

SGC share in $ = A$375 million (MC of 40 mil) 

This is for 1 well. 

Potentially there is more that I'm not seeing but it seems to me that even off the Borba 1-7 well, the SP should grow substantially for both companies once they actually start making money off these wells.

Please let me know if there is something wrong with my math or any massive inaccuracies in what I've said.

Edit: As expected, my math is off. They have 70% CoS for 10.3/19.5Bcf respectively. Recalculated, this gives $51.5 mil and $97.5 mil. These numbers still seem pretty good at their current MC's.</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 21:40:28+10:00">
    <body>You’re using the wrong numbers from the report. It’s actually a 70% chance of 19.5bcf for SGC and 10.3bcf for XST - see page 5 of SGC’s report and page 3 of XST’s. 

You have to use these numbers because these are the numbers that account for the different layers. The higher numbers aren’t adjusted for the probability of each layer. 

The 141bcf total figure is the total for all layers ignoring the fact that each layer has its own probability of success. It’s not as simple as “70% chance of 141bcf” and despite what you read on here and HC the report doesn’t actually say that.

A lot of people think the report is overly conservative and that may or may not be right, but if you’re going to do the sums based on the report at least use the right figures.</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 21:53:43+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
     <body>Ahh okay, that makes sense. So essentially its saying they have a 70% chance of recovering $51.5 mil (XST)/97.5 mil (SGC) worth of gas each. I've had a look at other resource reports and it seems that 70% CoS is quite high. 

What do you make of future drills in this area? The MD seems very bullish on it. It seems that this is kind of a proof of concept to show that there is recoverable gas in this area.</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 21:59:51+10:00">
      <body>I honestly don’t know what to think. I’ve got a small amount of SCG that I’m willing to lose if it’s a duster, and I’m just going to let the drilling speak for itself.

People have a lot of strong options either way so I’m done speculating on Borba. I’m just locked and loaded. I only wanted to correct your numbers so that you knew better what you were looking at.</body>
      <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 22:04:15+10:00">
       <body>Yeah its for sure a high risk play - i think peoples expectations for the resource report were a bit unrealistic. I've got small amounts in both and happy to hold through drill results. Cheers for the correction!</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 22:13:47+10:00">
        <body>I’ll also add that no one really knows what’s down there - even the independent expert. Could be more could be less could be nothing. 

So a big success could involve more than the predicted bcf each - but there’s only one way to find out and anything else is true speculation at this point!</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-22 01:36:30+10:00">
      <body>Is not 70% its multiple lots of 17% chance.

So TECHNICALLY it works to be 70% but math doesn't always work out that way.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:45:44+10:00">
    <body>I definitely read the report as fine news, and am happy to hold out. It's a huge loss for me so far but I know it's worth more than that it is now.

Just a sit and wait game. I honestly think my XST is a very long hold.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="wednesdaythefrog" created="2021-02-22 06:11:35+10:00">
    <body>Hey mate, just a quick pointer - although it's easy to just calculate the gross estimated gas by current gas prices - the reality is, is that it's not free to pump out. Try using the net present value formula to expense out the cost of production and to ensure that it's economical.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-22 07:12:40+10:00">
     <body>Careful - people don’t want real numbers they only want good news. I typed up a NPV calculation for SGC (on Hot Copper don’t shame me lol) and it upset someone so much that they followed me to here to accuse me of setting up a scam.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="angelusinc" created="2021-02-22 05:55:43+10:00">
   <body>I'm on the LKE train but I'd like to hear from people who decided to pass on this. I'm trying to find any negative DD but I'm not finding much outside of the fact that Indochine didn't make it, and Steve led that one. Anything else I'm missing?</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-02-22 06:21:15+10:00">
    <body>It was a great call by many here and people that followed that got on the 10c mark. I feel that the upcoming announcement is partially priced in with the current value. People who are calling LKE to hit $1 haven't realised that this will mean LKE at 1B Market cap. Can't see that happening but hey, what do I know.</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 06:53:48+10:00">
     <body>There's a fuck ton of people new here who start screeching about prices with no concept of what a Market Cap is, it's actually doing my brain in.</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:05:10+10:00">
      <body>Oh I do need a market cap!
Do you do custom designs?</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="platypusreacharound" created="2021-02-22 08:35:40+10:00">
      <body>I'm in for 2 market caps please.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="angelusinc" created="2021-02-22 06:25:50+10:00" sentiment="TIP 10">
     <body>Maybe not this year but I ideally want to hold this for like 5-10 years so if we get a few more catalysts and phase into production, I cant see why it won't be at least over $3 by that time. There's just so much more to go. This is still the beginning in my opinion. I can see why day traders may want to stay away though</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-02-22 07:31:10+10:00">
      <body>Same with PRL last week, people got in the hype
 and VUL took 3 years to get to the same place I saw this morning. Lots of announcements to come by LKE will take a couple of years</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MachinaDoctrina" created="2021-02-22 06:48:12+10:00">
     <body>VUL has a 750M market cap why not LKE, to be honest LKE is sitting on a larger deposit than VUL</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-02-22 07:44:16+10:00">
      <body>Isn't some of that VUL cap due to ESG bullshit tho</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MachinaDoctrina" created="2021-02-22 07:46:00+10:00">
       <body>Why exactly would that factor into their market cap and not LKE?</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-02-22 08:11:20+10:00">
        <body>Cause of the carbon zero processing method. It's proprietary and adds value.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 17:54:04+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Been accumulating more TLG. Currently the only and possibly the largest graphite resource with vertically integrated anode production in Europe – where EV transition will be spearheaded. Tier-1 mining jurisdiction in Sweden. 

Anode/graphite material makes up a large volume/weight of the Lithium-ion battery but has generally been the less talk of all battery materials even though demand is also projected to eclipse supply. BUT recently there has been a strong increase in interest and price actions across all Graphite/Anode players. Some Graphite stocks in the US has been going gangbuster. TLG is well set up to take advantage of this being the potentially largest graphite/anode player in Europe. Someone going to need to supply the demand…outside China.

DFS for the ‘initial’ 20k tpa anode production (NOT graphite but anode material) expected in March 2021 and that should result in price action, follow by hopefully binding JV with LKAB (Swedish mining company) and Mitsui. Further scoping study has been done to potentially increase this production up to 100k tpa. 

Anyway, obligatory rockets  🚀  🚀  🚀</body>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 18:52:17+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>I’ve got such high hopes for TLG. If they do what they plan to it’s easily a 10 bagger from here. Still risk in execution of the plans but huge potential payoff.

There’s a talga subreddit now. Good collection of articles and info

https://www.reddit.com/r/talga/</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Luxim_" created="2021-02-21 19:45:50+10:00">
    <body>Is $1.50 a decent entry price for TLG?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-02-21 19:54:55+10:00">
     <body>Yes. It’s unlikely to drop lower than that since *I think* they handed out a shit load at that price not too long ago. They’ve been in the $1.50 - 1.60 noose for a while now. According to HC , It’s a popular shorted stock atm.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 20:00:48+10:00">
      <body>The short i believe is very inconsequential at 0.02%.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 20:13:42+10:00">
       <body>Shorting has to be the most misunderstood thing on hot copper (and it’s a low bar). Unbelievable how many times shorters get blamed for a drop in share price and like you say, you check the short interest and it’s practically nothing.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 19:59:30+10:00">
     <body>My view yes. It has the 1.45 CR support. And there will be a few catalysts coming up soon.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 20:09:28+10:00">
     <body>I think so, I’ve gone in for 150k shares +/- a few cents either side of $1.50

I don’t think it’s going to rocket though, just steady increases over the next 2-3 years as milestones are reached and the projects get de-risked</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="yogaisnow" created="2021-02-21 20:52:03+10:00">
    <body>I’m also in on TLG, very organic growth and the managing director seems to know what he’s doing. Their site in Sweden has been labeled as ‘national significance’ and LKAB is a owned by the Swedish govt - this stock is going to be huge in a few years time I can see US listing in the future. HOLD! 💎🙌🏻</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-22 08:32:47+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>Got in NNG on Friday, IPO on Thursday and closed Friday 40% up from IPO price of $0.20.

Reasons

 - price held up well above Thursday's close despite XJO was in deep red on Friday. I took this as a sign of holders not letting go of their shares at current level and have high confidence 

- buy/sell depth added conviction to the above observation 

- about 45% of total 111mil SOI held by top holders and are in escrow, so about 63mil shares to trade on market, relatively small float.

- stock in tech space, I bet on its growth potential to be overvalued in a short term once it was promoted by some stock news websites/caught public's attention

- if it didn't go well, I have the $0.265 wall to sell into, so about 4% downside


During the weekend, I saw QPM and its chart, and now I believe that would've been a better hold over the weekend.

Reasons

- break out of previous resistances on high volume, closed Friday at ATH

- announcement from last week would likely be used as hype fuel

- closed $0.088, if it makes 10%, there's a chance that the momentum will push it above $0.10 and the pip change will take it up further

- the 500% gains mania in last week may have not ended and QPM looks to have similar recipe to those that was pumped to 500%

- I'll see how this open and decide whether to jump in</body>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="29" downs="0" author="murray_01" created="2021-02-21 17:35:52+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 20">
   <body>Let's go Z1P 🚀🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="BOUND_TESTICLE" created="2021-02-21 18:15:07+10:00">
    <body>Conference call on Thursday, Does anyone know what chemist takes Zippay so I can buy some lube before the market shoves a red rocket up my ass?</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Seedysloth89" created="2021-02-21 19:32:05+10:00">
     <body>I saw zip pay at the checkout at chemist warehouse. It was higher in the list of acceptable transactions than afterpay which i found to be curious.</body>
     <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="BOUND_TESTICLE" created="2021-02-21 19:48:45+10:00">
      <body>This is solid due diligence. Zip target now $79 a share.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Spectre-__-" created="2021-02-21 17:57:07+10:00">
    <body>plannig to put 5k into it lets see how it goes</body>
    <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="murray_01" created="2021-02-21 18:06:34+10:00">
     <body>You'll be fine if you hold. I was in the red by a lot for months, now I'm way up. They're an underrated company, but at the end of the day the market does as it does. 

I think a good report on 25/02 is already priced in, but news on ADRs and/or substantial US investor would send it higher.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="azad_s" created="2021-02-22 08:15:10+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 18">
   <body>Great assay results just received from COD. Been sitting on this since ipo. Time to start seeing some tendies 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:18:18+10:00">
    <body>Don't trust fish man, they fucking LIE!

Edit: sorry, just woke up. Not constructive yet</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 17:19:20+10:00">
   <body>This week is going to be a good week. I can't tell you how I know, but I definitely feel it.
Not a ridiculously good week, but a very good week.

I also predict cannabis to be down 😟</body>
   <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-21 17:33:34+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>When i saw scomo getting the jab on the news i thought...oh yeah..the market will like this #tendies</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-21 18:15:58+10:00">
    <body>Down in your lungs?</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 18:17:44+10:00">
     <body>Down everywhere.
Totally unrelated feeling to today being my first day of a 3 week holiday from work</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-22 06:44:57+10:00">
      <body>Whats the best canabis stock for me to jump on? Will DMOR of course.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 07:46:01+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 18">
       <body>My money is in LGP, plenty of positives to read into and good future plans.

It's only problem is that it's playing too aggressive. Yearly spending is just about doubling every year. I can't see it being profitable for a while though it's definitely starting to do some good deals.

So it's gamble - if they start making serious money to offset what they spend 🚀🚀🚀.
If not, well they'll get the money by diluting you back to the stoner age.</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-22 07:47:54+10:00">
        <body>really does sound like a gamble</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 17:21:26+10:00">
    <body>[removed]</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 17:21:27+10:00">
     <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="65" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 17:19:55+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>LRS and LKE should release this week 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-02-21 17:45:15+10:00">
    <body>Is that a good thing for LRS? Hopefully isn't another XST type of announcement.</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 17:46:46+10:00">
     <body>I will definitely be prepared to sell the news if it runs prior to the announcement and the results are less than spectacular.</body>
     <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 18:20:43+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
      <body>I'll be watching like a hawk. I'm ready to dump this baby for 70% profit right now if things look XST like.

Side note - XST to climb 30% by the end of the week, or I'll delete my binding of Isaac save file (only 1 more achievement to 100% - play 31 dailies)</body>
      <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 19:14:43+10:00">
       <body>I would proof or ban you, but I'm not comfortable with cruel and unusual punishment.</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-02-21 20:36:09+10:00">
       <body>I fucking hope so.  That cunt of a thing burnt a lot of people!</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 19:58:16+10:00">
       <body>70% is very nice. I’ve traded this fucker a bit so barely green at my current buy.

No idea what the second paragraph means at all lol</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 19:13:41+10:00">
      <body>Might be better to sell the rumour as most are considering selling news. Just a thought</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 19:56:15+10:00">
       <body>I’m kinda keen to see the news but not a bad idea to reduce one’s position after the next run. I’m not holding a huge amount anyway as my balls often start tingling when every man and their dog keeps pumping the results of a stock.</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 20:01:40+10:00">
        <body>Problem I see is regardless of the announcement everyone has the idea of sell the news plus the pump is on. More will probably buy in to do the same. I’d beat them to the punch. What’s The dual listing been doing latley</body>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:09:23+10:00">
         <body>That’s true but as it hasn’t gone super saiyan parabolic I don’t feel like anything is overly priced in quite yet. 

I’m using OAR as my example of the market not responding to results straight away. Big gap up on open then died. That’s what I think is possible with LRS if results aren’t up to scratch. Those who understand the results (not me) won’t want to sell the news right away, they’ll want it to pump first then sell into the volume...or so my theory goes.</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-02-21 17:50:53+10:00">
     <body>Well that's the speccy nature of exploration mining but from initial results, LRS seems like its in for a decent ride with 3N grade halloysite found at 15% and kaolin for approx 40%. Detailed assays to come

And that doesnt even factor in any of its gold tenements, so definitely some more legs to run if the halloysote/kaolin doesnt pan out well</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 18:32:59+10:00">
      <body>LRS have 3N halloysite in the ground?

I’m not a geo but I don’t think that can be correct</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 17:55:59+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
      <body>I think the results will be roughly the same as ADN and then it’s on to the gold, lithium and copper results 🚀</body>
      <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-02-21 18:16:54+10:00">
       <body>Dont want to sound pessimistic or anything but im not sure itll be ADN level/ volume... But i guess the assays will confirm.

That said, im long term holding for the gold...</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 20:43:48+10:00">
        <body>I thought I read that they have a larger resource then ADN?</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 21:21:31+10:00">
         <body>To some extent the quality of the resource is more important that the size with an industrial mineral like this. WAK have a huge kaolin resource and are pretty much ready to go, but can only sell it for $200-300/t on small margins which is reflected in the $50m market cap. Until we see some results from LRS it’s a guessing game. I think the hype has got ahead of the reality on this one at the moment</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-22 07:23:15+10:00">
      <body>Legit, everyone talking about selling the news but there’s gold results coming as well as copper and lithium reserves....</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="d2blues" created="2021-02-21 19:24:55+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
     <body>XST directors exercising options and selling immediately wasn’t a great look.

Positive LRS halloysite results should have ADN potential.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SnooOwls5021" created="2021-02-21 19:15:11+10:00">
    <body>Too late to buy LRS or LKE?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-21 19:44:27+10:00">
     <body>Lke certainly not, the battery results haven't come out, no offtake yet either.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 20:44:30+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
     <body>Both are great long term holds 🚀</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="willy2milly" created="2021-02-21 20:16:36+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Excited to see how nvx and lke will do this week. Lot of hype around lke, should go for a nice good run tomorrow</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="MachinaDoctrina" created="2021-02-22 07:02:39+10:00">
    <body>let's hope its not just a pump and dump</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="86" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-02-21 20:19:32+10:00">
  <body>The quality of this sub unfortunately has finally hit a wall. 

The number of newbies "giving advice" is watering down the sub.

Whilst I respect what the mods have done to prevent spamming, some of you new users have to understand that if you're ever going to get good at this, you gotta do your time and figure out your strategy.

If you can't read financials, can't read charts, don't know very common trading terms, don't understand why some stocks are hyped up in the first place (often intentionally) or even worse, don't even how to use Google, don't expect this to be fun.

If you're just blindly following random posts and buying stocks without even knowing what the company does, you're literally a sheep that some more experienced lads want to prey on. 

Sure some of you will get lucky and get a bagger or more easy (first one's always free).

But how you react when your investment turns on you will be more interesting for the rest of us honestly. 

You want good advice? Invest what you're willing to lose and this is especially true if it's a risky trade. If that number is $2K for example and that disappears, it shouldn't bother you too much because you knew the risk from the start. 

Why? Because that's my favourite part of trading. If I fuck up, that's on me. But if my analysis is right, I win. 

That's really it.</body>
  <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:32:33+10:00">
   <body>I feel so targeted.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-21 20:25:54+10:00">
   <body>I tell ya what, some of them will be absolutely astounded to find out that the questions they have have already been asked and they can find them by using the search bar! 

It’s unbelievable how many posts I’ve seen the mods delete asking just basic questions or posting the same shit posted already even that day. Sad to see the quality of this great sub diminish. 

Hopefully the growth’ll slow and all the noobs can catch up but I’m not holding my breathe.</body>
   <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 20:28:29+10:00">
    <body>We need to start pumping out a lot more DLC recommendations to the low effort posts.</body>
    <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 20:52:19+10:00">
     <body>The hedgies are bringing this sub down</body>
     <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 21:02:07+10:00">
      <body>REEEEEEE</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-02-21 20:47:54+10:00">
     <body>This. This right here. The only solution.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="min0nim" created="2021-02-22 07:32:07+10:00">
     <body>You know, I do this already but I’m half suspecting that it will take a bull run and they’ll start producing dildos for lithium miners, make a fortune, and make me look like a complete fool.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 21:42:52+10:00">
   <body>Posts that are literally just "Thoughts on (shit stock X)?" with nothing else should just be auto-deleted IMO, waste of ASCII characters</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-21 22:10:02+10:00">
    <body>It's an r/ausstocks thing, so you can immediately tell where they've come from</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="steveydraws" created="2021-02-22 02:18:28+10:00">
     <body>I literally made a post in that sub asking the mods for a better gatekeeping strategy to prevent these type of posts but looks like it’s still continuing and a few of them actually said not to have any regulations like wtf enjoy the shitty quality posts then</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-22 08:20:00+10:00">
    <body>Just copy paste their question back to them. Unlikely you'll get any thoughts back tho lol</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:04:17+10:00">
   <body>It’s natural in the most bullish market ever, who knows if this is the peak but as people flock to “easy free” money this is bound to happen. As soon as we see a red day there’s already panic</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AUinvestoscootAU" created="2021-02-22 05:43:28+10:00">
   <body>Wait so you mean I can’t just slap the ask on some rando’s portf?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="65" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 17:19:55+10:00">
  <body>LRS and LKE should release this week 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-02-21 17:45:15+10:00">
   <body>Is that a good thing for LRS? Hopefully isn't another XST type of announcement.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 17:46:46+10:00">
    <body>I will definitely be prepared to sell the news if it runs prior to the announcement and the results are less than spectacular.</body>
    <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 18:20:43+10:00">
     <body>I'll be watching like a hawk. I'm ready to dump this baby for 70% profit right now if things look XST like.

Side note - XST to climb 30% by the end of the week, or I'll delete my binding of Isaac save file (only 1 more achievement to 100% - play 31 dailies)</body>
     <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 19:14:43+10:00">
      <body>I would proof or ban you, but I'm not comfortable with cruel and unusual punishment.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Stratton-0akmont" created="2021-02-21 20:36:09+10:00">
      <body>I fucking hope so.  That cunt of a thing burnt a lot of people!</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 19:58:16+10:00">
      <body>70% is very nice. I’ve traded this fucker a bit so barely green at my current buy.

No idea what the second paragraph means at all lol</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 19:13:41+10:00">
     <body>Might be better to sell the rumour as most are considering selling news. Just a thought</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 19:56:15+10:00">
      <body>I’m kinda keen to see the news but not a bad idea to reduce one’s position after the next run. I’m not holding a huge amount anyway as my balls often start tingling when every man and their dog keeps pumping the results of a stock.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 20:01:40+10:00">
       <body>Problem I see is regardless of the announcement everyone has the idea of sell the news plus the pump is on. More will probably buy in to do the same. I’d beat them to the punch. What’s The dual listing been doing latley</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:09:23+10:00">
        <body>That’s true but as it hasn’t gone super saiyan parabolic I don’t feel like anything is overly priced in quite yet. 

I’m using OAR as my example of the market not responding to results straight away. Big gap up on open then died. That’s what I think is possible with LRS if results aren’t up to scratch. Those who understand the results (not me) won’t want to sell the news right away, they’ll want it to pump first then sell into the volume...or so my theory goes.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-02-21 17:50:53+10:00">
    <body>Well that's the speccy nature of exploration mining but from initial results, LRS seems like its in for a decent ride with 3N grade halloysite found at 15% and kaolin for approx 40%. Detailed assays to come

And that doesnt even factor in any of its gold tenements, so definitely some more legs to run if the halloysote/kaolin doesnt pan out well</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 18:32:59+10:00">
     <body>LRS have 3N halloysite in the ground?

I’m not a geo but I don’t think that can be correct</body>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 17:55:59+10:00">
     <body>I think the results will be roughly the same as ADN and then it’s on to the gold, lithium and copper results 🚀</body>
     <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-02-21 18:16:54+10:00">
      <body>Dont want to sound pessimistic or anything but im not sure itll be ADN level/ volume... But i guess the assays will confirm.

That said, im long term holding for the gold...</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 20:43:48+10:00">
       <body>I thought I read that they have a larger resource then ADN?</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 21:21:31+10:00">
        <body>To some extent the quality of the resource is more important that the size with an industrial mineral like this. WAK have a huge kaolin resource and are pretty much ready to go, but can only sell it for $200-300/t on small margins which is reflected in the $50m market cap. Until we see some results from LRS it’s a guessing game. I think the hype has got ahead of the reality on this one at the moment</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-22 07:23:15+10:00">
     <body>Legit, everyone talking about selling the news but there’s gold results coming as well as copper and lithium reserves....</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="d2blues" created="2021-02-21 19:24:55+10:00">
    <body>XST directors exercising options and selling immediately wasn’t a great look.

Positive LRS halloysite results should have ADN potential.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SnooOwls5021" created="2021-02-21 19:15:11+10:00">
   <body>Too late to buy LRS or LKE?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-21 19:44:27+10:00">
    <body>Lke certainly not, the battery results haven't come out, no offtake yet either.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 20:44:30+10:00">
    <body>Both are great long term holds 🚀</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="55" downs="0" author="ToiIets" created="2021-02-21 19:26:30+10:00">
  <body>I hope LRS never release the results and if they do I hope they are shit. 


Don't mind me I'm just trying reverse psychology so I stop checking LRS every morning every 10 minutes from 7am-10am hoping that lil ⚠ appears.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="cheebaihai" created="2021-02-21 19:55:58+10:00">
   <body>Had me in the first half ngl</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:41:19+10:00">
   <body>Shit report 🚀
Good report 🛬</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="54" downs="0" author="Jayalef" created="2021-02-21 18:45:03+10:00">
  <body>Sub should be renamed ASX_pumps</body>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="genuinelivesmatter" created="2021-02-21 19:25:06+10:00">
   <body>It's a bit of both. You got to sort out the pump stocks from the good stocks.</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-21 19:45:42+10:00">
   <body>Dyorgltawtfbbqdildo</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="53" downs="0" author="mOOse32" created="2021-02-21 18:40:16+10:00">
  <body>Does anyone actually read this thread in its default state or do you sort by new like a normal person?</body>
  <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-02-21 18:48:02+10:00">
   <body>Wasn't there a vote and everyone voted to sort by new?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-21 18:45:03+10:00">
   <body>I just change it back to sort by new.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 19:15:42+10:00">
   <body>Sort by new or bust. I hope they change it soon.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mOOse32" created="2021-02-21 19:36:14+10:00">
    <body>I thought it was an oversight but apparently they want it this way..</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 19:43:52+10:00">
     <body>Sounds like you’re going for a board spill with mods?</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mOOse32" created="2021-02-21 19:48:32+10:00">
      <body>Haha nah, I'm good... I just wanna save myself a couple of taps.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Resident_Duck3116" created="2021-02-21 20:20:57+10:00">
   <body>I sort by colours, because I can smell them.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Christiee28" created="2021-02-21 18:44:13+10:00">
   <body>I do before I remember it isn’t sorted by new</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:13:45+10:00">
   <body>New. Always new.

EDIT: I think our voices (cries) have been heard. It's now defaulting to new.</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-02-21 19:45:38+10:00">
   <body>New</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="47" downs="0" author="WowVeryJosh" created="2021-02-21 22:15:10+10:00">
  <body>God damn you boys are ruthless cunts. I've never seen so many tickers getting mass downvoted.

This can only lead to a great Monday.</body>
  <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-02-21 22:20:41+10:00">
   <body>The OGs are now demanding loss porn as part of the baptism if newbs wanna join the sub. 

_Feed us more losses_</body>
   <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:36:19+10:00">
    <body>I haven't sold, but my portfolio is 40% XST at .0192.

Does that count?</body>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 22:17:46+10:00">
   <body>The BS meters are returning to full strength. Nature is healing.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="43" downs="0" author="mantyq" created="2021-02-21 18:38:49+10:00">
  <body>T+2 ing some LKE and selling my ETF's if i fuck it up. Wish me luck boys</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:51:52+10:00">
   <body>Sell your ETFs anyway and plough them into pennies. I did it months ago - it's quite liberating</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Yaals" created="2021-02-21 19:33:56+10:00">
   <body>gl</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:38:48+10:00">
   <body>I like the idea of T+2, but it would have fucked me hard with XST. So I'll definitely avoid it</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Saltedcaramelpopcorn" created="2021-02-22 01:42:21+10:00">
   <body>I want to see this</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="38" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-21 17:48:19+10:00">
  <body>This is our week LRS holders. Double digits cmon</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-21 18:29:39+10:00">
   <body>Hoping LRS will carry me overall into green, still recovering from my GME/AMC losses and XST didn't help either (thankfully I unloaded all my bags at 0.016).

LKE/LRS....my knights of shining armour &lt;3</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Bl4ckhamm3r" created="2021-02-21 18:45:10+10:00">
   <body>If there two things I'm a dirty little slut for, it's 1) Back tickles and 2) LRS</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="38" downs="0" author="jolebu" created="2021-02-21 17:53:34+10:00">
  <body>Just a thought on the ‘mental health’ post bans... should make the guys make a donation to black dog institute as way back in earlier with an apology post and proof of donation</body>
  <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 18:07:51+10:00">
   <body>Make the amount donated scale exponentially too lmao</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="PM_me_ur_bingo_nos" created="2021-02-21 18:52:35+10:00">
   <body>Not a terrible idea. Aside from the creating anew profile to join.

Mods? [u/mcfucking](https://www.reddit.com/u/mcfucking)</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jolebu" created="2021-02-21 20:34:12+10:00">
    <body>They can make a new profile or just cop a small fine.. If even a few paid still going to a good cause!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-02-21 18:32:04+10:00">
   <body>Sweet idea</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="31" downs="0" author="is2017goingtobebad" created="2021-02-21 20:40:32+10:00">
  <body>Can’t wait to lose money again!</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="BuggeredBudgie" created="2021-02-21 20:56:35+10:00">
   <body>Can’t sleep Stonks will Eat me!!</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Pricy2401" created="2021-02-21 21:12:40+10:00">
    <body>the monster under the bed's just waiting to steal tendies</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="32" downs="0" author="trashbets" created="2021-02-21 20:20:23+10:00">
  <body>Went to Woolies and bought some lube so I can be prepared for XST to hit my G-spot and rocket me back to somewhat close to the ath I bought in at or you know cry whatevers good</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 21:12:43+10:00">
   <body>I think once the drill bit start talking, we'll get a much better picture as to how good of a prospect this is. Hopefully he gets some mates soon too..</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:29:22+10:00">
   <body>Free Lube in a Brisbane area Woolworths for anyone who finds me and says "I need XST lube". 

I whistle a far bit at work, that's the only clue - start asking</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="therealeddiek" created="2021-02-21 20:27:49+10:00">
   <body>Good plan !!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="30" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-21 20:24:12+10:00">
  <body>I spent the weekend using the recent ‘how to’ post by u/yothuyindi (thanks man) to compare approx 30 companies and rate them according to the factors discussed. Also looked at the diversity of the management and directors and whether I thought the CEO’s got paid too much relative to market cap and performance. I have come to a short list which I just have to dive into a little bit more. I could possibly be applying biases in my ratings in order to get the results I am after but so long as I’m confident that’s all that matters :) I’ll share my decisions and reasoning this week maybe get help with any mistakes. 

Interesting how much my opinion of a company changes when I find out how much the ceo does or doesn’t pay themself. One of my top watchlist stocks would picks be ruled out because I’m disappointed with the CEO pay. Unless I can find something that makes up for it somewhere.</body>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 20:27:40+10:00">
   <body>Look at you go using your brain and own DD to make decisions, don't forget about us when that investment bank hires you</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-21 20:33:27+10:00">
    <body>Oh my god I could not do this for a job hahahahaha hahahahaha hahahahaha hahhaa well maybe if it wasn’t my money lollllll 🙈👌</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 20:36:23+10:00">
     <body>That's the beauty of it, not your money and you get paid no matter how great or shit your return is for the year.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-21 20:42:00+10:00">
      <body>You son of a bitch, I’m in!</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 20:30:23+10:00">
   <body>Management salaries for microcaps and startups is a very quick way to see who’s in it for the lifestyle and who is really looking long term to build a business. Not always 100% accurate but I’ve found it to be useful in making quick assessments.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-21 20:34:45+10:00">
    <body>Yeah man I was so disappointed with some. Feels like being betrayed. lol 
Like I wanna find out if they donate heaps to charity or should I just deal with it and move on.</body>
    <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 20:37:09+10:00">
     <body>On the other hand management owning heaps of options with strike prices multiples higher than the current share price is something I can definitely get behind. Happy for them to get rich if we all do as well.</body>
     <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Exalted_HC" created="2021-02-21 21:11:32+10:00">
      <body>This is a very good post. :)

Management is 50% of a companies chance of success.

Said to me by a very successful investor friend of mine, top 10 in ADN and IHL among others and made millions. Rings especially true in the spec end of the market.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 20:49:35+10:00">
   <body>Aww thanks dude; remember, it was more just a post to introduce you all to some of the useful online tools out there and some ways to use them, as well as an example of a thought process, more than saying "you should follow my investing style".

I personally just like to try and add an extra layer of protection of *actual company earnings* when choosing my individual stocks (even small caps), so you won't see the tickers of many of the holdings I own mentioned here very often... haha.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="28" downs="0" author="costaa_96" created="2021-02-21 17:05:07+10:00">
  <body>Interested to see how LKE and NVX hold up after Friday</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-21 17:22:47+10:00">
   <body>Should be a great week</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="kooksy_monster" created="2021-02-21 17:26:24+10:00">
   <body>Yeah hopefully I can catch it on a dip this time [*laughs nervously*]</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="29" downs="0" author="murray_01" created="2021-02-21 17:35:52+10:00">
  <body>Let's go Z1P 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="BOUND_TESTICLE" created="2021-02-21 18:15:07+10:00">
   <body>Conference call on Thursday, Does anyone know what chemist takes Zippay so I can buy some lube before the market shoves a red rocket up my ass?</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Seedysloth89" created="2021-02-21 19:32:05+10:00">
    <body>I saw zip pay at the checkout at chemist warehouse. It was higher in the list of acceptable transactions than afterpay which i found to be curious.</body>
    <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="BOUND_TESTICLE" created="2021-02-21 19:48:45+10:00">
     <body>This is solid due diligence. Zip target now $79 a share.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Spectre-__-" created="2021-02-21 17:57:07+10:00">
   <body>plannig to put 5k into it lets see how it goes</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="murray_01" created="2021-02-21 18:06:34+10:00">
    <body>You'll be fine if you hold. I was in the red by a lot for months, now I'm way up. They're an underrated company, but at the end of the day the market does as it does. 

I think a good report on 25/02 is already priced in, but news on ADRs and/or substantial US investor would send it higher.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="25" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 21:24:23+10:00">
  <body>XST/SGC -

Either I'm missing something or people are misunderstanding what is happening with XST/SGC. The Borba 1-7 well is not the end of the story, its the start and we haven't even started drilling yet. It was always intended that Borba 1-7 would "open-up" a greater TCF play. I don't think a multi tcf single well was ever on the cards. If you look at the earlier Dempsey prospect, it was always touted as a 1+TCF play and they ended up spudding multiple wells.

You'll note that the resource report (which is usually conservative in its numbers) shows a 70% chance of success with the company indicating it expects an 80% chance of development - these numbers are high. 

Going off what the company director is saying there will be more spuds happening after this one (which we're still yet to get results from). From here there should be plenty of announcements coming through in the next 30 days or so from actual drilling results. 

Now, I'm always hesitant to try to calculate the worth of something like a natural gas well as I'm not a geologist and there's probably more to it than just taking the amount of gas and multiplying it by the price of gas, but doing so gives the below results: 

Gas price avg = A$5/Mcf (thousand cubic feet) 

XST/SGC split = 38/75 Bcf  

XST share in $ = A$190 million (MC of 32 mil) 

SGC share in $ = A$375 million (MC of 40 mil) 

This is for 1 well. 

Potentially there is more that I'm not seeing but it seems to me that even off the Borba 1-7 well, the SP should grow substantially for both companies once they actually start making money off these wells.

Please let me know if there is something wrong with my math or any massive inaccuracies in what I've said.

Edit: As expected, my math is off. They have 70% CoS for 10.3/19.5Bcf respectively. Recalculated, this gives $51.5 mil and $97.5 mil. These numbers still seem pretty good at their current MC's.</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 21:40:28+10:00">
   <body>You’re using the wrong numbers from the report. It’s actually a 70% chance of 19.5bcf for SGC and 10.3bcf for XST - see page 5 of SGC’s report and page 3 of XST’s. 

You have to use these numbers because these are the numbers that account for the different layers. The higher numbers aren’t adjusted for the probability of each layer. 

The 141bcf total figure is the total for all layers ignoring the fact that each layer has its own probability of success. It’s not as simple as “70% chance of 141bcf” and despite what you read on here and HC the report doesn’t actually say that.

A lot of people think the report is overly conservative and that may or may not be right, but if you’re going to do the sums based on the report at least use the right figures.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 21:53:43+10:00">
    <body>Ahh okay, that makes sense. So essentially its saying they have a 70% chance of recovering $51.5 mil (XST)/97.5 mil (SGC) worth of gas each. I've had a look at other resource reports and it seems that 70% CoS is quite high. 

What do you make of future drills in this area? The MD seems very bullish on it. It seems that this is kind of a proof of concept to show that there is recoverable gas in this area.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 21:59:51+10:00">
     <body>I honestly don’t know what to think. I’ve got a small amount of SCG that I’m willing to lose if it’s a duster, and I’m just going to let the drilling speak for itself.

People have a lot of strong options either way so I’m done speculating on Borba. I’m just locked and loaded. I only wanted to correct your numbers so that you knew better what you were looking at.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="choomby93" created="2021-02-21 22:04:15+10:00">
      <body>Yeah its for sure a high risk play - i think peoples expectations for the resource report were a bit unrealistic. I've got small amounts in both and happy to hold through drill results. Cheers for the correction!</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 22:13:47+10:00">
       <body>I’ll also add that no one really knows what’s down there - even the independent expert. Could be more could be less could be nothing. 

So a big success could involve more than the predicted bcf each - but there’s only one way to find out and anything else is true speculation at this point!</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-22 01:36:30+10:00">
     <body>Is not 70% its multiple lots of 17% chance.

So TECHNICALLY it works to be 70% but math doesn't always work out that way.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:45:44+10:00">
   <body>I definitely read the report as fine news, and am happy to hold out. It's a huge loss for me so far but I know it's worth more than that it is now.

Just a sit and wait game. I honestly think my XST is a very long hold.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="wednesdaythefrog" created="2021-02-22 06:11:35+10:00">
   <body>Hey mate, just a quick pointer - although it's easy to just calculate the gross estimated gas by current gas prices - the reality is, is that it's not free to pump out. Try using the net present value formula to expense out the cost of production and to ensure that it's economical.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-22 07:12:40+10:00">
    <body>Careful - people don’t want real numbers they only want good news. I typed up a NPV calculation for SGC (on Hot Copper don’t shame me lol) and it upset someone so much that they followed me to here to accuse me of setting up a scam.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="lycheeboi21" created="2021-02-21 19:42:27+10:00">
  <body>I hope LRS is even better than ADN so it doesn't end up like XST</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-02-21 20:12:43+10:00">
   <body>Agreed</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:35:56+10:00">
   <body>Don't curse it</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="26" downs="0" author="dlaybruh" created="2021-02-21 17:35:17+10:00">
  <body>CRO &amp; LRS ... if ya know 🤷‍♂️</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SaltyAlert" created="2021-02-21 17:59:57+10:00">
   <body>Be interesting to see how CRO settles up post CR</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="dlaybruh" created="2021-02-21 18:04:59+10:00">
    <body>I’d say we’ll end up positive as it’s a Cornerstone Investor &amp; with the webinar the following day and a merger with appstablishment in the near sight, just solid news to come! 🙏</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ubiquitouswede" created="2021-02-21 18:08:57+10:00">
     <body>Yep, CRO is refuelling on the way to Pluto! 🚀🚀🚀</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SnooOwls5021" created="2021-02-21 20:59:25+10:00">
   <body>Too late to invest in CRO? Or nah</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="dlaybruh" created="2021-02-21 21:04:04+10:00">
    <body>Mid-Long Term, nah... Short Term; could be</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SnooOwls5021" created="2021-02-21 21:04:33+10:00">
     <body>Lol I’m scared if I buy tomorrow I could lose lol</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-21 19:18:13+10:00">
  <body>Rare earth prices booming on China supply jawboning

IXR 

Bout to drop 2 mega announcements on JORC resource increase, and financial scoping study, that will confirm this as the largest and premier rare earth project outside China.

Cashed up fully after recent CR, with $12-14mil in the kitty 

This is going to pop, hard</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mouthpiecenomnom" created="2021-02-21 20:58:47+10:00">
   <body>You sum of the beach. I mean.


Love a good dumbfuck small cap trend play.

Edit.   Good volume hell ya batman!


Edit 2:   ruh roh  all time high share price makes my pee-pee soft.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:12:15+10:00">
   <body>I’m big kev excited. Now one of my biggest holdings and strongest conviction plays.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Forumbane" created="2021-02-21 22:37:00+10:00">
   <body>Dangit, thought I had a good position in the rare earth sector holding LYC and VML, now I have to research this too.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-02-21 20:14:37+10:00">
   <body>Didn’t realise there were two an due</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-21 20:23:56+10:00">
    <body>Yep. One before end Feb, and one by end Mar

Exciting times to be onboard !!</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-02-21 20:25:47+10:00">
     <body>Very excited indeed</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TinyParamedic" created="2021-02-21 22:23:25+10:00">
   <body>Haven't really looked into it, but bigger than Lynas?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-22 07:08:51+10:00">
    <body>Different style of project, different type of rare earth deposit. 
LYC is hard rock, it’s higher grade but more expensive to process and refine and ultimately less profitable per kg. They have already invested billions getting it to this stage 

IXR is ionic clay, you essentially just lightly treat the ore to separate the REE. Easier processing means MUCH lower capex, and ultimately higher returns. It’s also going to be a monster resource life beyond 25-30yrs. 
Capped at only $150m this is entry level buying here</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-21 20:10:11+10:00">
  <body>I dipped a toe into crypto and made money on the weekend. Doesn't even come  close to the loss i made on Friday . I forgot how bad it was and when i checked i thought I'd logged onto someone elses account. 

My predictions for the week? Stonks gonna stonk.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:21:14+10:00">
   <body>Good luck mate, it’s a whole new world. 

I’ve got mates up 7 digits in crypto that have been trying to get me in but I won’t allow myself to as I’ll never switch off.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-02-21 20:25:17+10:00">
    <body>Yeah pretty much

Had to stop cause stocks + crypto means its a 24/7 game</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:26:49+10:00">
     <body>Especially with its level of volatility it’s not for the faint hearted</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:47:38+10:00">
      <body>I bought BTC at the last ATH and it promptly plummeted. I held the bag until it hit a new ATH slightly above the old one and let me sell for a small profit. The whole thing caused me way more anxiety than it should.

Three days after I sold, Tesla announced their BTC purchase 😬

I don't think it's for me.</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:50:35+10:00">
       <body>My BIL did too. Went from 50k to less than 10k from memory (held other shit as well). HODL’ed that shit and years later he’s now up 20%+ with no plans of selling. Not for me either.</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:57:43+10:00">
        <body>I'll buy back in once the latest hype cools off. God help me but I actually think BTC has some sort of future. I don't know what, just that it does</body>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 22:10:21+10:00">
         <body>Don’t worry, you’re not the only one!</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:05:42+10:00">
       <body>Sounds exactly like how asx stonks perform, why diversify?</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-22 05:59:15+10:00">
        <body>Yeah but on steroids. They can swing 30-50% and multiply in a much shorter time compared to small caps. 

Crypto, like gold is also considered a hedge against the stock market which most predict will pullback at some stage.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-22 05:54:41+10:00">
    <body>Switching off is important</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-22 06:00:10+10:00">
     <body>Yes sir, although I rarely switch off from researching stonks haha</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-02-21 20:22:31+10:00">
   <body>Crypto is fun, but you got in at a good time.

I got out last week, when you are dealing with red days in crypto it drops so much faster than stonks</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-22 05:55:40+10:00">
    <body>Yeah i only have 1/10th of my money in crypto. See how it goes</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-02-21 20:11:41+10:00">
   <body>just look at your new laptop and remind yourself of the good days.  They'll come back :)</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-21 20:17:55+10:00">
    <body>Oh yeah, i'm not going to cry or anything but i prefer making money to losing money. 

Also my tears have run dry...</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:47:57+10:00">
     <body>The market'll do that to ya</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-21 21:03:42+10:00">
   <body>Good on ya. I spent this morning reading up on crypto and thinking about diving in.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-22 05:57:07+10:00">
    <body>Check out our sister subreddit cryptobets.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-22 06:49:25+10:00">
     <body>Thanks mate but that was the first place I went for 'research'...and it was surprisingly helpful 🤔</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-22 07:06:19+10:00">
      <body>Technically we are breaking a rule chatting about crypto here</body>
      <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-22 07:23:32+10:00">
       <body>You're right. We're not noobs so we better set an example.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-21 18:18:06+10:00">
  <body>Uranium fam ☢☢☢ 

Its gonna be a better week! Monday should be green for most. The Global X Uranium ETF was up 3.3% when trading in the US on Friday. 

Hopefully this translates to a good start. But honestly- the ASX is almost as autist as us so who the fuck knows.</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 18:23:18+10:00">
   <body>Bear in mind that ETF fell about 5% the day before so we shouldn't be expecting ATH prices tomorrow, most likely some sideways movement, keep an eye on the Aus coalition trying to push their pro nuclear agenda forwards, still unsure how that will play out</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Steponmy92" created="2021-02-21 20:17:43+10:00">
    <body>Should go through sometime this week (or get rejected). I think it's annoying that some gas and coal power is being lumped in as well. For my own sake I am hoping it goes through. Looks like it could go either way right now.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Forumbane" created="2021-02-21 23:05:19+10:00">
    <body>Super interested in nuclear power as I believe it the best way to reduce CO2 but even if the laws change it will likely be many years before there are active plants here imo.

Not convinced it will be a huge boom for uranium though as nuclear power plants don't use that much uranium really (I know it takes more raw uranium to enrich to 3-20% U235), more interested in what else would boom from nuclear power.

I expect they will use foreign companies to construct plants/enrichment facilities? and do you think the plants will be publicly or privately run?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Jedsimpson96" created="2021-02-21 20:29:15+10:00">
   <body>DYL all day</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="smileedude" created="2021-02-22 08:42:44+10:00">
  <body>Let's not pretend we're all not refreshing commsec on a Monday morning waiting for an announcement saying "\[ticker you own\] has done very good thing that everyone likes"</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 20:52:28+10:00">
  <body>Repost from weekend thread since I put at least 5 mins effort into this: 

Hopefully some bounce on EV plays early next week!

LKE looks poised - may look to grab some more with the market continuing to anticipate the NVX test announcement. Still huge volume on the ASX and on the OTC markets - love this bad boy.

CXO could really use a bounce - can’t see it below the cap raise price (25c) for much longer. It should have some support here (hopefully) - doubling down could be on the cards for me.

Considering consolidating my manganese plays into just E25 - their latest presso looks absolutely prime

On a non EV front - DW8 saved me from big blushes late last week and hopefully it can continue. Probably my favourite growth stonk

PEN bouncing violently off 14 on Fri arvo was a thing of beauty - hopefully we get some tailwind from the new OTC listing and spring to a higher high. Nice volume on it so far on the new OTC listing - ASX investors are still frothing it too which is nice to see.

I was bringing people’s attention to it a couple weeks ago but now it’s for real - tin prices are mooning with futures up 11% last week. With the upcoming electronics boom, Myanmar coup (3rd largest tin producer) and current tiny supply levels - it would be an absolute travesty if we didn’t see some significant pump on some ASX tin plays. SRZ and VMS worth a look imo for speccy big upside. Will be slapping the ask on Mon.

RBL - get me the fuck out hahaha. MS established a sub holding at high $5s late last week post the results dump so I’m hanging my hat on that for now. Need the volume to sustain into next week and hopefully cash out toward mid-6s.

BOL DYOR etc. Moon soon 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Atmo_" created="2021-02-21 21:21:31+10:00">
   <body>Why are you bearish on RBL? Last results looked good plus Biden stimulus in coming soon which means more money for consumers to spend on e-commerce sites. Plus a positive buy rating from GS. What am I missing?</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:29:43+10:00">
    <body>Results are fine - they don’t justify soaring to new heights though by any means in my opinion.  I don’t see this next half being close to this - results seemed bloated with high margin mask sales in Q1. Personally was hoping for 55ish million EBIT. Q2 being lower than Q1 despite Halloween, Cyber Monday and Christmas was pretty disappointing I gotta say. The 12 month $7.11 price target from GS seems extremely reasonable. Wouldn’t say I’m bearish - I think you can make money by buying around here but I’m not optimistic about pumping anywhere near as hard as last year</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 21:59:08+10:00">
     <body>Mmmmm thats what people keep saying but it went from $1 to $7. I thought the results were great and bought on the weakness.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BeagleJools" created="2021-02-21 21:41:42+10:00">
   <body>E25 is solid. Been slowly adding since December.

Basically;
-starting production next few weeks
-great growth plan- plenty of upside with high purity manganese (green thanks to CSIRO and long term renewable power plans)
-low SOI- through low dilution and some shrewd investments.
-Low MC v stage 2 NPV.

They've gone from explorer to producer inside 12 months. I was fairly skeptical after watching their earlier Crux interviews but they've delivered.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Forumbane" created="2021-02-21 22:24:03+10:00">
    <body>Yep I researched E25 over the weekend and gonna grab some next week</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 23:20:34+10:00">
    <body>Just looked at E25. Very interesting but i dont have to time to plow through all info atm. 
Stage 1 is going to be completed in Q1 this year and i believe already has offtake for 100%. The npv is 500m for just stage 1 but MC does not seem to reflect this even though project is heavily derisked, what is suppressing the SP?

What is the ebit that will be generated from stage 1?

How likely can they produce high purity Manganese for battery use?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="BeagleJools" created="2021-02-22 02:28:34+10:00">
     <body>Not sure why the sp is suppressed. As for the ebit, we'll find out over the next two quarters. It'll supposedly pay for stage 2.
They've stated in interviews that high purity manganese can be generated more environmentally friendly and cheaper than China. They're really starting to push their green credentials now and there will be a PFS out for this later this year. I'm optimistic given what they've achieved so far.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:53:29+10:00">
   <body>MLX is my current DD win going forward from this week. Tin is about to be big</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:28:17+10:00">
   <body>VMS is due to run but looks like it’s potentially drifting back to CR price of 5.5. Market is being impatient with quite a few CR shares still to go through from memory, maybe 1-2 weeks worth at least. 

I made the mistake of not buying enough below 5.5 last dip. I won’t be making that same mistake again.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:32:33+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I’ll be watching closely - more interested in adding to my SRZ holding as of right now with a nice dip on Fri.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:37:02+10:00">
     <body>Not familiar with SRZ but looking at its chart, it’s a volatile fucker lots of big red candles but still trending up. 

Currently sitting on the EMA which it’s bounced off each and every time since it started running. Could be a good spot for an entry/top up.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:40:27+10:00">
      <body>Definitely a big speccy play - some salty legacy holders are suppressing what feels like an inevitable pump. If it opens 26/27 tomorrow I’ll be throwing the dice (again)</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:45:24+10:00">
       <body>I might do some digging and join you.</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="borkdpasito" created="2021-02-21 21:47:12+10:00">
        <body>Best of luck if you take the plunge - of course DYOR</body>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 21:48:05+10:00">
         <body>You too mate. Always do 👍</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-22 07:02:25+10:00">
   <body>Do you think AVZ gets overlooked as a tin speccie? Potentially 3rd largest Tin resource in the world and currently being confirmed with drill assays.

AVZ major resource and future revenue will mainly come from lithium (spodumene) and may pose a socioeconomic risk as the mine will be built in the DRC. 

Once Tin offtakes and future lithium offtakes are announced, this will signifcantly derisk the projects and with AVZ being in a great position purely based on having both tin and lithium prices flying-to me it seems there is alot of money to be made.

Not sure if people are sleeping on this company or if investors are waiting for signifcant derisking announcements like offtake ane final investment decisions.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="ASisko" created="2021-02-21 21:51:18+10:00">
  <body>Last week my momentum and google trends scans called out IOU, DOU and Z1P. IOU and Z1P did OK but you would have to get in early on Monday. DOU did spike on Monday too but finished the week down. I didn't do anything with the info.

This week my picks are MXC, NOV and LKE.

Positions: I already hold LKE.

I also predict that PEN holders will be happy with the week and FFG will go up even though it has no right to do so.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:40:53+10:00">
   <body>Got myself some PEN, but I think we're a couple weeks away from any substantial movement.

My picks for the week ahead are LRS, MLX, and DW8.

Only have LRS myself. MLX is looking to be my next long hold. DW8 I'm hoping to drop a grand on for a very quick sell later in the week. DW8 will be pumped I think</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-22 05:43:35+10:00">
   <body>Any DD available for NOV?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ASisko" created="2021-02-22 07:18:58+10:00">
    <body>No DD, this is a pure momentum and sentiment analysis.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 17:19:20+10:00">
  <body>This week is going to be a good week. I can't tell you how I know, but I definitely feel it.
Not a ridiculously good week, but a very good week.

I also predict cannabis to be down 😟</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-21 17:33:34+10:00">
   <body>When i saw scomo getting the jab on the news i thought...oh yeah..the market will like this #tendies</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-21 18:15:58+10:00">
   <body>Down in your lungs?</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 18:17:44+10:00">
    <body>Down everywhere.
Totally unrelated feeling to today being my first day of a 3 week holiday from work</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-22 06:44:57+10:00">
     <body>Whats the best canabis stock for me to jump on? Will DMOR of course.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 07:46:01+10:00">
      <body>My money is in LGP, plenty of positives to read into and good future plans.

It's only problem is that it's playing too aggressive. Yearly spending is just about doubling every year. I can't see it being profitable for a while though it's definitely starting to do some good deals.

So it's gamble - if they start making serious money to offset what they spend 🚀🚀🚀.
If not, well they'll get the money by diluting you back to the stoner age.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-22 07:47:54+10:00">
       <body>really does sound like a gamble</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 17:21:26+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 17:21:27+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-22 08:46:45+10:00">
  <body>Maybe people would be interested in a counter-DD post? Why would you NOT invest in this company?</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-22 08:50:39+10:00">
   <body>I love em. But instead of just shitting all over it. It’s probably better to present both positives and negatives in the format</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Voldemortina" created="2021-02-22 08:58:01+10:00">
   <body>You'll get downvoted to heck by people who own the stock.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 09:09:48+10:00">
   <body>A really good VAL DD was posted yesterday, final conclusion being is a dog. It was a good read and I would like to see more of it. Pretty much every obscure DD I've done has returned negative, and I just moved on. Perhaps i can contribute to this place by helping others not waste time</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 17:54:04+10:00">
  <body>Been accumulating more TLG. Currently the only and possibly the largest graphite resource with vertically integrated anode production in Europe – where EV transition will be spearheaded. Tier-1 mining jurisdiction in Sweden. 

Anode/graphite material makes up a large volume/weight of the Lithium-ion battery but has generally been the less talk of all battery materials even though demand is also projected to eclipse supply. BUT recently there has been a strong increase in interest and price actions across all Graphite/Anode players. Some Graphite stocks in the US has been going gangbuster. TLG is well set up to take advantage of this being the potentially largest graphite/anode player in Europe. Someone going to need to supply the demand…outside China.

DFS for the ‘initial’ 20k tpa anode production (NOT graphite but anode material) expected in March 2021 and that should result in price action, follow by hopefully binding JV with LKAB (Swedish mining company) and Mitsui. Further scoping study has been done to potentially increase this production up to 100k tpa. 

Anyway, obligatory rockets  🚀  🚀  🚀</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 18:52:17+10:00">
   <body>I’ve got such high hopes for TLG. If they do what they plan to it’s easily a 10 bagger from here. Still risk in execution of the plans but huge potential payoff.

There’s a talga subreddit now. Good collection of articles and info

https://www.reddit.com/r/talga/</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Luxim_" created="2021-02-21 19:45:50+10:00">
   <body>Is $1.50 a decent entry price for TLG?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-02-21 19:54:55+10:00">
    <body>Yes. It’s unlikely to drop lower than that since *I think* they handed out a shit load at that price not too long ago. They’ve been in the $1.50 - 1.60 noose for a while now. According to HC , It’s a popular shorted stock atm.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 20:00:48+10:00">
     <body>The short i believe is very inconsequential at 0.02%.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 20:13:42+10:00">
      <body>Shorting has to be the most misunderstood thing on hot copper (and it’s a low bar). Unbelievable how many times shorters get blamed for a drop in share price and like you say, you check the short interest and it’s practically nothing.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-21 19:59:30+10:00">
    <body>My view yes. It has the 1.45 CR support. And there will be a few catalysts coming up soon.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-21 20:09:28+10:00">
    <body>I think so, I’ve gone in for 150k shares +/- a few cents either side of $1.50

I don’t think it’s going to rocket though, just steady increases over the next 2-3 years as milestones are reached and the projects get de-risked</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="yogaisnow" created="2021-02-21 20:52:03+10:00">
   <body>I’m also in on TLG, very organic growth and the managing director seems to know what he’s doing. Their site in Sweden has been labeled as ‘national significance’ and LKAB is a owned by the Swedish govt - this stock is going to be huge in a few years time I can see US listing in the future. HOLD! 💎🙌🏻</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Briskey_Business" created="2021-02-21 18:01:44+10:00">
  <body>Might try and hop aboard this LKE rocket seems like people are pumped on it :)</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-21 20:06:36+10:00">
   <body>Seems like people are pumping it... corrected your spelling there</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="platypusreacharound" created="2021-02-22 05:52:09+10:00">
    <body>I assumed he meant, people are 'jacked' on it. Like, I want to inject some sweet LKE into the veins on my forehead. Makes sense.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-22 06:00:24+10:00">
     <body>It's all Greek to me</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:44:54+10:00">
   <body>Honestly scared of it, lots of pump and hype but I only read negative stuff from a lot of more established retards</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="angelusinc" created="2021-02-22 05:50:57+10:00">
    <body>Like what? I'm in LKE for the long run but I'd like to hear the other side. Where do we see this going bad?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="SAIUN666" created="2021-02-21 23:24:30+10:00">
  <body>Thoughts on the following tickers? SUK MUH BLS</body>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="NickM5526" created="2021-02-21 23:26:34+10:00">
   <body>DIQ ENN BLS always look good this time of year. Recommend getting in while it’s down cos once it starts going up it gets harder to not FOMO

VUJ EYE NUH is also really tempting to get into. Looks enticing, very rarely ends up being a mistake. It typically only goes into the red like once a month.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-22 07:19:26+10:00">
    <body>Lmfao</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:10:51+10:00">
    <body>My wife's boyfriend is into VUJ EYE NUH, he's doing great.

I'm in FKN KIL MEE OWN XST.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="uberloser2" created="2021-02-21 23:33:19+10:00">
   <body>go all in CBT</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="tofuroll" created="2021-02-22 08:17:05+10:00">
   <body>I prefer the taste of BTY SWT.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-21 18:04:03+10:00">
  <body>I'm going to watch nvx rise without me because I can't bring myself to sell any dw8 or lke to fund a buy in.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 08:42:59+10:00">
  <body>Thoughts on XYZ this morning? Their price is 0.420 but I think it really deserves to be the next APT at $420

Will it go up or down? I hear there could be an announcement soon, or not</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="phantom_hax0r" created="2021-02-22 08:50:47+10:00">
   <body>I see they just dropped an announcement, I haven't read it but what do we all think, is the announcement good? It says record earnings but the price went down wtf is happening? Thoughts on XYZ? 🚀🚀🚀 why are people buying it for $5 when the price is $4.20?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 08:55:47+10:00">
    <body>[Literally](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lord70/comment/go9zwut?context=3&amp;sort=new) 5 comments above</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="phantom_hax0r" created="2021-02-22 09:02:06+10:00">
     <body>[This too](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lord70/premarket_thread_for_general_trading_and_plans/go9yfkl)</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-02-21 17:14:10+10:00">
  <body>Finger my ass hole</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-21 20:17:34+10:00">
   <body>Flair checks out</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-21 18:30:03+10:00">
   <body>ok bb</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-02-21 21:11:14+10:00">
   <body>Not until you post some DD to convince me</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="willy2milly" created="2021-02-21 20:16:36+10:00">
  <body>Excited to see how nvx and lke will do this week. Lot of hype around lke, should go for a nice good run tomorrow</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="MachinaDoctrina" created="2021-02-22 07:02:39+10:00">
   <body>let's hope its not just a pump and dump</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 22:53:52+10:00">
  <body>So the latest small cap I've become intrigued by over the past week is **CGO**:

[https://www.marketindex.com.au/asx/cgo](https://www.marketindex.com.au/asx/cgo)

They provide IT systems and services mainly to the banking industry with revenue that's gone from $12.1 million over a *full year* to $18.1 mill in a *half year*, and 3 years straight of increasing profit... from $0.9 million profit the full previous year to $3 million profit in the last 6 months; "*Net Profit after tax attributable to members up 159.8%."*

Also growing in the US.

One I'll be keeping a close eye on, hopefully SP will drop down a little after its really strong report last week and then I may look to buy in.</body>
  <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:07:46+10:00">
   <body>To many potential stocks, not enough money</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 23:17:42+10:00">
    <body>\^ words which will be written on my tombstone</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="NickM5526" created="2021-02-21 23:34:48+10:00">
   <body>Who’s this seems like a great stock! $0.02/share in dividends for a 0.33 SP? That’s a $60 dividend payment for just $1000 investment if my math is correct.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="scienceofthelambs" created="2021-02-22 06:00:36+10:00">
   <body>Why was it at $0.90 in 2014 and subsequently dropped to $0.30?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 08:33:40+10:00">
  <body>TNT 🚀🚀🚀

Suck my balls Automod you'll do fookin nuttin</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mOOse32" created="2021-02-22 08:44:36+10:00">
   <body>An mma fan too i see, a man of culture.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Baz30066" created="2021-02-21 21:12:05+10:00">
  <body>BPH 🚀🚀: Nopta imminent lol (for 37th time)</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:48:48+10:00">
   <body>Hurry the fuck up. I hate this stock.

Very tired of reading about benign prostatic hyperplasia while trying to find the report. I want my bag now!</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-02-22 05:10:34+10:00">
    <body>Bags. Plural.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="BigKevStocking" created="2021-02-22 07:37:31+10:00">
     <body>Hodl?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-22 05:45:50+10:00">
   <body>https://www.abc.net.au/radio/newcastle/programs/drive/keith-pitt-pep11/13168022

Come on Keith - enough foreplay! We know you want to approve PEP11 just do it</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Baz30066" created="2021-02-22 05:46:34+10:00">
    <body>I agree - I am fully teased and ready to go</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="dahmachino" created="2021-02-21 18:06:22+10:00">
  <body>Keen to see the FOMO HYPE PUMP on LKE, hoping it does an IOU or a CRO make some mad gains and buy back in.
I'll be watching my 88E shares from the closet almost always wearing my superman costume to see how much hype it gets this week, as they have mobilised their drilling equipment and will start drilling in a couple weeks.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 19:26:51+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 19:26:52+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-21 19:49:44+10:00">
  <body>I am Xoping SomeThing good happens!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="kooksy_monster" created="2021-02-21 17:37:40+10:00">
  <body>Watching MNS, LKE and TNT and looking for a decent entry into any. LKE did me rough on Friday. I'm still shook.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-21 17:49:37+10:00">
   <body>TNT looking as good as it has over the past 6 months for an entry. Got a feeling some good news has to be around the corner soon.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kooksy_monster" created="2021-02-21 17:56:14+10:00">
    <body>Yeah man, bit of a paper handed affair with me selling the fuck load I was holding 🤷‍♂️ that 50% CGT discount wouldve been okay but I was recovering from a zip loss. Another paper handed affair 🤷‍♂️🤷‍♂️</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-21 18:10:46+10:00">
     <body>Nah this is a long termer for me. At least until the possibility of a CyberCX IPO, but don’t see that happening. I really like this company. Can’t see why we wouldn’t be 60c+ by EOCY</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-02-21 18:10:29+10:00">
    <body>Yeah tnt just going sideways lately . I really thought it was be higher as it is biggest cyber security and has tnt in the name 

Oh well I’ll still hold</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="kooksy_monster" created="2021-02-21 18:17:31+10:00">
     <body>The latter is 90% of the reason I got into the company 😏</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="heavy798" created="2021-02-21 20:08:45+10:00">
  <body>Looks like China is building new shit on their artificial islands

Gonna buy war stocks I think</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:48:27+10:00">
   <body>The way humans behave, always a safe bet</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:06:10+10:00">
   <body>DRO!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="DogLogik" created="2021-02-21 22:24:38+10:00">
  <body>If some stocks would hurry the fuck up and deliver their "imminent" results in less than a week my portfolio might actually be all green tomorrow.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-22 06:20:09+10:00">
  <body>I've got an uncomfortably bad feeling about today for no logical reason... Am I the only one?</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-22 06:31:17+10:00">
   <body>You are not the only one.  It feels like this week could be market correction week</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="tinfoilturducken" created="2021-02-22 07:26:34+10:00">
    <body>Lol, what was last week then?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-22 07:30:25+10:00">
     <body>A heads up with what's to come.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:04:13+10:00">
   <body>You're wrong mate. Today is going to nice</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-22 07:27:23+10:00">
   <body>how come? US wasn't too bad on Friday. Can't see today being any worse than last Friday here.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Trickyleaf" created="2021-02-21 18:27:49+10:00">
  <body>Anyone buying the IOU dip this week?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mirage1942" created="2021-02-21 21:06:10+10:00">
   <body>...are they still releasing the extra shares tomorrow ???</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Trickyleaf" created="2021-02-21 21:11:13+10:00">
    <body>On Thursday I believe, I’m loading up as there BNPL plan will be rolled out soon</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mirage1942" created="2021-02-21 21:25:29+10:00">
     <body>Thanks....will wait until then......the extra shares worry me a bit....</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-21 22:13:35+10:00">
      <body>its already priced in</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="pammyc103" created="2021-02-21 22:35:20+10:00">
      <body>the whole thing worries me a bit.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-21 22:03:24+10:00">
    <body>the capital raise already priced in with drop on thurs/fri.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="StinkyFatWhale" created="2021-02-22 07:33:19+10:00">
  <body>Big week on the cards.... Got me excited
Holdings in, CRO, DW8, LKE LRS got my blubber pumping. 

Still holding and got hopes for XST... Just not as high hopes as once was.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:00:08+10:00">
   <body>I do wish I had some CRO.
I scrubbed DW8 from my buy list though, I don't have faith - guaranteed to rocket without me 👍

LRS is my baby.

I'm scared of LkE.

... My week will be pain, but carried on by 2 stocks</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-02-22 08:51:05+10:00">
  <body>Hope &lt;insert my stonk ticker here&gt; goes up today instead of down.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 09:06:47+10:00">
   <body>Fucking oath. What do you think about said stonk?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Qwertyiantne" created="2021-02-22 09:19:41+10:00">
    <body>Stonks I own are good. Stonks I don’t own are bad!!</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 09:20:39+10:00">
     <body>🤯</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="raginglybulk" created="2021-02-21 18:52:42+10:00">
  <body>bought into a pretty speccy miner (rdn), will be interesting to see how it goes

i just fuckin love gambling</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-21 19:25:22+10:00">
   <body>I’m on SI6 completely because of one of their major share holders. Speccy as fuck but nickel is a big deal.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="miamivice85" created="2021-02-21 19:17:35+10:00">
  <body>Loading up IOU at .55 and under..</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="just_just_regrets" created="2021-02-22 07:38:53+10:00">
  <body>How do I spice up my mi go reng help</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Arkillis" created="2021-02-22 07:41:32+10:00">
   <body>Z1P holder cum or XST holder tears</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 07:47:13+10:00">
    <body>I have both!</body>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-02-22 07:52:17+10:00">
   <body>Whilst the water is boiling and the noodles have just been put in, crack an egg into the pot and get about a dash of sesame seed oil in. 2 minutes later just drain and mix in a bowl with the other seasoning packets, the egg should burst and the yolk becomes the base of the sauce.

Important not to over do the noodles, like mine Al dente.</body>
   <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="just_just_regrets" created="2021-02-22 07:57:30+10:00">
    <body>bone apple teeth</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-02-22 08:16:46+10:00">
     <body>But for real though: Sriracha sauce</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="KrondorMocker" created="2021-02-22 08:50:40+10:00">
      <body> But for real REAL though: Cocaine</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-21 17:05:36+10:00">
  <body>As I mentioned previously, [I'm gonna be buying more 4DS](https://9to5mac.com/2021/02/18/biden-admin-investigation-us-semiconductor-supply-chains) Biden EO re: semiconductors</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="CrusaderR4bbit" created="2021-02-21 17:08:47+10:00">
   <body>Are there any specific contracts or connections which 4DS have which would indicate that they will benefit from the EO? Or is this a "rising tide lifts all boats" sort of thing?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Forumbane" created="2021-02-21 22:52:23+10:00">
    <body>4DS not at the production stage yet, check their last announcement it was results of imec tests, looked positive but somewhat vague.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="TauCeti2050" created="2021-02-21 19:57:50+10:00">
  <body>Make stock go up 👁👄👁</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-02-21 20:48:27+10:00">
  <body>I really hope I'm not the only one holding Vr1/NVA.

Every time I sell a stock, it booms right after. I'll be selling one of those (partly if not all) to free up some cash.

If you hold one of those stocks, you can thank me later.</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="zyyes" created="2021-02-21 20:50:59+10:00">
   <body>trust the wombat</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-02-21 21:01:23+10:00">
    <body>Second this</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:00:53+10:00">
   <body>This whole sub is on NVA lol</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:41:13+10:00">
   <body>I'm buying more NVA. Guaranteed a year from now you will regret selling</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ssswarp" created="2021-02-21 21:32:14+10:00">
   <body>Im balls deep in NVA. Keep the faith it will boom</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-21 22:34:10+10:00">
   <body>Im in NVA too. Market is being very cruel to it based on gold slipping down to 1700s, and just generally quite undervalued. Waiting for April MRE to see some significant movement hopefully.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-02-22 06:32:25+10:00">
  <body>Hoping for some recovery in two infamous pumpy old world energy explorer stocks so that I can use that green to gtfo and get into that green ☢️.

Meanwhile, mostly free carrying lke (bagged but took out a bit less than investment) so just hoping I don't regret taking that out.

In general trying to find exit opportunities to consolidate my penny stocks a bit</body>
  <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 06:38:13+10:00">
   <body>Start stroking that PEN ☢️☢️☢️</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-22 07:13:30+10:00">
    <body>My PEN went soft last week on Friday morning but by days end my PEN went HARD. Never regret holding Uranium, they're the only stocks which are quite stable and are growing consistently (Holding PEN BOE LOT)</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-02-22 07:13:47+10:00">
    <body>Feels like a storm's brewin'. Not the kind that left Texas in the dark with no power, but a bit like that.

The energy producers are gonna be looking at Biden and the spot price and their reserves and the new plants and soon their math is going to start falling the same way as yours. They're gonna want to lock this in before (/in case) it goes much higher.

Edit: the reverse-rocket US dollar is going to be making them nervous too</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 07:17:32+10:00">
     <body>I wouldn't take anything for granted, renewable energy sources are significantly cheaper to implement and run than Nuclear Power. 

However, I do believe that we will see governments granting extensions on the operating lifetimes of existing Nuclear plants to meet their carbon emission goals and that Nuclear Power is irreplacable as a carbon free power source that can produce electricity regardless of geography (hydro) or weather conditions (solar, wind)</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 07:31:52+10:00">
  <body>Trading all night in my dreams - still did shit. Gonna try hard to remember the stock names and see if they are real</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="comninos" created="2021-02-21 17:13:03+10:00">
  <body>You degenerates have corrupted me im gonna sell my wbc and buy more rac</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-21 22:50:31+10:00">
  <body>Boys I was watching a documentary last night and it got me thinking - it was explaining the parallels of market crashes compared with Today and why the US market is in a bubble about to burst - explaining the relationship of low interest rates &amp; market / housing crashes - also goes into explain how upwards of 40% of every dollar the US has printed in history has been printed in the last 12 months - all major US shares are trading at 100% plus comparative of price recommendation based on PE ratio and goes into detail on many other things- made me think of a Buffet quote “be greedy when people are fearful and fearful when people are greedy” are people greedy now, or fearful?</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:12:13+10:00">
   <body>Greedy for sure, but circumstances now due to Covid aren't something Buffet has experience with.

Greedy and fearful I say.
Sit back, enjoy the bull, don't risk what you can't lose</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="buffalo_bill27" created="2021-02-22 07:12:22+10:00">
    <body>I agree. The post-war formula has basically stayed the same until this point.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-21 23:12:14+10:00">
   <body>I think there's a case to be made for interest rates being probably the strongest driver of equity prices. I also think that when controlling for current interest rates, prices aren't actually so sky high that we need to worry. Interest rates have never been this low. It makes sense that equities have never been this high. But i could be wrong im just a tard only learning trading the last year.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-21 23:43:29+10:00">
    <body>Imagine it like this - you take out a $500,000 loan now to buy a $600,000 house 🏠 at a .5% rate. Next year if interests rates rise to 3% your premium is now way up and the price of your house is down and people lose out on everything because they can’t afford to pay back loans and they take a big loss on the house if they sell</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-21 23:46:38+10:00">
     <body>Sure, but whats causing the boom is that the RBA has promised to keep rates nailed to the floor untill at least 2024....and im guessing it will probably go beyond. It might just be the way things are for along time.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-21 23:59:36+10:00">
      <body>To play devils advocate you could also say as long as the US keeps printing money and as long as they can pay their debts in US dollars the circus will continue. Still we all know the market tends to do the opposite of what we expect. Right now people seem confident the bull run will continue on. I’m not so confident.</body>
      <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-22 00:08:53+10:00">
       <body>To be fair the market has a 200 year history of trending upward. At the end of the day i'm personally not that stressed about it. I only really buy long 3/5/10 year holds...mostly etfs...and i honestly would welcome a monster 25% correction. I'm holding enough cash out of the market such that if any positions correct i'd just buy more. And again. Im fairly sure people arent giving enough credit to how hard interest rates drive prices. "Interest rates are everything" - Warren Buffett.</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-22 00:11:29+10:00">
        <body>Then your doing the right things - all this post really is for is to highlight people should have savings on deck ready for a monster correction but at the end of the day if your willing to hold for a few years you will be fine either way</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-21 23:27:37+10:00">
    <body>I will add that thats why have gone pretty deep on A200 because i think the full force of interest rates being planted to the ground is going to send the ASX through the roof for one of its best years this year. (i hope)</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-21 23:17:19+10:00">
   <body>You're not wrong, although it's hard to say what will happen to Aus when the US markets crashed, but take a look at SP500 and ASX200 weekly charts.

My uneducated guess is, when the US market crashes, Australia will too, but recover quicker, and many govs around the world will start pivoting to the new mega consumer economy - China. Do note that this sentiment has nothing to do with politics, just money.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Willing-Painting9991" created="2021-02-21 23:52:36+10:00">
    <body>I hope you are correct...i've gone dangerously deep on the ASIA ETF</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-22 07:07:57+10:00">
     <body>I think in the long term your pick will be correct, but don't forget that when the US catch a cold, the rest of the world sneeze</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-21 23:47:25+10:00">
    <body>Australia is a pin point in the international financial system so what is happening in US is extremely relevant to the rest of us . I agree with you we will recover quicker but it would be very ugly still we would also lose out big time on trade and your exactly right that would lead to much heavier Australian reliance on communist China. People are definitely greedy right now and everything is over valued I will start taking some profit and set up PUts in some US shares</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="andysev89" created="2021-02-22 07:07:21+10:00">
    <body>Old saying, when America sneezes, Australia will catch a cold. Basically talking how close we are tied together, however our markets are radically different and this was shown in the 2008 GFC, but your summation is pretty much right, except for the China part IMO. I think China is getting desperate as they have been burning their economy hard for the last 20 years, whether it's resources or labour, i do think they have another 10 or so years to consolidate their power. But China is China and i could be 100% wrong.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ASisko" created="2021-02-22 00:15:08+10:00">
   <body>As long as interest rates look like staying low for a long time the bubble can persist. I think at some point from now to 2 years from now we will have signs of inflation and the US Fed will say 'Hey, we might  actually raise rates this decade...', then everything that is priced on a low rate assumption will crash.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-02-22 04:55:40+10:00">
    <body>Rates determine the value of everything. It’s likely (but not certain) we’re going to see a decent re-rate this year. We’re already seeing rates rising. The ones the fed isn’t manipulating. Look at the 10 year bond in the US. Look at other countries. Big spikes.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-22 00:26:38+10:00">
    <body>The market loves certainty so as long as interest rates remain low i think you are right but in Saying that the market always does the opposite of what we think. Everyone is extremely bullish right now it just takes a market shock and it will reverse. It could come in the form of tensions with China or a conflict between China and India. If so it would amplify everything else and we would see a monster correction. Probably we will see a correction in the next 6 months Imo</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Forward_Pirate8615" created="2021-02-21 23:07:05+10:00">
   <body>Everything is overvalued</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="DuckDuckWin" created="2021-02-21 23:07:27+10:00">
   <body>Greedy... which makes me very wary</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-21 23:57:23+10:00">
   <body>https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=2g8PawZIRrk</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="drkmnmnstr" created="2021-02-21 23:48:00+10:00">
   <body>Can you share the link to that particular video? I would love to watch it.  

Just my gut instinct talking, but I think that this bubble will continue to grow for at least 6 more months, even a year or 2. I'm guessing everyone just expects the that the ASX will bounce back really fast like the GFC and last year's crash, that it doesn't really bother us as much now.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Gambin06" created="2021-02-21 23:57:12+10:00">
    <body>https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=2g8PawZIRrk</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="drkmnmnstr" created="2021-02-22 00:01:39+10:00">
     <body>cheers  good sir.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="angelusinc" created="2021-02-22 05:55:43+10:00">
  <body>I'm on the LKE train but I'd like to hear from people who decided to pass on this. I'm trying to find any negative DD but I'm not finding much outside of the fact that Indochine didn't make it, and Steve led that one. Anything else I'm missing?</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-02-22 06:21:15+10:00">
   <body>It was a great call by many here and people that followed that got on the 10c mark. I feel that the upcoming announcement is partially priced in with the current value. People who are calling LKE to hit $1 haven't realised that this will mean LKE at 1B Market cap. Can't see that happening but hey, what do I know.</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 06:53:48+10:00">
    <body>There's a fuck ton of people new here who start screeching about prices with no concept of what a Market Cap is, it's actually doing my brain in.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:05:10+10:00">
     <body>Oh I do need a market cap!
Do you do custom designs?</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="platypusreacharound" created="2021-02-22 08:35:40+10:00">
     <body>I'm in for 2 market caps please.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="angelusinc" created="2021-02-22 06:25:50+10:00">
    <body>Maybe not this year but I ideally want to hold this for like 5-10 years so if we get a few more catalysts and phase into production, I cant see why it won't be at least over $3 by that time. There's just so much more to go. This is still the beginning in my opinion. I can see why day traders may want to stay away though</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="springoniondip" created="2021-02-22 07:31:10+10:00">
     <body>Same with PRL last week, people got in the hype
 and VUL took 3 years to get to the same place I saw this morning. Lots of announcements to come by LKE will take a couple of years</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MachinaDoctrina" created="2021-02-22 06:48:12+10:00">
    <body>VUL has a 750M market cap why not LKE, to be honest LKE is sitting on a larger deposit than VUL</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-02-22 07:44:16+10:00">
     <body>Isn't some of that VUL cap due to ESG bullshit tho</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MachinaDoctrina" created="2021-02-22 07:46:00+10:00">
      <body>Why exactly would that factor into their market cap and not LKE?</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-02-22 08:11:20+10:00">
       <body>Cause of the carbon zero processing method. It's proprietary and adds value.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="boy_pikoy" created="2021-02-22 08:29:28+10:00">
  <body>O'right Lads prepare for the onslaught!! May the your almighty STONKS be blessed by stonk GOds'.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="I_COMPLETE_ME" created="2021-02-22 09:23:23+10:00">
  <body>VML signed drilling contract. Could be on here</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="blvd119" created="2021-02-22 09:56:13+10:00">
   <body>Fomo'd in too late and im still all red. hope they actually do well!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="corneilous_bumfrey" created="2021-02-22 09:56:13+10:00">
   <body>🤞🏼</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="WiseWalrus88" created="2021-02-21 18:02:25+10:00">
  <body>TMZ is gonna be quick out the blocks Monday. All it’s projects commodities have been crushing it lately. Still very undervalued here.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-21 19:10:17+10:00">
   <body>Massively agree with this. Any one of their projects would be worth the market cap alone... let alone gold, copper, silver, Tin optionality

All of their commodity prices are booming as well, except gold looking a bit flat atm. 

Check out the chart of Tin prices!!! Omg</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:53:16+10:00">
    <body>Stop it you're tempting me to double down</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="crookgypsy" created="2021-02-21 18:03:24+10:00">
  <body>ADX, LKE 🤞</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="danbrah1" created="2021-02-21 20:27:26+10:00">
   <body>In your opinion what separates LKE from other lithium miners? It's financials or execration methods ect.?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Crackersnuf" created="2021-02-21 18:25:41+10:00">
  <body>This should be called The Daily Pump</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="rpro13" created="2021-02-21 19:31:47+10:00">
   <body>There is some quality posting between the new Facebook pumpers. Although i think they believe they are being “cheeky” and pretending like we don’t know.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crackersnuf" created="2021-02-21 19:34:19+10:00">
    <body>If some of these overhyped stocks get the positive news all are waiting for, there’s going to be a colossal sell off on the news pump!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="martin0000001" created="2021-02-21 19:10:59+10:00">
   <body>Lol more like miss the pump and cream about the “profits”they could of made</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Steponmy92" created="2021-02-21 17:19:10+10:00">
  <body>Think the renewed Gamestop hype on Wallstreet bets is legit?</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-21 18:09:23+10:00">
   <body>Like Qanon found a pyramid scheme

I think anyone waiting to buy more GME on that sub is also waiting for the tooth fairy to give them the funds to buy partial shares</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="nickmcsnapz" created="2021-02-21 19:00:06+10:00">
   <body>I left wsb after years of being on there due to it just turning into noobs constantly posting shit about GME. The sub is ruined for now.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="seb_dm" created="2021-02-21 19:24:07+10:00">
    <body>Ape stronk though.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SnooRegrets406" created="2021-02-22 05:20:47+10:00">
    <body>Seen r/wallstreetsilver ?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-02-21 17:31:15+10:00">
   <body>Nothing is real</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="noegami" created="2021-02-21 17:40:55+10:00">
    <body>Username checks out</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Nevelo" created="2021-02-21 17:44:11+10:00">
  <body>Watching AGL's slow slide into the abyss</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="chewpstar" created="2021-02-21 17:55:28+10:00">
   <body>Yep me too... wondering whether or not to start buying more to bring my loss average down. I think it has good fundamentals for the longer term hold but not liked by anyone atm</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Nevelo" created="2021-02-21 18:14:30+10:00">
    <body>I think it might go into the 8s eventually.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="chewpstar" created="2021-02-21 18:57:51+10:00">
     <body>Hope not but if u have info to back that statement up I would appreciate it</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Nevelo" created="2021-02-21 19:48:33+10:00">
      <body>* Reduction in earnings next 3 years forecasted. Next year likely -35% earnings of FY20.
* Broker EPS forecast: FY21 85.5c, FY22 60.3c, FY23 46.0c.
* They do have green energy assets and gas power plants, but 85.7% of their power generation FY20 came from coal power. 
* 1 of their 3 coal plants is being shut down next year (Liddell). 
* They are paying 100% of their profit into dividends next couple of years (Don't seem to be investing in future).

There might be a deep value play at the end of this long train to hell, but I suggest you do some serious DD before chasing bad money.

(I'm a retard. Fuck you if you think this is advice.)</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-02-21 19:59:30+10:00">
    <body>you're joking right ?  
Maybe when it hits $2 and they produce a plan to get into this century you might want to think like that.....</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="chewpstar" created="2021-02-22 03:18:59+10:00">
    <body>Food for thought 👍🏽 thanks boys 🤙🏽</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="HCFaktor" created="2021-02-21 19:16:37+10:00">
   <body>Its not a loss til you sell.

*This is what I keep telling myself*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="No_Nefariousness_131" created="2021-02-21 19:46:38+10:00">
  <body>money please</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="dogbobwog" created="2021-02-21 19:54:00+10:00">
  <body>IXR to $1 baby</body>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-02-21 20:12:33+10:00">
   <body>Was hoping to pass the 10c mark first but happy to fly past it</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-21 21:49:08+10:00">
   <body>Why are folks so bullish on IXR? Genuinely curious</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:35:36+10:00">
    <body>The fuck is ixr</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tynub89" created="2021-02-22 05:50:54+10:00">
   <body>IXR is getting good volume and is consistent - rare earth metals is a good long term play but is there any impending news or such for IXR?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-02-21 20:50:56+10:00">
  <body>See if AR9 drops and maybe YOLO in.</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-02-21 21:21:23+10:00">
   <body>I really feel it will tank first half of day. Steady , then end up green . Or do this on Tuesday

The DD is just me being bored, my gf is out with her “friend” again. They spend a lot of time together lately ... hmmm</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-02-21 21:28:53+10:00">
    <body>Sounds like a good friend. You get more time to do DD.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="I_P_L" created="2021-02-22 01:56:56+10:00">
  <body>Really praying that LRS does something this week</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="oldirtydude" created="2021-02-22 07:46:51+10:00">
   <body>I will join you In prayer</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="joefarnarkler" created="2021-02-22 08:23:57+10:00">
  <body>What's the counter narrative on DW8. I read the DD and got excited but I'm very suggestible cause I know jack shit. Now I hear some took away the exact opposite from the DD?</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-22 08:42:21+10:00">
   <body>"Cut out the middle men and replace them with us, men in the middle" got me good</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-22 08:26:31+10:00">
  <body>Hello finance literate people, how does increasing bond yield impact stonks?</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-22 08:36:16+10:00">
   <body>Shhh we don't talk about those market indicators here</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Gidolphin" created="2021-02-22 08:36:14+10:00">
   <body>The short answer is generally not good.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="maybethough" created="2021-02-22 08:36:01+10:00">
   <body>People don't have to go chasing unrisky gains by piling on blue chip stocks anymore, because debt costs/earns money again.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Atmo_" created="2021-02-22 08:55:15+10:00">
   <body>Government bonds are seen as a risk free asset because the US, Aus, UK etc. are not going to default. So it’s a very safe way to park your cash and earn a return. When the interest rate on bonds increase it makes shares look like a less lucrative asset in comparison, hence not good for stonks</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="scorpio_" created="2021-02-21 21:40:03+10:00">
  <body>Third and final call for DW8! Can't wait to see how the unshackled SP will move this week.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:42:10+10:00">
   <body>Jump on board, but don't hold long. This bitch will drop fast.

Money to made, don't get greedy. I might try a grand for about 40%</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 21:57:39+10:00">
   <body>Lol that DD thread made it look pretty bad ngl</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-21 22:18:50+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I agree. For me it went from “I should look into this at some point” to “ok yeah nah”. That’s the risk of a DD pump I guess haha</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FewSoil4973" created="2021-02-21 21:59:43+10:00">
  <body>I'm hoping IOU can get some momentum and push to 80 cents.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="StaffordMagnus" created="2021-02-22 00:59:21+10:00">
   <body>Gunna be interesting to see what happens with this over the next few days, on the downward pressure side is the cap raising, although 50 cents is a good base to work from, on the upside last weeks rocket will have put this ticker on a lot more peoples radar.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Elegantmango77" created="2021-02-21 23:41:07+10:00">
  <body>Watching to top up on NMT, hoping the feasibility study into supplying India’s first lithium refinery gets good news soon, plus they have the factory being setup in Germany to showcase there JV battery recycling plant to recover metals.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-22 07:30:14+10:00">
  <body>LRS pre market auction looks good and shaping up for a gap up...</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="TheCowardMcCall" created="2021-02-22 07:48:28+10:00">
  <body>All my investmenting (gambling) money is tied up... LIT HWK QAN VUL. Need something to go up b4 I can play again 😩</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="djburns19" created="2021-02-22 07:51:58+10:00">
   <body>I am in exactly the same position. I wish I pulled Vulcan at $11 and worked with my profits and allocated a buy back in amount. I guess I don’t know what the future holds so I’m all tied up.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TheCowardMcCall" created="2021-02-22 07:55:42+10:00">
    <body>$11? I woulda been happy pulling out at $9 haha... guess my pull out game isn't as strong as I thought 🥴</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="djburns19" created="2021-02-22 08:01:43+10:00">
     <body>Haha yeh me either. Look at us now, balls deep at $6-$7. 

The other factor for me is that I see it as a medium to long term hold.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TheCowardMcCall" created="2021-02-22 08:05:19+10:00">
      <body>Yeah I don't doubt it'll go up long term, but I wasn't done having short term wins with it lol...</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="CrocodileCracking" created="2021-02-22 08:50:28+10:00">
   <body>Same here. Do you foresee any movements for HWK anytime soon?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-22 08:32:47+10:00">
  <body>Got in NNG on Friday, IPO on Thursday and closed Friday 40% up from IPO price of $0.20.

Reasons

 - price held up well above Thursday's close despite XJO was in deep red on Friday. I took this as a sign of holders not letting go of their shares at current level and have high confidence 

- buy/sell depth added conviction to the above observation 

- about 45% of total 111mil SOI held by top holders and are in escrow, so about 63mil shares to trade on market, relatively small float.

- stock in tech space, I bet on its growth potential to be overvalued in a short term once it was promoted by some stock news websites/caught public's attention

- if it didn't go well, I have the $0.265 wall to sell into, so about 4% downside


During the weekend, I saw QPM and its chart, and now I believe that would've been a better hold over the weekend.

Reasons

- break out of previous resistances on high volume, closed Friday at ATH

- announcement from last week would likely be used as hype fuel

- closed $0.088, if it makes 10%, there's a chance that the momentum will push it above $0.10 and the pip change will take it up further

- the 500% gains mania in last week may have not ended and QPM looks to have similar recipe to those that was pumped to 500%

- I'll see how this open and decide whether to jump in</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Rude-Letter" created="2021-02-22 08:40:13+10:00">
  <body>Good luck fellas here's hoping for a green day for all of us 🤑</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="choofedLEGObrick" created="2021-02-21 18:27:32+10:00">
  <body>$NDQ</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 18:44:36+10:00">
  <body>Interested to see how CI1 fares this week now that the meme pumpers have had their dabble with it and more of the wider market are aware of how solid financially it is for a small cap.

I've been in at $0.03 for a while and could have sold at $0.1, but I believe it's worth between $0.12 and $0.15 so we will see how the market responds to its upcoming report.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-21 20:21:13+10:00">
   <body>Yep in at .03 for months 
It’s a long hold for growth - short term wins to invest elsewhere</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-21 19:19:40+10:00">
  <body>Anyone in on NOX. Thinking about getting out and topping up RAC ??</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SAIUN666" created="2021-02-21 23:21:43+10:00">
   <body>Good time to top up RAC. We know there's at least 3 news updates coming by the end of March, but if there are none this week we could see the price fall back to the $2.80 range.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="rpro13" created="2021-02-21 19:56:34+10:00">
  <body>Anyone in ADO? Doing some DD seems like a legit company looking to make the world a better place. Up around 900% on the 1 year chart.. thoughts?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SnooOwls5021" created="2021-02-21 17:16:03+10:00">
  <body>CRO🚀🚀‼️</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ZedZrick" created="2021-02-21 17:20:14+10:00">
   <body>Capital raise soon yeh?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 17:26:23+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 17:26:24+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. (Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki) [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/]

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Tacomaster33" created="2021-02-21 17:31:58+10:00">
  <body>MND for earnings (already bought in on friday)
Results our Tuesday</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-02-21 20:08:46+10:00">
  <body>No cash left -  spent my last on AGY last week

But I'll find some down the back of the couch to top up on more LKE if it drops under 30c

In the meantime - will watch BD1 and PRL tumble.......want to take some parcels of them once everyone has forgotten and moved on....</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="HCFaktor" created="2021-02-21 22:27:41+10:00">
   <body>I'm unsure how far BD1 will tumble. Obviously hyped up way too much last week but I bought back in at $2.85 cos company is promising in the long term</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:48:18+10:00">
  <body>What happened to that $1 to $1 million guy? Im guessing things went pear shaped</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="squinlytime" created="2021-02-21 23:07:16+10:00">
   <body>He bought RFT for trade 12 last week: https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/llqf6v/journey_to_1m_1240_buy_update/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;utm_name=iossmf</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 23:13:29+10:00">
    <body>Cheers looks like i missed it</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 23:14:19+10:00">
   <body>Reported recently enough I think. Can't get 20% on your pick every week.

Hopefully XST didn't slow them down, though they were using a pretty conservative 15% loss sell yeah?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="steveydraws" created="2021-02-22 07:48:20+10:00">
  <body>What ever happened to that company that sells electric scooters/ bike? Didn’t someone say they would do well cos of their sales ?</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="djburns19" created="2021-02-22 07:54:20+10:00">
   <body>VMT. 

Been doing well for 2 years now. Worth keeping a very close eye on. They are releasing 3 new bikes tonight in timing with Chinese NY. 

The company has had continuous solid growth and already has roughly 12,000 orders in line for the start of this year. 

Publicity/media campaign is probably needed to push them into the next bracket. 

*I have been holding since early 2019.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:19:55+10:00">
   <body>I think I read a comment with some details about it in yesterday's daily post</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mr_X2017" created="2021-02-22 08:26:01+10:00">
  <body>QPM out with a good announcement to pump it up. What nice timing by them.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="VeezusM" created="2021-02-22 08:26:05+10:00">
  <body>BRK have farmed out a portion of their Jewell Well to SHE. SHE to fund 50% of all costs associated with drilling</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="McDogals" created="2021-02-22 08:37:02+10:00">
   <body>BRK about to see some real growth 🚀🚀🚀</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SkernMannnn" created="2021-02-22 09:01:49+10:00">
  <body>Interesting announcement by AXE this morning got me keen enough to place an order after sitting on my watchlist for a few months!

My faith is in IHL though! 

Let's pray for a good week!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-21 17:10:32+10:00">
  <body>Ajx, it’s hovering around 6c bit id like it hit 9 p</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CrusaderR4bbit" created="2021-02-21 17:29:53+10:00">
   <body>I know you said you'd like it to go to 9 rather than asserting that it would, but is there any reason it would being moving up?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-21 17:32:26+10:00">
    <body>Well quarterly report stated it was close to completing commercial agreements. If it eventuates, SP 🔼</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CrusaderR4bbit" created="2021-02-21 17:39:41+10:00">
     <body>Thanks for your response.   As someone with a background in materials chem I  am intrigued and will have a closer look at them.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Roc390" created="2021-02-21 17:42:07+10:00">
      <body>This is a wholesome journey</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="PM_me_ur_bingo_nos" created="2021-02-21 17:45:57+10:00">
     <body>Why would they have such a big jump? They currently have products for a tiny market. Maybe when they finally make the leap to the military/fire service stuff.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-21 17:47:09+10:00">
      <body>They jumped to 9 after they’re quarterly release so it’s possible. Also commercialization agreement for their military products could do it</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="G-forced" created="2021-02-21 18:32:25+10:00">
  <body>because money tree's are the perfect place for shade</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="seb_dm" created="2021-02-21 19:21:11+10:00">
  <body>9SP might finally be doing something. Hopefully there is an ann.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FRjunkie" created="2021-02-21 19:22:49+10:00">
   <body>They’re hiring more staff. I’m pretty confident.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-02-21 21:48:58+10:00">
  <body>Heard an announcement is looming this week from ADN regarding future productions.

🚀🚀🚀🚀  this week hopefully.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-21 21:51:05+10:00">
   <body>Hopefully. Ages ago I bought mep near 14c instead thinking it'd rerate to fair value (trading at under 50% of it rn) but that never happened. If ADN goes up at least MEP will follow.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rhythm34" created="2021-02-22 07:51:17+10:00">
   <body>With an Alan Kohler interview expected this week at minimum I’d expect a small share price pump from boomers. ADN have a history of dropping a decent announcement before interviews or conferences too, so who knows...

Something to do with batteries would be the dream to really blow a lid off the share price.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="swifty237" created="2021-02-22 06:36:56+10:00">
  <body>5k into UWL

5k into SKF

3k into TMT</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mr_X2017" created="2021-02-22 07:48:38+10:00">
   <body>I see a ticker I hold I upvote. I’m a simple man.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:01:00+10:00">
   <body>Proof or ban</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="swifty237" created="2021-02-22 10:31:36+10:00">
    <body>Uwl licked a fucks asshole and climbed up instead of dropping to 1.75

Tmt sucked some dick and went to 0.35 instead of .335

Been trynna buy more skf at 0.195 for a while but just no luck aye

Edit: how the fuck do I upload photos to reddit 

Edit2: cbs uploading to imgur aye, I hold 10k of TMT 5.8k of UWL and 5.2k of SKF which is the best proof I can be bothered to give</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 12:12:03+10:00">
     <body>Does Imgur even work anymore?

Best of luck, I haven't heard of any of those shares. So likely rockets 👍</body>
     <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Footballer217" created="2021-02-22 08:13:58+10:00">
  <body>Anyone know how long it takes for Commsec to process new trading applications? I applied on Friday.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="HyperIndian" created="2021-02-22 08:15:07+10:00">
   <body>Before: under a week. 

Now: who knows. A ton of people have overwhelmed trading and even crypto platforms with new applications</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Rum-Ham-Jabroni" created="2021-02-22 08:15:03+10:00">
   <body>Should be pretty quick. From memory a couple of days.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Footballer217" created="2021-02-22 08:17:34+10:00">
    <body>Much appreciated. Just weird when I submitted I didn’t get any email, just a text from netbank giving me a temporary password. Fingers crossed!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="JBruceLee" created="2021-02-21 17:58:51+10:00">
  <body>PWN was getting bought up like crazy in the last hour of trading in Friday. Hoping that signed deal we've been waiting for is on its way</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="76plants" created="2021-02-21 18:05:38+10:00">
  <body>Added Roots Sustainable Ag (ROO) to the portfolio on Friday so just in watching phase now.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-21 18:16:44+10:00">
   <body>Had a peek into this on Friday, can't understand how they are actually positioned to make money. Something about Israel and small plastic hose connections?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="76plants" created="2021-02-21 18:20:58+10:00">
    <body>They have a process/product to improve crop yields. Also getting into the cannabis market (which is good synergy cos I’ve made a bundle on Creso Pharma (+680%) to date...) and the rapidly growing plant based “meat” field. 
Only a minor grab at this point to see how it goes. Not expecting quick profits.</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="BigJimBeef" created="2021-02-21 20:05:58+10:00">
     <body>Post that sweet gains porn mate</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-21 20:27:14+10:00">
     <body>You are all just on here for a few days each - I have had ROO for a long time as I thought it was doing good stuff - Lucky I was happy with a long term hold as I’m down 50% so I hope your attempt at a pump works</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-21 20:34:14+10:00">
   <body>Its a dog shit stock man</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="beaver2233" created="2021-02-21 18:38:18+10:00">
  <body>Expecting tomorrow to be fairly red for me. ALC will likely retreat a bit after Friday's crazy run...unless of course they announce something alongside the half yearly.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ohJewJew" created="2021-02-21 18:47:51+10:00">
  <body>What are ur predictions on XST for tmr?</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 18:59:00+10:00">
   <body>Tomorrow? Up or down 2%.
30% for week by close Friday, or I delete my Isaac account</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-21 19:28:07+10:00">
    <body>Up 30% by the end of the week would be great.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="FlaminChain" created="2021-02-21 19:08:56+10:00">
    <body>Oh man I hope you're right about up 2%. I need to scrape that shit off my portfolio!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:07:49+10:00">
    <body>One tick is not 2%</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-21 22:25:43+10:00">
     <body>6%</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="rpro13" created="2021-02-21 19:07:56+10:00">
  <body>Small parcel on RBR hoping for a free carry</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-21 20:47:14+10:00">
  <body>MGT buy up before this MF gets discovered by the rest of you autists</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jontomlinson" created="2021-02-21 21:58:49+10:00">
  <body>CRW H2 2020 results this week 🥳 they had an insane black friday so i hope that makes up for lacklustre boxing day sales</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="dannyk1234" created="2021-02-22 07:52:57+10:00">
  <body>Appendix 2A for LRS up.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="BillyZaneTrain" created="2021-02-22 08:00:55+10:00">
   <body>Im on the shitter. Is it good?</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-22 08:01:59+10:00">
    <body>Appendix 2A means that options have been converted lol.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="BillyZaneTrain" created="2021-02-22 08:02:45+10:00">
     <body>Fucking lol I got way too excited</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="azad_s" created="2021-02-22 08:15:10+10:00">
  <body>Great assay results just received from COD. Been sitting on this since ipo. Time to start seeing some tendies 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-02-22 08:18:18+10:00">
   <body>Don't trust fish man, they fucking LIE!

Edit: sorry, just woke up. Not constructive yet</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="flailinghotel" created="2021-02-22 08:40:11+10:00">
  <body>MEM -  Memphasys limited

Here is some lazy shithouse info on MEM:

* They have made something like a sperm filter for male infertility to increase IVF success rates.
* Coming close to commercial sales announcement
* Printer / Ink sales model
* World male fertility rates falling.  [https://nypost.com/2021/02/20/why-more-men-are-suffering-from-infertility-than-ever-before/?utm\_source=reddit.com](https://nypost.com/2021/02/20/why-more-men-are-suffering-from-infertility-than-ever-before/?utm_source=reddit.com)
* IVF market to reach USD 36.39 billion by 2026
* Also works on animals for agriculture.</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Brizwizard" created="2021-02-22 08:41:56+10:00">
  <body>HT8 authorised apple reseller yeww</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Soft-Leek-280" created="2021-02-22 08:50:52+10:00">
  <body>Positive AGH annoucement. Hold it myself so hoping for more good news. 

[AGH annoucement ](https://cdn-api.markitdigital.com/apiman-gateway/ASX/asx-research/1.0/file/2924-02343962-3A561792?access_token=83ff96335c2d45a094df02a206a39ff4)</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="angelusinc" created="2021-02-22 08:53:22+10:00">
  <body>Anyone in here own BAT? I only did a small amount of DD on them but they look promising so I chucked 1k on it. Tell me how retarded I am</body>
  <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Elegantmango77" created="2021-02-22 09:42:56+10:00">
  <body>VKA is my only thing in the green over the last week</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 18:38:50+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 18:38:50+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. (Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki) [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/]

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 20:02:10+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 20:02:11+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 20:41:25+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 20:41:26+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-21 22:29:33+10:00">
  <body>Anyone use the investing.com app . This thing looks mad good.

Only thing that sucks it doesn’t show announcements like commsec does. 

Its got this really cool buy sell sentiment section that I like.</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 22:38:52+10:00">
   <body>Lol. I also hear this Uber app is useful for getting rides</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Drakoolya" created="2021-02-21 22:40:34+10:00">
    <body>Dude check my comment history , not a spam account . Just sharing some info.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-21 23:33:00+10:00">
     <body>Just playing with ya, yes the app is a must have</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 22:34:29+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 22:34:30+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. (Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki) [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/]

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-21 22:36:26+10:00">
  <body>Copper been soaring but none of the ASX plays seem to be following suit. Anyone here have their toes dipped in some cop? I hold nrx and nwc</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-21 22:47:44+10:00">
   <body>OZL has been doing fine for me, and they are pretty much copper-centric... what attracted you to those specific companies?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-22 07:57:39+10:00">
    <body>I can probably answer my reasons for NWC. They were able to acquire an old copper cobalt land holding in Arizona. Limited exploration required due to existing resource estimates. High grade VMS is being hit on most holes with further abnormalities to be drilled within aeromagnetic surveys and DHEM. They have direction and a goal which is to flip into a producer with the existing infrastructure within around 18 months. to 2 years. They're probably missing a couple things i like in an exploration turned producer phase. Cornerstone holders are limited but perennial just came on board both accumulating on market above CR and in the CR. They need some fucking smart money on the BOD someone with experience in financial markets to really give a longer term prospective to some larger investors early but instead they have suffered at the hands of persher who just continue to dump on market within a certain range.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-21 22:42:01+10:00">
   <body>I hold a fair few. I cant get my head around NWC not running earlier this year the VMS finds and assays should have put it around a 100 million market cap before the last cap raise should still be some action to come here but lots of the dilution doesn't help. Copper doesn't seem to run like gold and nickel does but we haven't really had a significant discovery for a while. Maybe were overdue?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="thickgucci" created="2021-02-21 23:54:51+10:00">
    <body>Hope so bro</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-22 07:36:33+10:00">
   <body>OZL probably the best copper play to be into. Massive producer. Wont rocket 50% overnight, but in the next coming years, can expect $40 SP imo</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 22:53:12+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 22:53:13+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. (Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki) [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/]

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="phantom_hax0r" created="2021-02-21 23:21:02+10:00">
   <body>Read faq</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-21 23:08:46+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-21 23:08:46+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-22 00:02:22+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-22 00:02:23+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. (Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki) [https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/]

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-22 07:18:04+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-22 07:18:04+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="somewhatready" created="2021-02-22 07:26:36+10:00">
  <body>SYA for a ride 💦💦</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CrusaderR4bbit" created="2021-02-22 07:44:36+10:00">
   <body>Why?</body>
   <comment ups="None" downs="None" author="None">
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="asx_better" created="2021-02-22 07:41:57+10:00">
  <body>A2m already up in New Zealand ... You love to see it you really do</body>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
