<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-02-26 Friday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>RED (14) HYPE=8, TIP=15</mention>
  <mention>LOT (11) HYPE=16, TIP=10</mention>
  <mention>RAC (9) HYPE=10</mention>
  <mention>BOT (7) </mention>
  <mention>DW8 (6) HYPE=8</mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="hk_melb" created="2021-02-25 17:50:55+10:00">
   <body>Any ideas why’s RED5 getting hammered??</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-02-25 19:43:18+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>Bro RED is fucking cooked. Huge overhead to build KOTH in coming (if they even get funding? Announcement is lagging which should have been sorted already?) 

The losses are insane, the way they hedge they’re gold at darlot is puss and the never ending work on a 30 year old plant to keep it running is going to be taxing on any profits.

Eventually if they wanna keep darlot going they need to find more dirt, underground is raped and they are starting to mine recently discovered open pit mines for fuck all grade and bugger all reserve. If this is enough to keep darlot running there will have to be a major overhaul on the site to keep it operating. 

KOTH is there only hope. It will bounce from this quarterly in the next week or so, just be careful with this one IMO.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-25 20:19:10+10:00">
     <body>Yikes glad I got out</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-02-25 20:23:23+10:00" sentiment="TIP 15">
      <body>If KOTH goes to plan it will be a good site. Was always going to be a plan of mine to play this report buy the dip and sell on the bounce, unfortunately my capital is tied up in another swing trade. 

RED is a long term play if KOTH goes well it should do okay. If not it’s gonna be fucked.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cant_right_good" created="2021-02-25 18:11:56+10:00">
    <body>I only skimmed it but it was not a good announcement they put out today</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 18:28:50+10:00">
   <body>Alright, I need y'all to be the bear case for me.
A2M looks like an absolute bargain to me at these prices, and the price will recover as they develop new sales channels and we recover globally from Covid. What am I missing?</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-02-25 18:37:28+10:00">
    <body>If it looks like a bargain, what is its fair value? How have you decided it's a bargain - just because the price has dropped?  
I know nothing of the business but what are the new channels? What sort of market penetration will they have/competitors?  How do you see the covid recovery as a positive for a powdered baby(?) milk company?  Are there logistics/freight benefits or something you see coming? Do you see increased demand because of more babies, growing wealth of buyers/premium pricing?</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Drumsteppin" created="2021-02-25 19:01:30+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>Alright so here's the DD Ive done on A2M. I was in IGA the other day, buying milk, and the 2L A2 milk was like $4.80 and the generic IGA milk was $2.55. 2.55&lt;4.80, hence I didn't buy the A2 milk. Based on those figures, things don't look too good for the company's sales. I didn't look at baby formula so cannot comment on how that part of the business competes. DYOR, thanks for reading my shitty DD.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:04:29+10:00">
     <body>People who can afford to pay a premium for a premium product often do so though.</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-25 19:22:21+10:00">
      <body>Buying overpriced milk is like buying overpriced water...

Speaking of which, the world seems to have forgotten Supreme bricks.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Drumsteppin" created="2021-02-25 19:24:41+10:00" sentiment="TIP 10">
      <body>That's fair. I was being pretty tongue in cheek before, but do you feel that the company is helping itself by setting that price point, or is it hindering itself? Do you think that part of the business can see growth, either by reducing costs to increase per unit profit from an existing customer base, or advertising/incentivising new customers to start buying the premium milk and hence growing volume? Or has the brand effectively reached its market size for that particular product and is unlikely to see growth unless it starts competing on price and increasing volume? Are competitors offering a similar or better product? Is it for a higher or lower price? 

I haven't researched any of this, but to me I don't see much potential for growth in that arm of the business, as for a lot of people milk is a commodity item, and often no-brand basic milk is good enough. Milk derivative products there is the potential for much more growth, the creation of interesting products, and the ability to have unique marketing. But, the questions I asked above can also be applied to the rest of their portfolio of products. When you look at their products from those perspectives, your investment becomes a bet of "do I believe that the company can attain appropriate growth in some of its markets, and will this growth be reflected in the share price?"</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Scomosbuttpirate" created="2021-02-25 19:20:41+10:00">
    <body>Shit management, sales to China are not coming back any time soon, you'd be better taking a short position the company is that fucked.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Aleckrandall" created="2021-02-25 19:12:10+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>Shit financial reports, declining sales &amp; profit margins</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-25 19:17:33+10:00">
    <body>Personally wouldn't touch something that is so utterly dependent on China, that's a built-in bear case for me right there 

lotta other stocks out there brother</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SmashPlayersRretards" created="2021-02-25 20:05:24+10:00">
    <body>they sell fuckin milk, how much do you think people need to drink for it to takeoff</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-25 18:30:32+10:00">
    <body>Nothing. I bought today for $8.88</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="is2017goingtobebad" created="2021-02-25 18:08:19+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>Since US markets have bigger swings, wouldn’t it be a better idea to buy LKE on NYSE? Since it will have more potential to rise massively, for e.g how PLL went to $35 on open from like $2 on NYSE while did little on ASX.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:40:30+10:00">
   <body>ASX is slim pickins for good stonks</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Nordvegr" created="2021-02-25 19:23:09+10:00">
    <body>You'd have a fucking skitz time if you were a geologist though.</body>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 19:35:04+10:00">
     <body>Even then, I’m not a fan of waiting years and years for actual money. Kinda like biotech stocks</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Pure_Beautiful_395" created="2021-02-25 18:48:19+10:00">
    <body>IMU</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:56:03+10:00">
     <body>I’d give it a solid 5/10</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pure_Beautiful_395" created="2021-02-25 19:27:57+10:00">
      <body>That’s honest tbh</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="-14" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:42:15+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>PIL! Have a look at the volume, relisted in ASX today.</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:00:02+10:00">
     <body>If you touch this - you deserve to get reamed. It went up mega today to suck in the retards. The power point presentation is just another pump and dump BS hypno spiel. It has all the right pics and figures to suck in the noobs that have no idea - be warned. Yes it could go up and make some people some money but at the end of the day - another scam stock. AVOID.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:45:15+10:00">
     <body>Errr I hope you’re not serious, this could be one of the worst stock atm on ASX</body>
     <comment ups="-8" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:48:04+10:00">
      <body>We will wait and see... the boomers on HC are loving it</body>
      <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 18:51:20+10:00">
       <body>That is usually a sure sign of dogshit.</body>
       <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:57:44+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
        <body>Will let you know if I make a profit tomorrow or not, if it costs me money I deserve a good teabaggin, if I get some coin off some HC boomers, that doesn't bother me 1 bit.</body>
        <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:29:28+10:00">
         <body>I admit it can make some money as the share price will move. The company itself tho - red flags everywhere. ASX regulations are fucked.</body>
        </comment>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:43:02+10:00">
         <body>I hope you take all their hard earned Boomer cash.</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:11:52+10:00">
   <body>Got a bit of an aut-ape question, wife's boyfriend probably knows but not allowed to ask... , how/where do people find out future dates when companies are to release an announcement?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Ok-Degree-5548" created="2021-02-25 20:18:00+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>I reckon you could look at some here 
https://www.commsec.com.au/content/dam/EN/ReportingSeason/February2021/CommSec_Reporting_Season_Calendar_February2021.pdf</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:19:30+10:00">
     <body>Actually pretty nifty sheet. Thanks for that</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:19:18+10:00">
    <body>Ask magic ball. The only annc a company can set a date for is financials and AGM. Everything else must be released to the market immediately the BOD is aware. Well - in theory anyway. You gotta be sucking BOD dick to know before us.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:20:43+10:00">
     <body>I usually ask magic ball on which stonk to go balls deep in... probably factored into that question too</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-25 20:15:31+10:00">
    <body>What. Unless the company gives some timeline, or its a financial report like a quarterly, that would require actual magic.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:17:23+10:00">
     <body>Often people being being like announcement due on say 28/2 for XXX company.. quite often not quarterly reports. Wondering which services if any others use to this?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="crabbypattytata" created="2021-02-25 19:23:27+10:00">
   <body>CI1 :(</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Faabs96" created="2021-02-25 19:39:30+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 20">
    <body>CI1 to the moon baby! 🚀🚀🚀</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="altarofbones" created="2021-02-25 19:06:13+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
   <body>Hope DW8 takes a run again. Come on wino’s, drink up and give me tendies.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="wherelamboman" created="2021-02-25 19:11:27+10:00">
    <body>I think there is a lot of people with their eye on it waiting for it to drop, but this might honestly be as low as it gets.</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Johnnyboii12333" created="2021-02-25 19:36:57+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 20">
     <body>To the moon boys 🚀🚀🌝</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-02-25 19:11:38+10:00">
    <body>Me too brother.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 17:53:58+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>BRN power 🧠🧠🧠  let's go</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-02-25 18:09:55+10:00">
    <body>It's a cool announcement</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 18:15:53+10:00">
     <body>I was so surprised that it wasn't announced on the ASX hey? But yeah good things to come this year from this bad boy</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:37:37+10:00">
      <body>For real? Anything that may affect price/material must be annc'd on ASX - before anywhere else. But hey - ASX is a fucken cowboy operation now.</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="oxymoreme" created="2021-02-25 18:21:38+10:00">
      <body>What happened?</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 18:31:27+10:00">
       <body>https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210224006179/en/BrainChip-Inc.-and-NaNose-Medical-Successfully-Detect-COVID-19-in-Exhaled-Breath-with-Fast-High-Accuracy-Results</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="oxymoreme" created="2021-02-25 18:37:15+10:00">
        <body>That's really good news</body>
        <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-25 19:35:16+10:00">
         <body>It’s too late though</body>
         <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="oxymoreme" created="2021-02-25 19:35:45+10:00">
          <body>For what?</body>
         </comment>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-25 17:54:22+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Z1P to $20 tomorrow 🚀

...please?</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mario32d" created="2021-02-25 17:57:55+10:00">
    <body>BNPL stocks in general are being shit lately.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Timeflyer4357" created="2021-02-25 18:15:51+10:00">
    <body>Let’s go never give up on ZIP nation baby 🤩 we will rise, we will fall but we will rise tomorrow to $45 to greatness #pumpitupZipperboys</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-02-25 19:06:57+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Automod 🚀</body>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="28" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-02-25 18:12:41+10:00">
  <body>It’s much quieter here over the last few days. Have a couple of red days scared all the newbies away already?</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-25 18:31:12+10:00">
   <body>The pumpers have fukd off?</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="gunit1987" created="2021-02-25 18:48:16+10:00">
    <body>Hope so</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-25 18:57:17+10:00">
   <body>I saw a couple have lost all their money and had second thoughts about this game. I feel very badly for them.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Fawksyyy" created="2021-02-25 20:00:38+10:00">
    <body>All? Did they just give it away?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="IndianLarper" created="2021-02-25 20:24:38+10:00">
   <body>So many ppl bagholding after the red</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="27" downs="0" author="Steponmy92" created="2021-02-25 19:02:40+10:00">
  <body>Selling all my stocks :( 
just found termites in my home and it is going to cost a pretty penny.</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="autodidact31" created="2021-02-25 19:10:22+10:00">
   <body>Termites? What's the ticker for them?</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Scomosbuttpirate" created="2021-02-25 19:15:52+10:00">
    <body>No ticker but you can probably get a bookie to take bets on who will win, the termites or the exterminator. I did see you were able to bet on if the KFC tower burger would come back a second time this year or be made permanent so you can really bet on anything now.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-25 20:04:31+10:00">
     <body>I wish KFC would still make the works burger.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="TransientSvcError" created="2021-02-25 19:25:23+10:00">
   <body>Burn it down, claim insurance, rent for 20k/year and put the rest back in to the market. Problem solved</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-25 19:08:33+10:00">
   <body>Sorry to hear that man. Fucking ants.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="kaydawg99" created="2021-02-25 19:35:02+10:00">
    <body>Ants my eyes Johnson</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-25 20:10:48+10:00">
   <body>Puts on your house 😢</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="20" downs="0" author="theangryantipodean" created="2021-02-25 18:56:54+10:00">
  <body>DW8 [half yearly report](https://cdn-api.markitdigital.com/apiman-gateway/ASX/asx-research/1.0/file/2924-02346938-6A1022093?access_token=83ff96335c2d45a094df02a206a39ff4) as of an hour ago.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Johnnyboii12333" created="2021-02-25 19:39:00+10:00">
   <body>can’t wait for tomorrow!!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="RayGamble" created="2021-02-25 17:05:46+10:00">
  <body>LKE went for another late arvo jog...hoping the cunt is bothered for another one tomorrow.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="18" downs="0" author="Ad4nothing" created="2021-02-25 17:56:38+10:00">
  <body>Super cheap just asked if I wanted to pay with zip. I said no but now I wanna buy z1p shares.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-25 18:49:28+10:00">
   <body>Maybe they were asking if you wanted to pay with zip shares.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="Happy_Distance_5571" created="2021-02-25 18:35:49+10:00">
  <body>After 6 months of austism in ASX, these red days don’t flinch me no more. Having spent months of red in IOU, Z1P, AL3, these red days are turning my hands into diamond 🖐💎🤚</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-02-25 19:17:37+10:00">
   <body>Same, I used to cry and dump shares on red days, now I buy more or do DD to double check my long position.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-25 18:40:46+10:00">
  <body>Yall heard it here first, RAC is blowing smoke up ye bums. Something is damn fishy about that whole operation</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-25 18:43:56+10:00">
   <body>They want to pump the price up to sell company or they are looking to sell off all their own shares they’ve been stacking - pump n dump.
Financials looked good but the US tranches??</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-02-25 19:12:12+10:00">
    <body>A lot of boomers would lose their money. Their life savings and retirement money from the looks of it. Bold statement</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:57:35+10:00">
   <body>Story is a bit too good to be true and the company executive is active on Hotcopper kek</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ToiIets" created="2021-02-25 19:12:52+10:00">
   <body>Everyone thinks wombat is a messiah so whatever he spruiks gets pumped... But I've been there for one of his worse pump jobs and it didn't end well</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-25 19:20:31+10:00">
    <body>What was that?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ToiIets" created="2021-02-25 19:42:55+10:00">
     <body>Mustang resources. To be fair the company was a bit dishonest, but wombat was there everyday riling everyone up saying this company was worth 1B.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-25 19:20:36+10:00">
   <body>I found it weird as fuck when the ceo was getting his knickers in a twist about people being trend traders on HC. If you go back on some CHN threads there company rep never did any of the sort of shit RAC does with the company rep function.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="smashin_tins" created="2021-02-25 18:56:31+10:00">
   <body>Keen to hear reasons</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-25 19:08:50+10:00">
   <body>Something damn fishy about all operations. Everyone in the world wants to take your money.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="thwacknerdthwack" created="2021-02-25 19:48:04+10:00">
   <body>I jumped on board at 2.70 or so, but I agree to an extent. Something is a bit off. But I think that also might be the cult that's sprung up around it. If you strip away the noise they have a great drug that should be commercially viable in some form. Will it go for $120 a share in two years? Probably not. But I agree there is far too much hype and consequently it has a bit of a pyramid scheme vibe.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="whiskeyboyo" created="2021-02-25 18:29:58+10:00">
  <body>I just came here to say good luck everybody

👁️👄👁️</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="casinos01" created="2021-02-25 17:07:14+10:00">
  <body>Is LKE due for some announcements soon or what?</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="luner124" created="2021-02-25 17:08:30+10:00">
   <body>NVX trading halt, maybe they will throw news out at same time as capital raise?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mr3_0_5" created="2021-02-25 19:41:19+10:00">
   <body>They did say a announcement was due by the end of feb</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 17:53:58+10:00">
  <body>BRN power 🧠🧠🧠  let's go</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-02-25 18:09:55+10:00">
   <body>It's a cool announcement</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 18:15:53+10:00">
    <body>I was so surprised that it wasn't announced on the ASX hey? But yeah good things to come this year from this bad boy</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:37:37+10:00">
     <body>For real? Anything that may affect price/material must be annc'd on ASX - before anywhere else. But hey - ASX is a fucken cowboy operation now.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="oxymoreme" created="2021-02-25 18:21:38+10:00">
     <body>What happened?</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 18:31:27+10:00">
      <body>https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210224006179/en/BrainChip-Inc.-and-NaNose-Medical-Successfully-Detect-COVID-19-in-Exhaled-Breath-with-Fast-High-Accuracy-Results</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="oxymoreme" created="2021-02-25 18:37:15+10:00">
       <body>That's really good news</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-25 19:35:16+10:00">
        <body>It’s too late though</body>
        <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="oxymoreme" created="2021-02-25 19:35:45+10:00">
         <body>For what?</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="Scrofl" created="2021-02-25 17:38:16+10:00">
  <body>Will probably buy more Z1P tomorrow after this week's dip. Financials are crazy good.</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="archbishopofoz" created="2021-02-25 17:47:53+10:00">
   <body>Last zip dip lasted 2 months</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Scrofl" created="2021-02-25 18:19:00+10:00">
    <body>True, but I can't see it dipping below $10 again, unless something catastrophic happens.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="zinger_zen" created="2021-02-25 18:38:26+10:00">
  <body>Thinking of putting 20k on zip and forget for 6 months to buy a Hyundai i20. what do you guys think?</body>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="GlitteringAerie6002" created="2021-02-25 18:44:32+10:00">
   <body>Are you going to buy the car on Z1P?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="zinger_zen" created="2021-02-25 18:45:41+10:00">
    <body>Haha! I would love to. Do any of the car dealers accept BNPL?</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="huydn" created="2021-02-25 19:08:30+10:00">
     <body>Why would they? They make a fair bit from car loans.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="zinger_zen" created="2021-02-25 19:32:21+10:00">
      <body>So that their cars can finally go to the moon?</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Nsj_1" created="2021-02-25 19:45:52+10:00">
     <body>BNPL only for services and parts.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-02-25 19:45:00+10:00">
   <body>A solid probably to the Z1P. A huge faaaark no to the i20</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="zinger_zen" created="2021-02-25 20:13:45+10:00">
    <body>😑how about MG3?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="BoxofYoodes" created="2021-02-25 17:05:40+10:00">
  <body>If RAC could just keep steadily climbing based on positive expectations that would be great</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="isnotabaker" created="2021-02-25 17:16:11+10:00">
   <body>I think RAC will keep climbing but I think there is some bot action and pumping going on making it more volatile. I'm not too concerned as it's a long hold for me but it wouldn't surprise me if it goes down tomorrow. Going down works for me, I want to buy more lol.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="matt_step" created="2021-02-25 18:31:51+10:00">
    <body>I agree with this. There’ll be a day soon where some profit taking will take this down somewhat for sure. Just when though....</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-25 18:52:02+10:00">
     <body>I'm taking a little bit at 3.80, won't move the needle one iota, though.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-02-25 19:36:43+10:00">
    <body>Yep I’m topping up 5k</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-25 17:24:46+10:00">
  <body>Love Lord of the Rings so might throw some cash on the following - Fellowship of the ring - ASX: FOR. The Two Towers - ASX TTT. Return of the King - NYSE: ROK</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-25 17:34:02+10:00">
   <body>Fuck any tickers related to the hobbit movies, pure trash. I’m looking at you Desolation of Smaug - CVE: DOS. Actually it’s up 7% today maybe worth a gamble. I’ve had a few beers</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Ad4nothing" created="2021-02-25 18:20:14+10:00">
    <body>https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=xKbyWSwd7hk</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="GetOnTheBets" created="2021-02-25 18:38:08+10:00">
   <body>I’ve seen a few people go for the numberplates strat but movie trilogies is new to me. How about Star Wars? NEW for a New Hope, EMP for Empire Strikes Back and RTR for the Return of the Jedi?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="WilyWillow" created="2021-02-25 19:25:01+10:00">
   <body>Great idea! I'm gunna buy some EGG cos it's my fav for breakfast</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="WilyWillow" created="2021-02-25 19:27:20+10:00">
    <body>Maybe with a side of BCN</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="altarofbones" created="2021-02-25 19:06:13+10:00">
  <body>Hope DW8 takes a run again. Come on wino’s, drink up and give me tendies.</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="wherelamboman" created="2021-02-25 19:11:27+10:00">
   <body>I think there is a lot of people with their eye on it waiting for it to drop, but this might honestly be as low as it gets.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Johnnyboii12333" created="2021-02-25 19:36:57+10:00">
    <body>To the moon boys 🚀🚀🌝</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-02-25 19:11:38+10:00">
   <body>Me too brother.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-25 19:09:57+10:00">
  <body>Where the Uranium fuck boys at? 

Need to keep the energy high cos PENis is dicking around.

Other Uranium stocks did well</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-25 19:27:28+10:00">
   <body>Nah it’s just giving me an entry finally.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-02-25 19:55:21+10:00">
   <body>Present, currently at half-mast from PEN but full mast from BOE action today</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="MikeLitoris7" created="2021-02-25 20:05:53+10:00">
   <body>Reporting in.

[Just jerking my glowing PENis to some uranium porn.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TSza2XH28hs)</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="VPforFREE" created="2021-02-25 17:54:22+10:00">
  <body>Z1P to $20 tomorrow 🚀

...please?</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Mario32d" created="2021-02-25 17:57:55+10:00">
   <body>BNPL stocks in general are being shit lately.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Timeflyer4357" created="2021-02-25 18:15:51+10:00">
   <body>Let’s go never give up on ZIP nation baby 🤩 we will rise, we will fall but we will rise tomorrow to $45 to greatness #pumpitupZipperboys</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 17:56:07+10:00">
  <body>Not a bad day for me.

CHK and IXR did the heavy lifting with CNB joining the party. 

Cut ties with PRL at probably the bottom but will get back in when CS stop selling

Picked up a few JXT on the sell off from the financials already known lol

RVR with the after hours announcement, revenue up 100%, net profit up 310% righto 😳 

New positions, CXO and BRK.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-25 19:11:00+10:00">
   <body>Wait for it I reckon BRK will become the next hype stock on the sub.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 20:13:48+10:00">
    <body>I think that’s a good thing??? Haha</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-02-25 20:14:57+10:00">
     <body>It is when you’re early 😂</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 20:21:50+10:00">
      <body>In that case let the pumping begin 😂</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-25 19:35:47+10:00">
   <body>Yes yes IXR... so excited for tomorrow !!</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 20:17:03+10:00">
    <body>Gapped up a couple of pips at the close for a second day in a row. Guess they want a seat at the table before an announcement comes!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-25 20:16:37+10:00">
   <body>Ah mate I thought we were in PRL all the way to the end! I'm still holding, the bastard had better bounce</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 20:24:16+10:00">
    <body>Haha oops. I’ll be back in by next week I’m guessing!


Fuck the price action had annoyed me the last two days. Runs up then gets dumped. Guessing it’s CS doing that.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Wannaliveinpenthouse" created="2021-02-25 18:05:56+10:00">
  <body>APX and A2M are two goddamn traps</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-02-25 18:12:50+10:00">
   <body>A2M has too many red flags. I don’t like the fact that their directors dumped shares before the SP crashed or that their sales channels rely on tourism.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Wannaliveinpenthouse" created="2021-02-25 18:17:50+10:00">
    <body>wait what!! their directors dumped their shares ?! Honestly a potential ending I conceive for this company is being acquired by a random Chinese food giants...</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-25 18:57:49+10:00">
     <body>At which point the Chinese won't trust the product any more.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="reptings" created="2021-02-25 18:07:58+10:00">
   <body>APX ain’t half as bad as A2M, just getting fucked as bad.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:33:48+10:00">
   <body>Market darlings could not test the trials of ASX</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-25 18:07:40+10:00">
   <body>Not if you bought in todays dip</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:27:44+10:00">
  <body>Alright, I'm gonna be that retard that asks that annoying fucking question, but only because I'm feeling really disheartened and uninspired and I don't know where to direct my attention in the market... How do y'all scan for stocks? Like, where do you start? Financial news? Podcasts/blogs? Technical scans?
Just looking for some help to shake my shit up a bit.</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:40:51+10:00">
   <body>Go find Yothuyindi's write up on scans from a cpla days ago - great post - hard to beat.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:50:09+10:00">
    <body>On here? I can't find it, maybe I have to scroll back a head.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-25 19:53:09+10:00">
     <body>https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lmzzj5/how_to_do_basic_due_diligence_dd_a_discussion/</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:54:09+10:00">
      <body>Champion! Thank you!</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:08:37+10:00">
     <body>Tuesday maybe?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Brilliant-Contract16" created="2021-02-25 19:51:58+10:00">
    <body>I knew someone would have done it better 😉</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="ExcitingNarwhal8617" created="2021-02-25 19:52:15+10:00">
   <body>You really have to decide what strategy you want to implement dude. Are you interested in high risk or low risk? Do you want to hold them for 5 minutes, 5 months or 5 years? Do you have money that you can literally burn for a shot at making heaps, or do you need your money safely invested? Those are some basics that you need to have locked in. 

Once you decide on some of those things, it will be easier to find stocks that suit.

Just start looking up every stock code that is mentioned in this forum, that's what I do until I find one I like the looks of.</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:53:48+10:00">
    <body>A majority of my portfolio is in ETFs, so my main goal for a satellite portfolio is to find good quality stocks that have a reasonable chances of doubling in 12 to 24 months.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ExcitingNarwhal8617" created="2021-02-25 20:02:19+10:00">
     <body>Nice, 12 - 24 months is long term for me. Look a things like:

KLL (should start production in then next 6 months or so and SP hasn't caught up). I can see them doubling by the time production starts.

5GG, they are a fairly new internet company that have good reviews and have a deal with NIVIDIA for GeForce NOW to be released this year. Worth a punt I reckon.

AVA, strong company with a market cap that doesn't reflect their business if you ask me, it's undervalued. Also they are in a niche market that could boom.

Those are some that I like for a 12 month + hold. Hope that helps.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Brilliant-Contract16" created="2021-02-25 19:43:14+10:00">
   <body>I have no doubt that others could do this better then me: look for a global trend, understand how it applies pressure and how people may gain from it. Understand is it short or long term, this effects how long you may be in the investment for. Google key words, honestly Google "Google search functions" it will help you apply a filter approach such as those keywords and asx. Once there start high level DD rinse and repeat. This advice provided by an ape. Bonus points try and have some knowledge in the area to help orientate you.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:51:16+10:00">
    <body>Thanks for the help my dude :)</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Day_Trade_Whore" created="2021-02-25 20:17:49+10:00">
   <body>You can go onto market index. Then you can click the market cap tab and it will show the lowest market cap.
Can go through and research them. Also put a ticker in hotcopper and see their sentiment. Alot of them do have retarded opinions about terrible stocks.

Also I goto cnbc alot and see what's happening around the world. I see that 3d printing might rise. So then I'll type into Google.  3d printing stocks asx.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="syyphon5" created="2021-02-25 20:27:22+10:00">
    <body>Tldr- buy 3dp</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 17:11:16+10:00">
  <body>Market green yet our pennies underperformed again</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DogLogik" created="2021-02-25 20:26:14+10:00">
   <body>Pennies don't seem to follow the market very well. Mine smashed it today, up 7%</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-02-25 18:30:28+10:00">
  <body>Booked a chiropractor session for PLL after it carried my portfolio today.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 19:48:07+10:00">
  <body>Well. Sold RFT for you guessed it EGR. If I had a sell order in on open would of got the sneaky 20% instantly. 

Some good discounts out today. LRS, A3D, CRL.

Thought vulcan would hit mid $5. That had a nice run today.

Bought a sneaky parcel of BPH at 0.17 and that had a nice run.

Trying to figure out RAC still. Getting FOMO.

AVA looking good for a buy in soon. 

IHL, whatcha doing bud?

LKE, bought the dip please start jogging. 

Do I own these all? No. Thought I'd have the noobs some some food for thought. 

What else. Ausfinance are shit.

Yeeeeeeet</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-02-25 19:55:39+10:00">
   <body>I've been in RAC since around $1.80. It's been a steady gainer for me, and most days/weeks the only thing holding up my port folio. I've heard nothing but positive sentiment about it on this subreddit and HC... up until now.

Only today I'm starting to see a massive spike in anti-RAC sentiment. Both rampers and downrampers (lower SP for big buys??) have something to gain from spruiking their views. Was it because of the post from the CSO on HC? or is there something else I am unaware about?

I really don't know what's going on, I'm very weary of everyone's motives. But I'll stick to my own DD that's worked well for me up until now.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 20:01:24+10:00">
    <body>Yeah it just slowly climbs and climbs, just trucks along. 

Yeah no idea aye, new accounts being wankers? Seeing more dumbshit on the subreddit everyday. It's slowly losing its charm.

Good op.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 20:05:26+10:00">
    <body>Or I have another hypothesis: People are just jealous it's running so hard.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="What-Is-Reddit-Even" created="2021-02-25 20:12:20+10:00">
    <body>I started the sentiment today. It’s about how it all looks too-good-to-be-true.
As an investor with their biggest chunk of their portfolio in RAC it’s only necessary to understand what I’m getting into by finding possible risks. Also important for the autistic fucks here who put in thousands with no DD based on word of mouth from here.
Very difficult to uncover the risks as the big holders who are posting about it here have massive holdings and are bearish, possibly for their personal benefit. Not to mention their Director or something spending hours on HC hyping it up and expressing his confidence. No one is capable of expressing any risks. A worrying sign because no stock is without risks.
And after the massive pump and dump of BD1 and sudden collapse of investor faith of XST and SGC it’s natural to prepare yourself for the consequences.

And the amount of new accounts expressing RAC as their Valentine’s date is concerning</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:23:26+10:00">
     <body>That HC director shit is totally illegal. I hope the fuckwit burns.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-02-25 20:28:32+10:00">
     <body>Just keep a very hard eye on it, that’s what I’m doing. Find the Balance. The hot copper threads are full of dreamers. Too big to be bought out? That insanity, pay no mind to that. Directors running a two year long pump and dump with international cancer research consultants and running fake trials to dupe investors? Sounds a bit strange but have to take all opinions and perspectives onboard. If you have a thesis stick to it and every time there is a new announcement test that thesis against it to make sure it holds up. As Harry Welsh said to Blythe in Band Of Brothers - it’s a game, that’s all. We’re all just moving the ball forward one yard at a time. Just a game. All the best, good luck.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:50:31+10:00">
   <body>Are you still doing the 20% per trade?</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 19:57:16+10:00">
    <body>Yes and no. I fucked up and bought to much EGR. I also think I can run EGR can run well past 20% gain. 

I'm thinking about jumping ship and doing the 20% challenge on the US market and using technical analysis to pick stonks. 

I'm fucking clueless.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-02-25 20:06:08+10:00">
     <body>But we're all cheering you on!!</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 20:08:30+10:00">
      <body>Yeah kinda scary aye. Got like 300 followers. I don't wanna disappoint. Pressure is on aye. Oh yeah I need to release the update.</body>
      <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-02-25 20:11:35+10:00">
       <body>I didn't even know following was possible in reddit!</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 20:14:25+10:00">
        <body>I think half of them see the flair and assume I'm a millionaire.</body>
        <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:26:19+10:00">
         <body>Fuck - you could move markets with that flair. (Please ramp DLC) 😂</body>
        </comment>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:16:04+10:00">
     <body>TA works but real TA not just drawing one line on a chart. Have a look at every stock that has mooned then pulled back or crashed back - RSI over 90% cannot be held for long - one or two days tops so this at least gives you an idea of when to bail or when not to FOMO. US stocks are hard unless you can find someone that really knows US stocks. Yes, they can move far more in a day than our stocks but that works both ways. If you are looking for almost sure thing in US, look at boring uptrend stocks like Microsoft, or NVidia etc. or index trades on SP500 or NDX using TA for support. Just gotta have some patience - which most people don't have. Or YOLO the latest wsb meme.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 20:20:33+10:00">
      <body>I got a group who are big on TA on the us market and they are doing really well. My background is engineering and I like the idea of how TA works and like how they are applying it. I'll play the US market as a medium risk gamble whilst ASX will be the high risk stuff.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Tacomaster33" created="2021-02-25 17:48:58+10:00">
  <body>Nxt with the great result, leggoooo the ride back up begins</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="unknown3901" created="2021-02-25 17:52:01+10:00">
   <body>I sold out at 12.70 but hope it goes up tomorrow. If it stays at the lower 11s I might buy in again</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="matt_step" created="2021-02-25 18:29:47+10:00">
   <body>I’ve got an average buy in that’s still above the SP at the moment 🙈 so yes agree, let’s go lol</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Tacomaster33" created="2021-02-25 20:13:40+10:00">
    <body>Me too 😂</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="logman_aus" created="2021-02-25 17:54:34+10:00">
  <body>Holdings Considered Lower Risk: 0/10

Selfwealth and I seem to have a difference of opinion.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Salty-Ant-8567" created="2021-02-25 18:34:49+10:00">
  <body>Today I converted my boomer portfolio to a ASX_Bets rocket launchpad. Sold all my MP1, SEK, DTC, KGN, NDQ, QAN, TLS shares. Bought RAC and WWG with the proceeds. LKE, LRS, IOU, ZIP, IBG had been bought days back thanks to this sub. Comments please, am I doing this right? Is this the way?!</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-25 18:46:46+10:00">
   <body>I hope so, for your sake. Just be ever aware that - unlike your Boomer stocks, which are 'set and forget' - lots of these penny stonks are far more volatile, and ultra sensitive to announcements, hype, hype trading, etc.

For some of these things you are possibly going to want to sell and buy back in at lower prices as events occur. If you're accustomed to seeing stop-losses, you'll need to take into account that the dips in some of these stocks can be much larger, but not always (or even *often*) points at which you actually would want to exit your position. Indeed, for a lot of this speculative stuff, you'll be wanting to buy big dips, not sell them, particularly when these doors are just profit-taking after announcements.

It's a much more active endeavour.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Salty-Ant-8567" created="2021-02-25 19:03:35+10:00">
    <body>Mate really appreciate the advice, many thanks. I was thinking of not touching these till Easter and see what happened. I’ve told myself to consider any loss as tuition fee paid for a financial literacy course (from the school of ASX_Bets... Go Rockets!!). Will make some moves after Easter. Will keep tuned in here, which is probably gonna make it hard to not touch my portfolio till then. Well, don’t have any more cash to invest till then anyway. Once again, thanks for the advice bro.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Highlander_O7" created="2021-02-25 20:18:11+10:00">
    <body>Great advice for beginners mate, thanks!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="tajid" created="2021-02-25 18:53:44+10:00">
   <body>IBG hasn't moved much though - what's everyone's thought on this? In fact it stayed at 0.029 the whole day today.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Salty-Ant-8567" created="2021-02-25 19:05:54+10:00">
    <body>Yeah! Till yesterday I didn’t think it moved at all, couldn’t figure if there was a halt on it or not.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="aaronrizz" created="2021-02-25 19:18:00+10:00">
   <body>All the memes!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Embarrassed_Peace224" created="2021-02-25 18:12:10+10:00">
  <body>BRN with NaNose detect Covid19 in Exhaled Breath?

I can see the light from the sky</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 18:28:50+10:00">
  <body>Alright, I need y'all to be the bear case for me.
A2M looks like an absolute bargain to me at these prices, and the price will recover as they develop new sales channels and we recover globally from Covid. What am I missing?</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="1234sr" created="2021-02-25 18:37:28+10:00">
   <body>If it looks like a bargain, what is its fair value? How have you decided it's a bargain - just because the price has dropped?  
I know nothing of the business but what are the new channels? What sort of market penetration will they have/competitors?  How do you see the covid recovery as a positive for a powdered baby(?) milk company?  Are there logistics/freight benefits or something you see coming? Do you see increased demand because of more babies, growing wealth of buyers/premium pricing?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Drumsteppin" created="2021-02-25 19:01:30+10:00">
   <body>Alright so here's the DD Ive done on A2M. I was in IGA the other day, buying milk, and the 2L A2 milk was like $4.80 and the generic IGA milk was $2.55. 2.55&lt;4.80, hence I didn't buy the A2 milk. Based on those figures, things don't look too good for the company's sales. I didn't look at baby formula so cannot comment on how that part of the business competes. DYOR, thanks for reading my shitty DD.</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="tob1asmax1mus" created="2021-02-25 19:04:29+10:00">
    <body>People who can afford to pay a premium for a premium product often do so though.</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-25 19:22:21+10:00">
     <body>Buying overpriced milk is like buying overpriced water...

Speaking of which, the world seems to have forgotten Supreme bricks.</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Drumsteppin" created="2021-02-25 19:24:41+10:00">
     <body>That's fair. I was being pretty tongue in cheek before, but do you feel that the company is helping itself by setting that price point, or is it hindering itself? Do you think that part of the business can see growth, either by reducing costs to increase per unit profit from an existing customer base, or advertising/incentivising new customers to start buying the premium milk and hence growing volume? Or has the brand effectively reached its market size for that particular product and is unlikely to see growth unless it starts competing on price and increasing volume? Are competitors offering a similar or better product? Is it for a higher or lower price? 

I haven't researched any of this, but to me I don't see much potential for growth in that arm of the business, as for a lot of people milk is a commodity item, and often no-brand basic milk is good enough. Milk derivative products there is the potential for much more growth, the creation of interesting products, and the ability to have unique marketing. But, the questions I asked above can also be applied to the rest of their portfolio of products. When you look at their products from those perspectives, your investment becomes a bet of "do I believe that the company can attain appropriate growth in some of its markets, and will this growth be reflected in the share price?"</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Scomosbuttpirate" created="2021-02-25 19:20:41+10:00">
   <body>Shit management, sales to China are not coming back any time soon, you'd be better taking a short position the company is that fucked.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Aleckrandall" created="2021-02-25 19:12:10+10:00">
   <body>Shit financial reports, declining sales &amp; profit margins</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-25 19:17:33+10:00">
   <body>Personally wouldn't touch something that is so utterly dependent on China, that's a built-in bear case for me right there 

lotta other stocks out there brother</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="SmashPlayersRretards" created="2021-02-25 20:05:24+10:00">
   <body>they sell fuckin milk, how much do you think people need to drink for it to takeoff</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-25 18:30:32+10:00">
   <body>Nothing. I bought today for $8.88</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Lifeofgordi" created="2021-02-25 18:30:14+10:00">
  <body>Brought in another 50k shares at the DW8 low today! Very keen for this inbound explosion</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-25 18:36:03+10:00">
   <body>Literally already picked what car I'm gonna buy when I sell</body>
   <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="Drumsteppin" created="2021-02-25 18:44:10+10:00">
    <body>A 90s Toyota Camry with 320,000kms on the odo?</body>
    <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="SatansFriendlyCat" created="2021-02-25 18:53:39+10:00">
     <body>And an alcohol interlock. And DW8 sponsorship logos on it.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-25 19:11:19+10:00">
      <body>[removed]</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-25 19:11:20+10:00">
       <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:33:09+10:00">
      <body>I just read their annc - how the fuck is this company even trading?</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-25 18:59:01+10:00">
     <body>Rude</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Drumsteppin" created="2021-02-25 19:04:35+10:00">
      <body>What car then? No body knows if you have $500 in the company or $50,000. A 90s Camry with 320,000kms on it could be a steal if you triple or quadruple bag your $500.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="EvilShogun" created="2021-02-25 19:06:57+10:00">
  <body>Automod 🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-25 19:39:03+10:00">
  <body>IXR resource upgrade tomorrow - prepare for confirmation of MONSTER status !! Such solid buying into the close today, 1 tick off its ATH


Also still running with TMZ and the multi-commodity exposure it has.


Waiting for SRK to wake up from its slumber and hopefully announce mining licence for Iron Ore and near-term cashflow 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-02-25 19:43:40+10:00">
   <body>Are you in PLY?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-25 19:51:37+10:00">
    <body>Yes. That’s my last remaining tech exposure, and only coz I think gaming has a fair bit to run here on the ASX.

Zero BNPL trash for me... 🤮</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-25 17:48:13+10:00">
  <body>IXR resource upgrade report</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Big_Bullfrog8178" created="2021-02-25 17:50:47+10:00">
   <body>Any good?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-25 18:13:25+10:00">
    <body>I dunno it's not out</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="bnplstrategist" created="2021-02-25 18:45:03+10:00">
   <body>When is this due</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-25 19:20:33+10:00">
    <body>Any day now, went up 10% today</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-02-25 19:36:20+10:00">
    <body>Due by end of Feb. Which only leaves tomorrow !!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-25 20:01:03+10:00">
  <body>Had my worst ever one-day performance today - down almost $10k. Would love to claw some of that back tomorrow...</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 20:02:01+10:00">
   <body>Flair holds up.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 20:13:00+10:00">
   <body>It’s been a rollercoaster ride of a week? What caused most of the damage? Or do I already know the answer? 😩</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Fast-Bandicoot7479" created="2021-02-25 20:14:40+10:00">
  <body>Oh dear lord no, no please not a Friday 😖</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="vanillaiceblock" created="2021-02-25 20:18:36+10:00">
  <body>A MILLION days ban for the psychological effects joke hahah, that’s awesome</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="slapperman12" created="2021-02-25 17:49:42+10:00">
  <body>Bph and buy. Simple really 🚀</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:40:30+10:00">
  <body>ASX is slim pickins for good stonks</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Nordvegr" created="2021-02-25 19:23:09+10:00">
   <body>You'd have a fucking skitz time if you were a geologist though.</body>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 19:35:04+10:00">
    <body>Even then, I’m not a fan of waiting years and years for actual money. Kinda like biotech stocks</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Pure_Beautiful_395" created="2021-02-25 18:48:19+10:00">
   <body>IMU</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:56:03+10:00">
    <body>I’d give it a solid 5/10</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Pure_Beautiful_395" created="2021-02-25 19:27:57+10:00">
     <body>That’s honest tbh</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-14" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:42:15+10:00">
   <body>PIL! Have a look at the volume, relisted in ASX today.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:00:02+10:00">
    <body>If you touch this - you deserve to get reamed. It went up mega today to suck in the retards. The power point presentation is just another pump and dump BS hypno spiel. It has all the right pics and figures to suck in the noobs that have no idea - be warned. Yes it could go up and make some people some money but at the end of the day - another scam stock. AVOID.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 18:45:15+10:00">
    <body>Errr I hope you’re not serious, this could be one of the worst stock atm on ASX</body>
    <comment ups="-8" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:48:04+10:00">
     <body>We will wait and see... the boomers on HC are loving it</body>
     <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 18:51:20+10:00">
      <body>That is usually a sure sign of dogshit.</body>
      <comment ups="-1" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:57:44+10:00">
       <body>Will let you know if I make a profit tomorrow or not, if it costs me money I deserve a good teabaggin, if I get some coin off some HC boomers, that doesn't bother me 1 bit.</body>
       <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:29:28+10:00">
        <body>I admit it can make some money as the share price will move. The company itself tho - red flags everywhere. ASX regulations are fucked.</body>
       </comment>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:43:02+10:00">
        <body>I hope you take all their hard earned Boomer cash.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="crabbypattytata" created="2021-02-25 19:23:27+10:00">
  <body>CI1 :(</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Faabs96" created="2021-02-25 19:39:30+10:00">
   <body>CI1 to the moon baby! 🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-25 20:05:48+10:00">
  <body>BPH - financial repot - thoughts please?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-02-25 20:26:43+10:00">
   <body>No one cares. It's all about NOPTA.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-02-25 20:27:41+10:00">
    <body>good talk</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Fostered_meme" created="2021-02-25 17:17:58+10:00">
  <body>My body is ready for another day of red.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="alg1979" created="2021-02-25 17:22:11+10:00">
   <body>Today’s blood is tomorrow’s lube</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="The_Frag_Man" created="2021-02-25 17:21:08+10:00">
  <body>not sure if hide the pain harold, or this is fine dog on fire</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="alg1979" created="2021-02-25 17:21:38+10:00">
  <body>No cunt wants to dissect the BPH announcement right here on my behalf por favor? 💁‍♂️</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Crackersnuf" created="2021-02-25 17:25:35+10:00">
   <body>It’s intriguing. Requesting a trading halt for a new consultant.. could be more to it 🧐</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="spagdoge" created="2021-02-25 17:30:56+10:00">
    <body>Think he means the latest one</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crackersnuf" created="2021-02-25 17:59:36+10:00">
     <body>Didn’t even notice the hy’ly</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 17:28:41+10:00">
   <body>Not sure what to make of part of it. Revenue and losses are up but assist value also up. That's just a quick glance. Normally a report released at the end of the day isnt a good sign</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Baz30066" created="2021-02-25 17:44:15+10:00">
    <body>nah revenue thing is a non issue

They don't have any revenue yet until they sell can BARM and Gas. So it going down to $32k doesn't mean anything - to put into context their market cap is over $100M and they had a capital raise for $9M a few weeks ago. The only revenue they were getting was from interest from loans which they converted into Coritical equity so no longer receive that little bit of interest

Increasing rev will come as cortical and advent energy takes steps forward.  


Half yearly looks pretty standard BPH puts out plenty of announcements so everything in there is already known to the market</body>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 18:39:56+10:00">
     <body>It was a quick glance at the gym haha. 

Yeah that's why I wasn't concern with rev. Overall didn't look bad, not amazing. Interested to see how this affects SP tomorrow.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jakekustardmustard" created="2021-02-25 17:38:34+10:00">
    <body>Revenue is down"</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-25 17:34:28+10:00">
  <body>No more dull weekends. Now I can lose cash on the international markets as well as asx</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 17:54:54+10:00">
   <body>I got cryptos just so I could lose money 24/7. Even better</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-02-25 18:04:43+10:00">
    <body>I’m wrapping my head around that too.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-25 17:50:55+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-25 17:50:56+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Seymourbuttzpls" created="2021-02-25 17:35:10+10:00">
  <body>PFT bounce back incoming</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-25 17:48:02+10:00">
  <body>CHK continues to steadily rise as copper price continues to climb 🚀. Cant move electrons without copper wire boys.</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-02-25 18:22:47+10:00">
   <body>I did at least 17mins of DD on this last night and liked what I saw short term (assays etc.) and long term (BHP takeover?) so I jumped in this morning 

Can’t go tits up</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Oldelpaso678" created="2021-02-25 19:22:18+10:00">
   <body>I wish I had some capital to buy into this. Looks like a good stock.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Randomfeel" created="2021-02-25 18:17:53+10:00">
  <body>Wasn’t really a bad day today. After being in red for the last few days, it’s nice having a breather.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="mehungy136" created="2021-02-25 18:31:40+10:00">
  <body>Lots of YouTube asx pundits saying we just had a market correction? I mean I was a little down but nothing compared to the 15% my portfolio ranked during the GME thing. Did anyone else experience a broader market correction this week? I did not</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="biggunzmcgee" created="2021-02-25 18:35:22+10:00">
   <body>Most of my watchlist was red all week. Thank fuck nothing I hold though. It did look to me like a slight correction</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="notasabretooth" created="2021-02-25 18:35:24+10:00">
   <body>It was almost an intra-day correction until JPow reassured everyone the Fed had their backs.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-25 19:08:17+10:00">
   <body>I got fkd 27% during GME lol</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-02-25 19:14:30+10:00">
   <body>I still have GME and had mentally written it off as a loss, woke up and checked Stake this morning and I was back in the green somehow lol (bought at $75)

A surprise bonus to balance out today and yesterday being red ASX days for me</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-25 20:07:10+10:00">
    <body>Whats ur pull-out game for it?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Highlander_O7" created="2021-02-25 20:25:11+10:00">
   <body>Can you link a few of your favourate pundits?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Solid_Mechanic7436" created="2021-02-25 18:37:41+10:00">
  <body>Can LPD sign a god damn off take agreement, just fucking one, that’s all I want.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ElonzMusc" created="2021-02-25 19:07:15+10:00">
   <body>Im with you bro...they have a few lithium  and ceasium/rubidium offtakes to get signed before June according to timelines. I also own AVZ and still waiting for like 4 other offtakes before June as well. 

To be fair, if LPD announced any price sensitive shit in this current market- price would go backwards. Market is fkn weird atm. Lithium hydroxide price is still climbing up, only a matter of time before lithium stocks are the rockets agian

And to put how fkd our market is....Qantas announces 1 billion dollar loss or some shit and moves up a few good pips</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="n0tNotanaLtaccount" created="2021-02-25 19:28:50+10:00">
  <body>Well AVH is going to eat a bag of dicks tomorrow. Trading halt today to do a CR. Common shares issued at 60 odd cents less than yesterdays close.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-02-25 19:36:01+10:00">
   <body>These guys burn cash and make not much money. Hence why its SP has been stagnating for awhile.
Another market darling fading away into obscurity</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:39:29+10:00">
    <body>Lifestyle company but with the amount of new investors hitting the market - everything old is new again and again and again.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-02-25 19:49:41+10:00">
  <body>“You’re alright boyyy” - Arthur Morgan, willing that EGR stallion on</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="KiwiElonMusk" created="2021-02-25 20:09:38+10:00">
  <body>Another good day for CHK. Results on the way. Copper still flying ! 
Could be huge 🚀🚀</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DogLogik" created="2021-02-25 20:16:21+10:00">
   <body>AND I FUCKING SOLD IT GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH.  


This is what I get for being a paperhanded bitch.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="KiwiElonMusk" created="2021-02-25 20:16:53+10:00">
    <body>Damn ? When ?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DogLogik" created="2021-02-25 20:17:41+10:00">
     <body>3 days ago. Sold for a fuggin loss too.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="KiwiElonMusk" created="2021-02-25 20:20:41+10:00">
      <body>Anything can happen tomrorow dude ! Don’t stress about it 😊 on to the next one</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DogLogik" created="2021-02-25 20:22:41+10:00">
       <body>Oath to that. It'll all work out some day.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:20:40+10:00">
    <body>So buy it back??</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DogLogik" created="2021-02-25 20:22:17+10:00">
     <body>Might just have to.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-02-25 20:26:48+10:00">
   <body>The tears of joy were certainly flowing today. Looked strong as.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="meragy" created="2021-02-25 17:13:01+10:00">
  <body>EGR and VUL. Finally.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="steveydraws" created="2021-02-25 18:14:32+10:00">
  <body>Still hating on AVH 😡</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="n0tNotanaLtaccount" created="2021-02-25 19:35:22+10:00">
   <body>Even more so now they've offered shares under $5.50. Cunts.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-02-25 18:49:55+10:00">
  <body>EGR / RNU are my current picks</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ThatSaucyBoi1993" created="2021-02-25 18:56:47+10:00">
  <body>Delayed reaction to the GDA record half year financials today. $0.1 barrier broken, $1 next. Pappa needs his $5K to turn into a home deposit.

Also keen for some A2 Milk action if it drops closer to $7 range. Solid core for daigou buyers to prop back up come late 2021.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Whatsinacan" created="2021-02-25 19:20:57+10:00">
   <body>Ya massive delay. Was pretty surprised to login and see it up 25%. Any idea why there is such a lag?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ThatSaucyBoi1993" created="2021-02-25 19:31:32+10:00">
    <body>Low cap with no mainstream media interest. Seen this before. Requires people to actually know who GDA are and read their reports instead of seeing Motley Fool screaming STONKS 🚀🚀🚀 and them FOMOing.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Whatsinacan" created="2021-02-25 20:03:28+10:00">
     <body>I will be more in my game next time</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="-Dug" created="2021-02-25 18:57:40+10:00">
  <body>Noob question what do we think DW8 price will do? They’ve just released their half yearly and it seemed relatively positive, worth waiting or jumping on?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Johnnyboii12333" created="2021-02-25 19:38:44+10:00">
   <body>There was some great DD posted and it’s just reaffirming them at this stage, a lot have gotten in at the 0.05 I think read the DDs and read the report and make your own decision. But I know a lot were keen for this report</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Vivalagloria733" created="2021-02-25 19:02:31+10:00">
  <body>Sell MVW buy Asia 

Watch A2M</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="stehroids" created="2021-02-25 19:05:23+10:00">
  <body>Bought rnt this morning and got a nice little bump from it today</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-25 19:15:25+10:00">
  <body>I know this is asx forum but just wanted to say that there is some shenanigans jiu jitsu shit going on again with GME. 200 percent up in germany. Thought this shit died. 

As long as it does not fking affect the wider stock market again.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="ToiIets" created="2021-02-25 19:37:31+10:00">
   <body>Some options have gone up 10000% in a few days. Granted you'd have to have bought them pretty far OTM, but damn a lot of people probably had a crack and became overnight millionaires.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jooyaao" created="2021-02-25 19:38:47+10:00">
    <body>Again ... with some people going to be left burnt at the end</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="SunkDestroyer" created="2021-02-25 19:29:05+10:00">
   <body>Wtaf</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="wherelamboman" created="2021-02-25 19:26:30+10:00">
  <body>Wtf can anyone help me interpret the data from the dw8 half yearly that just dropped? My brain can not compute this many numbers</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:41:47+10:00">
   <body>I read it - I give them 10/10 for making a turd look like a gold nugget.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="StandardAgency" created="2021-02-25 19:28:23+10:00">
   <body>nothing new, nothing bad, on track for the "market" project. Assuming priced in, all my opinion.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="azad_s" created="2021-02-25 19:52:34+10:00">
  <body>COD gonna bring in the tendies over the next 6 weeks 🍗🍗🍗</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snck_Pck" created="2021-02-25 17:01:35+10:00">
  <body>I thought the SRN announcement was positive? What happened?</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="nsjmas" created="2021-02-25 17:05:22+10:00">
   <body>Positive announcements don’t always reflect positive price movements. Buy the rumour sell the news</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="RayGamble" created="2021-02-25 17:05:18+10:00">
   <body>Standard day traders taking their profits...it’ll be back up soon.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Weird-Cell5892" created="2021-02-25 17:03:39+10:00">
  <body>Less go HCH</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-02-25 18:12:05+10:00">
   <body>I sold the bottom of the dip last month 🙃</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-02-25 17:43:45+10:00">
  <body>Srnoc fked me today, ik I should of sold when it hit 3c</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ugliestname" created="2021-02-25 17:46:30+10:00">
  <body>Please NYR you are such a tease</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="is2017goingtobebad" created="2021-02-25 18:08:19+10:00">
  <body>Since US markets have bigger swings, wouldn’t it be a better idea to buy LKE on NYSE? Since it will have more potential to rise massively, for e.g how PLL went to $35 on open from like $2 on NYSE while did little on ASX.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gunit1987" created="2021-02-25 18:55:23+10:00">
  <body>SXA &amp; RLE merging next month to form pure hydrogen. Anyone else looking into this as a clean energy hydrogen play?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Suitable_Energy3671" created="2021-02-25 18:56:53+10:00">
   <body>I’m in SXA. I think it works out best to buy SXA over RLE but I could be wrong!</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="gunit1987" created="2021-02-25 18:57:21+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I agree</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Whitebeltboy" created="2021-02-25 19:24:34+10:00">
  <body>Hold on to your hats boys 10y field up 4%</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 19:52:21+10:00">
   <body>?? 10 yr yield? US 10yr do you mean?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Whitebeltboy" created="2021-02-25 19:55:21+10:00">
    <body>Haha yeah, fuck</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:07:48+10:00">
     <body>They may have seen a 4% drop in price but the yield is not at 4%.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ToiIets" created="2021-02-25 20:09:20+10:00">
   <body>US premarket doesn't seem to care, maybe because the initial 'bond yields rising!' news has already passed we won't have too crazy a time.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-25 19:59:54+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-25 19:59:54+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:11:52+10:00">
  <body>Got a bit of an aut-ape question, wife's boyfriend probably knows but not allowed to ask... , how/where do people find out future dates when companies are to release an announcement?</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Ok-Degree-5548" created="2021-02-25 20:18:00+10:00">
   <body>I reckon you could look at some here 
https://www.commsec.com.au/content/dam/EN/ReportingSeason/February2021/CommSec_Reporting_Season_Calendar_February2021.pdf</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:19:30+10:00">
    <body>Actually pretty nifty sheet. Thanks for that</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-02-25 20:19:18+10:00">
   <body>Ask magic ball. The only annc a company can set a date for is financials and AGM. Everything else must be released to the market immediately the BOD is aware. Well - in theory anyway. You gotta be sucking BOD dick to know before us.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:20:43+10:00">
    <body>I usually ask magic ball on which stonk to go balls deep in... probably factored into that question too</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-25 20:15:31+10:00">
   <body>What. Unless the company gives some timeline, or its a financial report like a quarterly, that would require actual magic.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="UnholyTurkey" created="2021-02-25 20:17:23+10:00">
    <body>Often people being being like announcement due on say 28/2 for XXX company.. quite often not quarterly reports. Wondering which services if any others use to this?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-25 20:12:25+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-25 20:12:26+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-02-25 20:14:50+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-25 20:14:50+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="hk_melb" created="2021-02-25 17:50:55+10:00">
  <body>Any ideas why’s RED5 getting hammered??</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-02-25 19:43:18+10:00">
   <body>Bro RED is fucking cooked. Huge overhead to build KOTH in coming (if they even get funding? Announcement is lagging which should have been sorted already?) 

The losses are insane, the way they hedge they’re gold at darlot is puss and the never ending work on a 30 year old plant to keep it running is going to be taxing on any profits.

Eventually if they wanna keep darlot going they need to find more dirt, underground is raped and they are starting to mine recently discovered open pit mines for fuck all grade and bugger all reserve. If this is enough to keep darlot running there will have to be a major overhaul on the site to keep it operating. 

KOTH is there only hope. It will bounce from this quarterly in the next week or so, just be careful with this one IMO.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-02-25 20:19:10+10:00">
    <body>Yikes glad I got out</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-02-25 20:23:23+10:00">
     <body>If KOTH goes to plan it will be a good site. Was always going to be a plan of mine to play this report buy the dip and sell on the bounce, unfortunately my capital is tied up in another swing trade. 

RED is a long term play if KOTH goes well it should do okay. If not it’s gonna be fucked.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cant_right_good" created="2021-02-25 18:11:56+10:00">
   <body>I only skimmed it but it was not a good announcement they put out today</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="noobinvestin" created="2021-02-25 18:03:22+10:00">
  <body>The only ETF you guys should be buying is ASX. FOOD</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Rum-Ham-Jabroni" created="2021-02-25 18:35:10+10:00">
  <body>After my failure with XST, I really really hope FFG announcement tomorrow is positive.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="martin0000001" created="2021-02-25 19:15:48+10:00">
   <body>You want negative ann, positive has proven to only bring SP down scientifically proven</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="i_reddit_at_reddit" created="2021-02-25 19:42:52+10:00">
    <body>You need to do DD to understand the due date of the announcement and buy when that info becomes available. You then find every sucker buys pre announcement hoping to get a boost and then everyone sells on announcement which brings the price down. That's my opinion after learning the hard way, but I'm still new at it all...</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="BackgroundAgitated98" created="2021-02-25 20:19:20+10:00">
  <body>PIL for the 🚀🚀🚀

Launching in massive market and with tiny market cap. This has heaps to go, welcome to tendie town. 
Take a PIL and you’ll feel better in the morning!!</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-4" downs="0" author="kb-187" created="2021-02-25 20:22:11+10:00">
  <body>What up fools , been into stocks for about 3 weeks now and am down $700 wondering if there’s anyone on here who gives legit information, or what forums or sights should i be looking at to find the knowledge to actually make money on stocks, thank you and go fck urself</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-25 20:23:59+10:00">
   <body>Are you a writer for the fucking motley fool</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-7" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 18:41:17+10:00">
  <body>PIL relaunched on the asx today, the shear trading volume was impressive and it stayed rock solid for the entire day, ready for the next leg up tomorrow and then the launch pad to moon town on Monday!</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-25 19:17:23+10:00">
   <body>The volume doesn't count since they are sub 10c so pretty cheap... Huge float which usually is a red flag for me, I haven't dove deep into them, mind sharing more about them?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 19:35:54+10:00">
    <body>I'm sorry but I'm not going to waste my energy since everyone is hating on me, its a short term trade for me.  I definitely don't think its a good company, juat want to cash in on the speculation, did it with ffg, iou, and ci1, longest one I held was ci1 for 5 days, turned 10k into 30k.  I would love a long term hold but I am struggling to find legitimately good companies.</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-02-25 19:38:30+10:00">
     <body>Ok glad you're just trading the trade. Huge float stocks usually stay flat for a long time without attention</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="debtandregret1984" created="2021-02-25 19:40:16+10:00">
      <body>The volume on this one dollar wise today was also impressive.  More cash than cro, iou, ffg and ci1, have a look.  I think it will get a handbrake pulled on it in the morning.  I need some boomer money 😂</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-11" downs="0" author="AsxInvest" created="2021-02-25 17:11:10+10:00">
  <body>u guys think LRS gonna go back up or keep going down</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-02-25 17:12:37+10:00">
   <body>It will do both....</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-02-25 17:12:10+10:00">
   <body>Lrs has 5 more announcements to come in the next month I believe</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Scomosbuttpirate" created="2021-02-25 17:31:27+10:00">
    <body>They have like another 600 holes to release the assays for still</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AsxInvest" created="2021-02-25 17:12:59+10:00">
    <body>u holding?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="ChilliNoodles68" created="2021-02-25 18:00:20+10:00">
     <body>Yes holding</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="WhiskeyandTequila" created="2021-02-25 17:58:23+10:00">
   <body>Just hold. It’s a solid long term stock, don’t be a paper hands bitch</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Scrofl" created="2021-02-25 17:38:44+10:00">
   <body>Let me just check my crystal ball</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-02-25 17:12:20+10:00">
   <body>Will keep tanking for now imo.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-12" downs="0" author="chaddownunder_" created="2021-02-25 18:59:05+10:00">
  <body>RAC 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-02-25 18:59:06+10:00">
   <body>This isn't being deleted(yet), but we suggest trying harder next time.

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-25" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-02-25 17:01:12+10:00">
  <body>First in best breast</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Rum-Ham-Jabroni" created="2021-02-25 18:35:36+10:00">
   <body>I lol'ed</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-02-25 19:13:32+10:00">
   <body>Lol. 

I really hope this red tide turns but I’m not going to hold my breast  

Harharahrarahahhaa</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
