<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root date="2021-03-03 Wednesday">
<highlights>
 <discussed>
  <mention>LKE (11) HYPE=28, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>PEN (10) HYPE=18</mention>
  <mention>LOT (10) </mention>
  <mention>TOP (9) HYPE=28, TIP=5</mention>
  <mention>IXR (8) HYPE=28, TIP=5</mention>
 </discussed>
 <tip>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-02 17:13:39+10:00">
   <body>LRS - Please do something tomorrow. Maybe in the upward direction this time?

XST/SGC - Continue doing what you did today and I will forgive you for your past sins

RAC - Continue to climb at a slow and steady rate.  I don't care if you break through $4 this week. No rush.

NVX - Have we hit the bottom yet??</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 18:11:43+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>NVX is long term, they have so many divisions and projects from synthetic graphite to anode and cathode material, electrolyte,  single crystal tech and dpmg.... Battery testing, research patents * gasp *, the list goes on. Oh I forgot they're building micro grid batteries too. 

Anyway just hold. The moment you sell it'll launch to the moon.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-02 18:16:55+10:00">
     <body>Yep, will probably be my longest hold. Have no intention of selling this. Pretty excited about this. If the SP continues to drop, I'll just average down.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 18:20:17+10:00">
      <body>Sp will stick at these levels until the SPP is done. Now that the price is below the offering, it likely won't be over subscribed, a shame because they really could have used that money for projects.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-02 19:01:55+10:00" sentiment="TIP 10">
       <body>SPP runs until 22nd. I’d be surprised if the stock doesn’t break back through $2.90 by then</body>
      </comment>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-03-02 19:51:40+10:00">
       <body>Thought they had already over subscribed last week?

*edit*

Herp derp, that was for the institutional investors.  Ignore me</body>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 20:17:33+10:00">
        <body>Correct and at least those guys won't be dumping whilst the SP is below their purchase price.</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-03-02 18:43:54+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>Looking for some knowledge.

Ive been trading TMR a fair chunk over the last year. Its been pre good to me. But i dont understand its current market cap and the sentiment around it.

Current MC - 14/15mil
SP 17c

Gold explorer potentially to be producer within a year.  Major project is the blackdome/elizabeth mine in canada. This was a previously producing mine that shut down due to shit gold prices like a decade plus ago. Currently hitting large quantities of shallow low grade gold in the blackdome area (average value, not good - not bad) and triple digit assays high grade sweet shiz gold in the elizabeth section of the project. Aiming to have a full resource assessment done by mid year, with potential to do a half arsed one as is with the assays its already drilled.


On top of this, it also has a mill on site that wouldnt be more than a few mill to get back up and running. 

So what the fuck is going on with the pump and dumps and massive volatility. Im so confused my smooth brain doesnt get it. I know its  low liquidity and shit atm is a pain but im pretty sure its got more in assets than it does MC and thats wild AF.


any thoughts fellow apes?</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-03-02 18:59:32+10:00">
    <body>Sir this is a casino</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-02 18:14:55+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
   <body>So I'm looking at investing in one of the following and if you're holding one, would be nice to hear ya thoughts.

NTI - Not mentioned much around here but did a CR today to fund for their upcoming human trials. Hoping for it to drift more so that I can get on. Current SP 0.063

VML - Might see it drift a little more and hoping to get it below 0.05 (I know I know, a man can still dream). Current SP 0.062

SPT - I know the BNPL is dominated by Afterpay and Z1p but their recent results don't look too bad. Can definitely see this heading back to the 1.5 mark at some point this year. Current SP 1.110

AGY- Was keen on it but with their report out today, seems as if their production is headed for end of 2022 (read earlier it would be end of 2021) so dunno sorta discouraged me. Still think it has plenty of potential and room to grow. Current SP 0.115</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-02 18:23:08+10:00">
    <body>VML going below 5c is not going to happen sorry mate. Its the beginning of the Ramp up to Production going from Explorer to Producer it may hover in the 6c range for a small time frame but eventually its going to bust out and move up again.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:24:25+10:00">
    <body>Held SPT but got out with some popcorn chicken and so glad I did
Think they've still got $90M to spend but for fk sake spend it !  They are at massive risk of being left behind

AGY. I'm all in</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-03-02 18:34:22+10:00">
    <body>Do some DD on CPV and KTG for safe and ongoing growth.  You might be surprised.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-03-02 19:37:30+10:00">
    <body>NTI is a diamond in the rough - this is one to keep an eye on</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-02 20:22:21+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 20">
   <body>Dripping with anticipation for IXR to come back out of TH with a monster resource upgrade


TMZ went into a TH today for (another) acquisition...so have to wait till Thursday to see what they’re snapping up 


Falling asleep watching SRK do sfa with all their massive potential. It’s starting to drive me nuts. But soon this will pop to the moon and I’ll be able to say - told you so !! 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-02 20:24:25+10:00">
    <body>IXR upgrade is going to be huge. And with how hot rare earths are right now, it will run massively at open.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="MoneyHustard-1" created="2021-03-02 17:34:20+10:00">
   <body>IXR - ohh baaabbbyyy.  
RNU - love you.  
LRS - you're kinda pissing me off but I still love you.  
LKE - thought of selling you but whatevs I'm gonna leave you in my portfolio for 6-12 months and see what you do.</body>
   <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-02 17:50:18+10:00" sentiment="TIP 5">
    <body>LRS is that athletic kid with so much potential but just keeps fucking around</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </tip>
 <hype>
  <comment ups="27" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:21:25+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 18">
   <body>Okay this list was started yesterday, but I want at least 30 items before I email this to the investor relations contact for Peninsula Energy. This is a collective effort to brainstorm ideas for the company to make money because they clearly need our fucking help. 


\#1. Start producing fissile material for Kim Jong Un

\#2. Create an Onlyfans  (credit /u/aj3806)

       - Viral Marketing cum tribute? PENis out for PEN? (credit /u/nyatesy)


\#3. Collaboration with KFC, Glowing tendies for all, we have many willing buyers (credit /u/Goody55)

\#4. Start a pump and dump with Biotech Nuclear medicine rumours (credit /u/catch_dot_dot_dot)

\#5. Sell a radioactive box to make your PENs grow bigger

\#6. Glow in the dark Pokemon cards, new rarity class on top of holo? (credit /u/SunkDestroyer)

\#7. Partnership with ASX:DLC to make PENetrating™ Uranium dildos (inspired from /u/Phishbaron)

\#8. Collaborate in tea making with Putin

\#9. Start organ trafficking with the CCP by encouraging mutagenic growth in "volunteers"

\#10. Open a lemonade stand

\#11. Fraudulently employ workers to steal Stimulus PPP money

\#12. Ask CEO nicely to do some market manipulation   (credit /u/luner124)

\#13. Nucleosynthesis of Lithium from decay products to raid LRS/LKE tendies market share

\#14. Extend Joe BiPEN's half-life and make him run another 4 years (credit /u/check_meat)

\#15. Build Nuclear Bomb powered [rockets 🚀🚀🚀]( https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Project_Orion_(nuclear_propulsion)  and beat Elon to Mars

\#16. Collaboration with Coca-Cola and start making Nuka-Cola with Uranium Glass (credit /u/FameLuck)

\#17. Lobby parliament to stop raping staffers and start building Nuclear plants (credit /u/tony_macaroni123)

\#18. Have CEO Wayne Heili start streaming Fallout New Vegas on twitch (credit /u/ninenet909)

\#19. Watchmen advertisement, stick a PEN logo on Dr. Manhattan's giant PEN?? (credit /u/rom_stoll)

\#20. Uranium laced Fish tackle, glows in the dark, skins the fish before it reaches you? (credit /u/Jenky83)

\#21. Rename the ticker, BBC/BWC, something suggestive of large growth (/u/justarandommoniker)

\#22. Rebuild Texas power grid with Nuclear power, if they don't call them Commie cucks (/u/Hypertrollz)

\#23. Take a lump of Uranium into the US senate, start snorting flakes to prove how safe it is (/u/Pigionbore)

\#24. Lobby for a Uranium state fair in Wyoming, glowing candy floss etc. (/u/Pigionbore)

\#25. Partner with Goop and make Uranium eggs to shove up your cooch (/u/Pigionbore) 

\#26. Wicked Wicked Wings, topped with Uranium flaked seasoning (/u/PowerBottomBear92)

\#27. Make Gluten-free flour out of Uranium somehow??? (/u/PowerBottomBear92)

**Please suggest some more, my brain is numb**</body>
   <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="ninenet909" created="2021-03-02 17:36:07+10:00">
    <body>Have the CEO start streaming Fallout New Vegas gameplay on Twitch</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:39:58+10:00">
     <body>I like it, gotta milk those 12 yr old donos</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Tony_Macaroni123" created="2021-03-02 17:25:36+10:00">
    <body>Convince our government to build some nuclear reactors instead of more fucking shitty coal mines</body>
    <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:27:50+10:00">
     <body>That makes too much sense to actually happen, I'll add it to the list anyway</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="JustARandomMoniker" created="2021-03-02 17:57:23+10:00">
    <body>PEN needs to think bigger. 
Rebrand for ticker BBC or BWC.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Hypertrollz" created="2021-03-02 18:10:38+10:00">
    <body>Convince Texas to go Nuclear for its new grid, unless they are commie loving yellow belly pussies.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-02 18:20:29+10:00">
    <body>I mentally picture this as your gang's mascot: [https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0625/4877/products/231e13df77c9e79579b448f71b186aa6\_1200x1200.png](https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0625/4877/products/231e13df77c9e79579b448f71b186aa6_1200x1200.png)</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Jenky83" created="2021-03-02 17:47:08+10:00">
    <body>glowing squid jigs and fishing lures</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:56:32+10:00">
     <body>Fish would stop struggling before they reach the boat and would already be skinned, very effective</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-03-02 18:25:41+10:00">
    <body>Fuck me! Can you please email this! I would love to see the response. I reckon there could be a whole asx_bets movement here- you tank, expect some fucked up ideas from us!</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:37:13+10:00">
     <body>If we hit thirty items, I'll make a separate post with an email draft for the rest of you bagholding cunts to proof-read</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rom_stoll" created="2021-03-02 17:50:32+10:00">
    <body>Crossover advertisement with Dr Manhattan</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:53:15+10:00">
     <body>That's someone with a giant swinging PEN, good place for a new logo?</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-02 17:54:29+10:00">
    <body>The possibilities of combining 5, 7 and 9 are endless but all hinge on the partnership with DLC. Glow in the dark fleshlights, extra titties, double knobs, Glow in the dark titties, nuke-powered anal intruders, Homer fantasy wear, "chat" line telemarketing and stock pumping/lobbying...</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:55:37+10:00">
     <body>Now here's a real ideas man, you should lobby for a position on the board.</body>
     <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-02 17:57:56+10:00">
      <body>Would do it for DLC options and all the lube I can carry.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="biscobisco" created="2021-03-02 19:31:39+10:00">
     <body>&gt;nuke-powered anal intruders

I like the sound of this, would be helpful with conditioning our collective backsides for the rigours of this current market.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Hypertrollz" created="2021-03-02 18:09:27+10:00">
    <body>What's the play with PEN, hodl till 2024?</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:11:27+10:00">
     <body>Min hold till end of this year, Uranium cycle is on the timescale of 2021-2025, hopefully will have caught on by then</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Pigionbore" created="2021-03-02 19:28:59+10:00">
    <body>Bring a lump of uranium to the US senate. Show them it aint nothin to be afraid of by snorting flakes in front of them.

Lobby for a Uranium state fair in Wyoming to sell some supply and get locals hyped.

Partner with Goop to make Uranium products (Uranium exfoliate soap, Uranium candles, Uranium lump lamp etc)</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 19:38:15+10:00">
     <body>Fuck me you're a natural</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-02 20:01:10+10:00">
    <body>Market yellowcake powder as a new chicken seasoning at KFC

&amp;#x200B;

Sell yellowcake as a gluten-free flour alternative</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 20:11:18+10:00">
     <body>We getting fucking close now, only three left</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-03-02 18:25:10+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>Great time to top up on IHL. Short term stock fluctuations are random! next stop the moon 🌙🚀</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cheeky_cheeseburger" created="2021-03-02 19:23:01+10:00">
    <body>OSA read out due by Mid march  in my opinion...  


topped up again today!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="JDK-Ruler" created="2021-03-02 17:03:47+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
   <body>LKE to the moon or down into the depths of the earth? Who fucking knows what to expect daily.</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-02 17:07:33+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>🚀🚀🚀</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="catch_dot_dot_dot" created="2021-03-02 19:45:09+10:00">
    <body>It's had pretty strong growth, it's definitely not going to the depths. On the other hand, it won't do another quick 100% climb but it's a grower.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="unahbs" created="2021-03-02 17:04:28+10:00">
   <body>Lets make appen happen</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="streit23" created="2021-03-02 17:06:52+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
    <body>It's Appenning tomorrow 🚀</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ManaLra" created="2021-03-02 17:13:40+10:00">
     <body>Out of curiosity how with the FY20 results is this appenning??</body>
     <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="streit23" created="2021-03-02 17:24:10+10:00">
      <body>Most likely not Appenning tomorrow or in the near time but one day it will be back Appenning and I'll be there!! A2M went up over 7% today with no hopes, so why not!!</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="likadong" created="2021-03-02 17:43:55+10:00">
   <body>Balls deep on IHL</body>
   <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-02 18:06:06+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 8">
    <body>Surprised really tbh with them posting that amazing jump in revenue, you'd think it wouldn't be drifting at the very least. Nonetheless, holding firm as this year will bring us tendies no doubt.</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="likadong" created="2021-03-02 18:36:27+10:00" sentiment="HYPE 10">
     <body>Just bought some more @.210 buying my seat on the rocket 🚀</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SkernMannnn" created="2021-03-02 18:10:30+10:00">
    <body>Yesssss! Get it son!

Was thinking about loading up on some more today too!</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-03-02 19:40:33+10:00">
    <body>Tempted to buy in more at this low - also NTI being another weed stock in the low 0.06 however in different avenues.
We’ll see what tomorrow comes in at.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </hype>
</highlights>
&#10;&#10;
<Comments>
 <comment ups="48" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-02 18:17:39+10:00">
  <body>I find the "I like the stock" crap lame and Americanised, we never said that shit here before

but that's just me 💘</body>
  <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-02 18:24:49+10:00">
   <body>Same. I’d like to get rid of “autist” and “retard” too while we’re at it. We aussies can do better than that. Offend everyone instead of just offending some people, ya know.</body>
   <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:32:23+10:00">
    <body>Cunts a much better term, we don't need to import every seppo word</body>
    <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-02 18:52:11+10:00">
     <body>cunt is so versatile, and it's *ours*</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-02 18:39:10+10:00">
     <body>Yeah and then maybe MSM would fuk off and leave us alone.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:40:36+10:00">
      <body>Honestly I'm okay sticking with retards and autists, all the new stuff that sprung up from the GME tards needs to get the fuck outta here</body>
      <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-03-02 19:02:11+10:00">
       <body>Retard could be a bit disparaging to the retard community, don't you think? Cunt isn't really offensive to anyone.</body>
       <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-02 19:53:33+10:00">
        <body>Real retards don't know enough to be offended, it's all the poser retard cunts that are</body>
       </comment>
       <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Yeah_nah_yeah_maybe" created="2021-03-02 19:46:59+10:00">
        <body>I like retard and autist, a lil offensive to to the mentally disabled, but I think it's complimentary to those with autism, myself on a minor scale included</body>
       </comment>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Benny-Kenobii" created="2021-03-02 19:02:30+10:00">
     <body>Just a bunch of cunts shooting darts at the back pages of the fin review</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-02 20:22:35+10:00">
     <body>TISM really got it right with "I might be a cunt but at least I'm not a fucking cunt"</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-02 18:35:59+10:00">
    <body>Yep, totally agree</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-02 18:49:45+10:00">
    <body>agree</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Greeenkitten" created="2021-03-02 18:53:28+10:00">
    <body>&gt; I’d like to get rid of “autist” and “retard” too while we’re at it.

Rebranding /r/ASX_Bets to "Nuffies of the ASX" for the facebook clout?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-03-02 19:40:22+10:00">
     <body>Strong yes to Nuffies or noofies</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Rosencrantz1710" created="2021-03-02 19:40:27+10:00">
    <body>Drongos and/or galahs</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 18:31:38+10:00">
    <body>[removed]</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 18:31:39+10:00">
     <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:42:09+10:00">
   <body>If I see another cunt talking about hedgies, I'm gonna have an aneurism</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 18:45:33+10:00">
    <body>Spazcunt?</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="catch_dot_dot_dot" created="2021-03-02 19:41:52+10:00">
    <body>Every time a stock goes down, there's always people talking about stupid "hedgie" conspiracies. Get fucked.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-03-02 20:06:21+10:00">
    <body>But if no one mentions the hedges shorting a stock how will I know it's being squeezed</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 18:46:43+10:00">
   <body>I don't see it much outside of the pun for LKE. Would be nice to differentiate ourselves from the far more retarded USA</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-03-02 18:18:55+10:00">
   <body>Same</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="35" downs="0" author="UhOhNoOnion" created="2021-03-02 17:44:24+10:00">
  <body>I have lost 6 months salary since being back in the office 2 weeks ago. Worst trade deal in the history of trade deals</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-03-02 17:45:58+10:00">
   <body>Wtf on</body>
   <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Bigzyzz27" created="2021-03-02 17:58:41+10:00">
    <body>PEN.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-02 18:42:54+10:00">
   <body>Still got six months worth of salary left to go!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Toujayjay" created="2021-03-02 18:25:09+10:00">
   <body>Good work keep it up mate haha don't stop there</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-03-02 18:03:57+10:00">
   <body>Oof</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:13:21+10:00">
    <body>Is that the ticker</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="31" downs="0" author="smileedude" created="2021-03-02 19:11:25+10:00">
  <body>Proposed asx_bets lingo based off Simpson's in Australia:

A booting: stocks red. "I copped a booting today" 

Chuzwuzzas: the frog/ booming growth/rockets. "cunts gonna go chuzwuzzas today."

Dollarydoos: tendies

Andy: the fed government. "if Andy passes the regulation I'm copping a booting"</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 19:17:10+10:00">
   <body>OI ANDY, SLAP THE ASK FOR US ON FRIDAY YA LAZY CUNT</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Darcyjay_" created="2021-03-02 19:36:40+10:00">
   <body>This is top tier content</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 19:37:00+10:00">
   <body>Tendies should be snags

Chuzwuzza...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="check_meat" created="2021-03-02 19:54:33+10:00">
   <body>Staring at our stocks pretty sure we can all identify both with Mr Burns tapping his fingers “eeexcellent” and “Doesn’t Gill get a lick?”</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 20:11:13+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 20:11:14+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 18:18:21+10:00">
  <body>People here complaining about LKE only gaining 5% today on news we knew was coming since 20 cents. The material is de risked, it's better than commercial battery grade lithium, it's sustainable and the brine project can be scaled with more pumps if needed. 

Now you know that an off-take is basically guaranteed (you seen the price of lithium carbonate lately?), don't complain if that gets announced sooner rather than later.</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:22:08+10:00">
   <body>What he/she said</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 18:44:46+10:00">
    <body>Did you just assume my gender? I identify as a bottle of 2017 Rockford's basket press.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 19:16:07+10:00">
     <body>Touché</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="martin0000001" created="2021-03-02 18:45:09+10:00">
   <body>The people complaining thought the announcement was gonna say Tesla is partnering up with lke, maybe that would of been up to their standards. People expect to much from a company that’s why they all shit themselves with announcements. Bag holding lke until death 🔝</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="asxist" created="2021-03-02 18:49:46+10:00">
   <body>Yeah a whole lot of goal post moving going on. This new ann was just confirmation of what the market already knew, so no rockets but we'll see strong support around these levels. I don't see an off-take happening until after the final round of battery tests and who knows when that will be at this point.</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 19:13:25+10:00">
    <body>For any other resource I'd agree but this is lithium, every EV maker, grid storage, home storage and consumer battery company is going to want to lock in supply, and soon. The price of lithium carbonate is almost up 60% in the last half year. 

You can replace cathodes and anodes with whatever you want material wise, but you'll always need lithium.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="24" downs="0" author="n0tNotanaLtaccount" created="2021-03-02 19:08:26+10:00">
  <body>Another day of not looking at CommSec till I get home so my coworkers don't see me cry.</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="lululemonhead" created="2021-03-02 19:40:59+10:00">
   <body>Or question your mood swings</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="imamachine87" created="2021-03-02 19:26:20+10:00">
   <body>Lol know the feeling</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="27" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:21:25+10:00">
  <body>Okay this list was started yesterday, but I want at least 30 items before I email this to the investor relations contact for Peninsula Energy. This is a collective effort to brainstorm ideas for the company to make money because they clearly need our fucking help. 


\#1. Start producing fissile material for Kim Jong Un

\#2. Create an Onlyfans  (credit /u/aj3806)

       - Viral Marketing cum tribute? PENis out for PEN? (credit /u/nyatesy)


\#3. Collaboration with KFC, Glowing tendies for all, we have many willing buyers (credit /u/Goody55)

\#4. Start a pump and dump with Biotech Nuclear medicine rumours (credit /u/catch_dot_dot_dot)

\#5. Sell a radioactive box to make your PENs grow bigger

\#6. Glow in the dark Pokemon cards, new rarity class on top of holo? (credit /u/SunkDestroyer)

\#7. Partnership with ASX:DLC to make PENetrating™ Uranium dildos (inspired from /u/Phishbaron)

\#8. Collaborate in tea making with Putin

\#9. Start organ trafficking with the CCP by encouraging mutagenic growth in "volunteers"

\#10. Open a lemonade stand

\#11. Fraudulently employ workers to steal Stimulus PPP money

\#12. Ask CEO nicely to do some market manipulation   (credit /u/luner124)

\#13. Nucleosynthesis of Lithium from decay products to raid LRS/LKE tendies market share

\#14. Extend Joe BiPEN's half-life and make him run another 4 years (credit /u/check_meat)

\#15. Build Nuclear Bomb powered [rockets 🚀🚀🚀]( https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Project_Orion_(nuclear_propulsion)  and beat Elon to Mars

\#16. Collaboration with Coca-Cola and start making Nuka-Cola with Uranium Glass (credit /u/FameLuck)

\#17. Lobby parliament to stop raping staffers and start building Nuclear plants (credit /u/tony_macaroni123)

\#18. Have CEO Wayne Heili start streaming Fallout New Vegas on twitch (credit /u/ninenet909)

\#19. Watchmen advertisement, stick a PEN logo on Dr. Manhattan's giant PEN?? (credit /u/rom_stoll)

\#20. Uranium laced Fish tackle, glows in the dark, skins the fish before it reaches you? (credit /u/Jenky83)

\#21. Rename the ticker, BBC/BWC, something suggestive of large growth (/u/justarandommoniker)

\#22. Rebuild Texas power grid with Nuclear power, if they don't call them Commie cucks (/u/Hypertrollz)

\#23. Take a lump of Uranium into the US senate, start snorting flakes to prove how safe it is (/u/Pigionbore)

\#24. Lobby for a Uranium state fair in Wyoming, glowing candy floss etc. (/u/Pigionbore)

\#25. Partner with Goop and make Uranium eggs to shove up your cooch (/u/Pigionbore) 

\#26. Wicked Wicked Wings, topped with Uranium flaked seasoning (/u/PowerBottomBear92)

\#27. Make Gluten-free flour out of Uranium somehow??? (/u/PowerBottomBear92)

**Please suggest some more, my brain is numb**</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="ninenet909" created="2021-03-02 17:36:07+10:00">
   <body>Have the CEO start streaming Fallout New Vegas gameplay on Twitch</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:39:58+10:00">
    <body>I like it, gotta milk those 12 yr old donos</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Tony_Macaroni123" created="2021-03-02 17:25:36+10:00">
   <body>Convince our government to build some nuclear reactors instead of more fucking shitty coal mines</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:27:50+10:00">
    <body>That makes too much sense to actually happen, I'll add it to the list anyway</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="JustARandomMoniker" created="2021-03-02 17:57:23+10:00">
   <body>PEN needs to think bigger. 
Rebrand for ticker BBC or BWC.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Hypertrollz" created="2021-03-02 18:10:38+10:00">
   <body>Convince Texas to go Nuclear for its new grid, unless they are commie loving yellow belly pussies.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="yothuyindi" created="2021-03-02 18:20:29+10:00">
   <body>I mentally picture this as your gang's mascot: [https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0625/4877/products/231e13df77c9e79579b448f71b186aa6\_1200x1200.png](https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0625/4877/products/231e13df77c9e79579b448f71b186aa6_1200x1200.png)</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Jenky83" created="2021-03-02 17:47:08+10:00">
   <body>glowing squid jigs and fishing lures</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:56:32+10:00">
    <body>Fish would stop struggling before they reach the boat and would already be skinned, very effective</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="aj3806" created="2021-03-02 18:25:41+10:00">
   <body>Fuck me! Can you please email this! I would love to see the response. I reckon there could be a whole asx_bets movement here- you tank, expect some fucked up ideas from us!</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:37:13+10:00">
    <body>If we hit thirty items, I'll make a separate post with an email draft for the rest of you bagholding cunts to proof-read</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="rom_stoll" created="2021-03-02 17:50:32+10:00">
   <body>Crossover advertisement with Dr Manhattan</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:53:15+10:00">
    <body>That's someone with a giant swinging PEN, good place for a new logo?</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-02 17:54:29+10:00">
   <body>The possibilities of combining 5, 7 and 9 are endless but all hinge on the partnership with DLC. Glow in the dark fleshlights, extra titties, double knobs, Glow in the dark titties, nuke-powered anal intruders, Homer fantasy wear, "chat" line telemarketing and stock pumping/lobbying...</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 17:55:37+10:00">
    <body>Now here's a real ideas man, you should lobby for a position on the board.</body>
    <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="phlanoe" created="2021-03-02 17:57:56+10:00">
     <body>Would do it for DLC options and all the lube I can carry.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="biscobisco" created="2021-03-02 19:31:39+10:00">
    <body>&gt;nuke-powered anal intruders

I like the sound of this, would be helpful with conditioning our collective backsides for the rigours of this current market.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Hypertrollz" created="2021-03-02 18:09:27+10:00">
   <body>What's the play with PEN, hodl till 2024?</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:11:27+10:00">
    <body>Min hold till end of this year, Uranium cycle is on the timescale of 2021-2025, hopefully will have caught on by then</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Pigionbore" created="2021-03-02 19:28:59+10:00">
   <body>Bring a lump of uranium to the US senate. Show them it aint nothin to be afraid of by snorting flakes in front of them.

Lobby for a Uranium state fair in Wyoming to sell some supply and get locals hyped.

Partner with Goop to make Uranium products (Uranium exfoliate soap, Uranium candles, Uranium lump lamp etc)</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 19:38:15+10:00">
    <body>Fuck me you're a natural</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="PowerBottomBear92" created="2021-03-02 20:01:10+10:00">
   <body>Market yellowcake powder as a new chicken seasoning at KFC

&amp;#x200B;

Sell yellowcake as a gluten-free flour alternative</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 20:11:18+10:00">
    <body>We getting fucking close now, only three left</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="23" downs="0" author="InexpensiveHat" created="2021-03-02 17:22:46+10:00">
  <body>Tomorrow I will start the day by crying into my hat. Then cry some more into my wife’s boyfriend’s hat. Then, and only then will I have my coffee and proceed to cry into it also. 

Then open up commsec I guess.</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="WhitePinboard" created="2021-03-02 17:51:32+10:00">
   <body>Username checks out</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-03-02 18:06:57+10:00">
   <body>Please let this be the next cum tribute.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="22" downs="0" author="MoneyHustard-1" created="2021-03-02 17:34:20+10:00">
  <body>IXR - ohh baaabbbyyy.  
RNU - love you.  
LRS - you're kinda pissing me off but I still love you.  
LKE - thought of selling you but whatevs I'm gonna leave you in my portfolio for 6-12 months and see what you do.</body>
  <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="NoDuffTrading" created="2021-03-02 17:50:18+10:00">
   <body>LRS is that athletic kid with so much potential but just keeps fucking around</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="21" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-02 17:13:39+10:00">
  <body>LRS - Please do something tomorrow. Maybe in the upward direction this time?

XST/SGC - Continue doing what you did today and I will forgive you for your past sins

RAC - Continue to climb at a slow and steady rate.  I don't care if you break through $4 this week. No rush.

NVX - Have we hit the bottom yet??</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 18:11:43+10:00">
   <body>NVX is long term, they have so many divisions and projects from synthetic graphite to anode and cathode material, electrolyte,  single crystal tech and dpmg.... Battery testing, research patents * gasp *, the list goes on. Oh I forgot they're building micro grid batteries too. 

Anyway just hold. The moment you sell it'll launch to the moon.</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="Whiteknickers" created="2021-03-02 18:16:55+10:00">
    <body>Yep, will probably be my longest hold. Have no intention of selling this. Pretty excited about this. If the SP continues to drop, I'll just average down.</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 18:20:17+10:00">
     <body>Sp will stick at these levels until the SPP is done. Now that the price is below the offering, it likely won't be over subscribed, a shame because they really could have used that money for projects.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-02 19:01:55+10:00">
      <body>SPP runs until 22nd. I’d be surprised if the stock doesn’t break back through $2.90 by then</body>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="citizenerased89" created="2021-03-02 19:51:40+10:00">
      <body>Thought they had already over subscribed last week?

*edit*

Herp derp, that was for the institutional investors.  Ignore me</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="itsdankreddit" created="2021-03-02 20:17:33+10:00">
       <body>Correct and at least those guys won't be dumping whilst the SP is below their purchase price.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="19" downs="0" author="likadong" created="2021-03-02 17:43:55+10:00">
  <body>Balls deep on IHL</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-02 18:06:06+10:00">
   <body>Surprised really tbh with them posting that amazing jump in revenue, you'd think it wouldn't be drifting at the very least. Nonetheless, holding firm as this year will bring us tendies no doubt.</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="likadong" created="2021-03-02 18:36:27+10:00">
    <body>Just bought some more @.210 buying my seat on the rocket 🚀</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="SkernMannnn" created="2021-03-02 18:10:30+10:00">
   <body>Yesssss! Get it son!

Was thinking about loading up on some more today too!</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-03-02 19:40:33+10:00">
   <body>Tempted to buy in more at this low - also NTI being another weed stock in the low 0.06 however in different avenues.
We’ll see what tomorrow comes in at.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="protesttime" created="2021-03-02 17:20:08+10:00">
  <body>Going to top up on zip and DW8 tomorrow. Feel like it's all I need long and short term now. This is what ausfinance meant by diversify right?</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Mysterious-Ball-6640" created="2021-03-02 17:43:36+10:00">
   <body>BNPL &amp; Wine - perfect combination.</body>
   <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="protesttime" created="2021-03-02 18:04:41+10:00">
    <body>It's ironically how I'll end up spending my life if it goes tits up</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="matt_step" created="2021-03-02 18:57:07+10:00">
   <body>Throw a little RAC’s way on the side and that’s a trifecta there. Good luck mate</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="hippoctoraptor" created="2021-03-02 19:28:24+10:00">
   <body>Still a long way for Z1P to go down. Fuck I love that little stonk.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="xxt3nt4c10n" created="2021-03-02 18:25:10+10:00">
  <body>Great time to top up on IHL. Short term stock fluctuations are random! next stop the moon 🌙🚀</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="cheeky_cheeseburger" created="2021-03-02 19:23:01+10:00">
   <body>OSA read out due by Mid march  in my opinion...  


topped up again today!</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="Darcyjay_" created="2021-03-02 18:53:27+10:00">
  <body>I just want green days back</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-03-02 19:38:52+10:00">
  <body>Going to be adopting a new method before I buy into any stock. The Ancient Greek historian Herodotus wrote about a tribe, may have been the Scythians, having a very long piss up and sitting in ‘weed saunas’ before they made a decision to go to war. If after this long session of madness the decision still seemed like a good one, they would go. Now I can’t replicate the weed sauna on account of my living situation but I can quietly drink in my room for a week and then make a decision that way. Will keep y’all posted.</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="lululemonhead" created="2021-03-02 19:48:41+10:00">
   <body>Just sit in the bath and punch a few gravity bongs bro</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-02 19:45:28+10:00">
   <body>Thats the same ancient Greek historian who told me to buy brn in september in my sleep</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 19:47:48+10:00">
    <body>Melvinites Buttfucker of Cyrus was it?</body>
    <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-02 19:48:26+10:00">
     <body>Yes yes that name rings a bell</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Pkan2707" created="2021-03-02 19:45:32+10:00">
   <body>Lol - please drink responsibly</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-03-02 20:01:29+10:00">
   <body>the effects of weed and alcohol are different though...</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rom_stoll" created="2021-03-02 20:21:40+10:00">
   <body>Better suggestion. Jerk off to loss porn to achieve "kenja time" before you buy.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="fjsuwjxjrnf" created="2021-03-02 19:52:17+10:00">
  <body>Tonight’s commonwealth reporting season update.... tech is shit, BNPL is shit, materials is shit... might as well put ya 500K into woolies and pull out 500.01K in 2049</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 17:30:18+10:00">
  <body>I bought MYD at $1.80 through comsec, its now at $1.07, have I made money?

If this trade goes well I'm considering becoming a professional trader.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-02 17:43:10+10:00">
   <body>Do a chargeback claim for a refund. Not as advertised</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-02 18:43:57+10:00">
   <body>Maybe an accountant instead since you're clearly an expert at tax deductions (I'd know)</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 18:56:59+10:00">
    <body>I did a depreciation schedule for my brain, submitted to Ato, offset 100% of my losses. Offset was equal to value of loss at $500. Though does that value my brain at on or about $500? Qik mafs: checks out!</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-03-02 19:09:12+10:00">
  <body>This market is dangerous at the moment. Any strength is getting sold into. Heads down and be careful.</body>
  <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-02 19:15:01+10:00">
   <body>At least JXT finished green lol</body>
   <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="reecej_nz" created="2021-03-02 19:20:30+10:00">
    <body>Indeed. How did you know my portfolio?</body>
    <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-02 19:33:30+10:00">
     <body>Were watching you</body>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Dark_Raiden_" created="2021-03-02 19:55:49+10:00">
     <body>It is well known you are in love with JXT. Inseparable.</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="nsjmas" created="2021-03-02 17:05:52+10:00">
  <body>PEN hammering me with erectile dysfunction. My cock is completely numb at this point</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-02 17:09:05+10:00">
   <body>Will be looking back at this point wishing i topped up more. I'm only one pill away from having an everlasting PEN</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="knickspicks" created="2021-03-02 17:12:41+10:00">
   <body>Checking the daily threads from a couple of weeks ago and seeing the dingdong uranium gang with their emojis</body>
   <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Miscalculated_Stunt" created="2021-03-02 17:21:27+10:00">
    <body>☢️😞</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-03-02 18:57:57+10:00">
    <body>☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️RETARD GANG ALERT☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️☢️ 

🚨🚨🚨MUM SAID IT'S MY TURN FOR TENDIES 🚨🚨🚨</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-02 17:06:52+10:00">
   <body>Literally lol</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="alg1979" created="2021-03-02 17:10:53+10:00">
   <body>Honestly what’s the point of it even being a stock. It doesn’t know what to do</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="PM_me_ur_bingo_nos" created="2021-03-02 17:09:20+10:00">
  <body>What a fucked day when Ass 2 Mouth is the best it gets for me.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="12" downs="0" author="JDK-Ruler" created="2021-03-02 17:03:47+10:00">
  <body>LKE to the moon or down into the depths of the earth? Who fucking knows what to expect daily.</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Mundane_Document8765" created="2021-03-02 17:07:33+10:00">
   <body>🚀🚀🚀</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="catch_dot_dot_dot" created="2021-03-02 19:45:09+10:00">
   <body>It's had pretty strong growth, it's definitely not going to the depths. On the other hand, it won't do another quick 100% climb but it's a grower.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-03-02 18:21:28+10:00">
  <body>So, hypothetically speaking, how would a cum tribute for the entire asx work?</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Guy-Incogneto" created="2021-03-02 18:34:58+10:00">
   <body>Mods are already planning this [here](https://old.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/luz28p/asx_bets_1_year_birthday_celebration/)</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-02 18:29:42+10:00">
   <body>You may need to offer your wife's bf up?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cameltrowe" created="2021-03-02 18:27:47+10:00">
   <body>Depends how much cum your willing to drink</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-03-02 20:04:46+10:00">
   <body>Its called a circlejerk</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-02 20:15:56+10:00">
   <body>As soon as everyone's out of ammo and ready to relax that's when the red begins. We need more then a cum tribe, we need an orgy</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="CoalRenewables" created="2021-03-02 19:36:34+10:00">
  <body>NVX below its Cap Raise so i've just put in an order for 3,500 at $2.89 to add to my existing position. Would wait for the SPP but expect that to be massively oversubscribed and not get the full $10,000 each holder is allowed  


Expecting it to fill in the morning auction at $2.80-2.85 giving me around 14,000 shares at average price of about $1</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="00tts" created="2021-03-02 20:01:53+10:00">
   <body>Jelly mate, nice pumps</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="ninenet909" created="2021-03-02 17:12:33+10:00">
  <body>Another pip on XST would be sick. Also hoping IXR's estimate comes good and people don't sell off nor is it priced in as I entered at 5.1c 😬

Rare earths do be popping off rn tho</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="wattoa" created="2021-03-02 18:12:53+10:00">
  <body>Hoping DW8 keeps making its way up thinking a close above $0.08 is very close</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="JaimeAllNight" created="2021-03-02 18:15:59+10:00">
  <body>Watch DW8 and RAC pull me out of the FOMO shithole I dug for myself with SI6</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-02 18:40:43+10:00">
   <body>SI6 was always a pump and dump. Didn't you get the memo?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="JaimeAllNight" created="2021-03-02 19:06:18+10:00">
    <body>I can’t read, but I’m ready for next time 🤡</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="10" downs="0" author="Salty-Ant-8567" created="2021-03-02 18:25:00+10:00">
  <body>My ASX\_Bets portfolio took a beating but LKE fortunately held the fort. Today's change +$436.11 (1.29%). Green: IBG, LKE.  Red: IOU, LRS, RAC, WWG, Z1P.   
Player-of-the-Match: LKE change today: +$820.70 (LKE makes up biggest chunk of my portfolio, bought $16k worth at $0.387). When LKE goes down, the entire portfolio goes down.

Tomorrow, gentlemen, will be a green day. See you on the other side.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-02 17:02:50+10:00">
  <body>IXR - your time has come.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-02 17:09:21+10:00">
   <body>Praise to the tendies gods</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-02 17:11:45+10:00">
    <body>I’ll be saying some prayers tonight after the beating I copped today.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-02 17:10:05+10:00">
  <body>Hoping IXR breaks through my zipper. Ready to bust a nut</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-02 17:12:36+10:00">
   <body>Cum ritual? Mods? 😂</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-02 17:15:23+10:00">
    <body>unrelated to cum. Just peeling My walnuts</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="TradeTragic" created="2021-03-02 17:23:22+10:00">
     <body>That’s disappointing. Wait what</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Critta18" created="2021-03-02 18:07:06+10:00">
  <body>Just gonna sit and wait for my DW8 tendies</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Hello_Bel" created="2021-03-02 18:27:56+10:00">
  <body>I'm slowly winding down all my positions, looking to buy a house in a month. Fkin depressing if I buy and my shares start sky rocketing.</body>
  <comment ups="14" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:34:25+10:00">
   <body>That's a silly statement.
You have a goal.
You stick to the goal.
You don't look back.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-02 18:36:55+10:00">
   <body>Best decision you can make - buy the house then start again with stocks.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 18:35:08+10:00">
   <body>Just in time for the interest rate hike?</body>
   <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-03-02 18:51:17+10:00">
    <body>What interest rate hike? Federal reserve is locked in on interest rates for another three years. Just lock half ya loan on fixed and half on a discounted if they hike them after 2023</body>
    <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 19:00:54+10:00">
     <body>ok. Thought i heard something today about having to lift soon To curb prop prices</body>
     <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="n0tNotanaLtaccount" created="2021-03-02 19:11:50+10:00">
      <body>Lol, the federal government would literally deliver wheelbarrows full of cash to every house in Australia to keep property prices propped up. All their boomer voters would be our for blood if their precious house valuation dropped.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 19:13:55+10:00">
       <body>We will see if they let prices keep climbing as they look like they will</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="jkphilp" created="2021-03-02 19:03:55+10:00">
      <body>No chance.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
    <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 19:04:48+10:00">
     <body>property - buy when everyone is selling and sell when everyone is buying. Its the same for everything</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="lameanddepraved" created="2021-03-02 19:36:48+10:00">
   <body>I played with part of my property deposit. It was fun. Had to pull most out. Fair chunk went down, some went up. But my property is rock solid, not going anywhere, all mine. Sure I have to keep pumping in mortgage payments, but being able to hang out there in lush nature.... Much more fun than any stock</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="gloriathehippo" created="2021-03-02 17:09:59+10:00">
  <body>WBT - After hours webinar was highly encouraging 

GAL - Drilling results due this or next week

My balls are tingling, hopefully it’s not PEN cancer</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Pandibabi" created="2021-03-02 17:16:44+10:00">
   <body>Whats the status w WBT?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-02 17:13:50+10:00">
   <body>where can i view the webinar TENDI</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="gloriathehippo" created="2021-03-02 20:00:23+10:00">
    <body>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LQGx-bnq-tg&amp;feature=emb\_title&amp;ab\_channel=WeebitNano</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FlyingStonk" created="2021-03-02 20:22:33+10:00">
     <body>Thank you many much will gander</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="throwaway8726529" created="2021-03-02 17:21:32+10:00">
  <body>HCH impending announcement of exploration results. Should be interesting. I don’t hold much, but it’s nice I guess. Edit: I should mention it’s a trading halt. 

Other than that, slow and steady with RAC. I finally set a stop-loss today haha. Risk profile was too high as RAC became 80% of my liquidity. 

Been eyeing off FMG, and now that the prices are better with the dividend sell off it might be the right time.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Possible_Ice882" created="2021-03-02 18:25:03+10:00">
  <body>Going to drink 5 Irish coffees then watch LKE manage to lose 8% by lunchtime... then average up.

Also looking to buy some EGR if it ever goes on discount.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="mikemakesit" created="2021-03-02 18:58:19+10:00">
  <body>Going to top up on TLG, QPM, ASNOC, maybe NVX and RAC if they dip enough and might buy into VML while I wait for IXR results.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 19:08:30+10:00">
   <body>[removed]</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 19:08:30+10:00">
    <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="unahbs" created="2021-03-02 17:04:28+10:00">
  <body>Lets make appen happen</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="streit23" created="2021-03-02 17:06:52+10:00">
   <body>It's Appenning tomorrow 🚀</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="ManaLra" created="2021-03-02 17:13:40+10:00">
    <body>Out of curiosity how with the FY20 results is this appenning??</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="streit23" created="2021-03-02 17:24:10+10:00">
     <body>Most likely not Appenning tomorrow or in the near time but one day it will be back Appenning and I'll be there!! A2M went up over 7% today with no hopes, so why not!!</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-02 18:00:57+10:00">
  <body> IXR will awaken from it's slumber and deliver some tendies.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="catch-10110" created="2021-03-02 17:12:12+10:00">
  <body>Well I won my ban bet but I don’t feel good about it. Sorry LAK rocket gang.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-02 18:20:38+10:00">
  <body>My plan tomorrow? Don't look here or commbank and enjoy my day at work

Can't believe how shit it turned from such a start!</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 18:44:07+10:00">
   <body>Enjoy your day at work??

Why are you here exactly?</body>
   <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="kickrockeitflipflops" created="2021-03-02 19:14:57+10:00">
    <body>To make 15k and invest in an emu farm</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 19:40:14+10:00">
     <body>Fuckin' nice.

It's like living the chicken farm dream... But BIGGER!

🙇</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-02 20:19:04+10:00">
      <body>Emu tendies</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Calm_Lengths" created="2021-03-02 18:32:14+10:00">
   <body>Not sure if i can do that,  i seem to hit refresh at least once a minute...</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="EMHURLEY" created="2021-03-02 18:39:11+10:00">
  <body>*BGL trading halt and appointment of auditor*

Bag holding mode: activated</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cant_right_good" created="2021-03-02 19:53:43+10:00">
   <body>I read that as being an oversight on their part rather than a material fuck up that will cost them... thing dips any more and I'm diving in. Project too good to be this cheap for long</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Phishbaron" created="2021-03-02 20:10:43+10:00">
    <body>Yeah I don't think its gonna have much effect. Depending on the length of suspension it may be beneficial. If the gold spot get s back up in between that time and management add to the fucking resource they promised then everything's gonna be ok.

Am I in denial here</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="cant_right_good" created="2021-03-02 20:16:43+10:00">
     <body>There's plenty more to be found there but I think they've just been focused on the transition to mining it more than expanding inferred material ad nauseum. But that'll come I would imagine. DHEM basically direct detects mineralisation. What a dream</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="mojoblazer" created="2021-03-02 18:28:05+10:00">
  <body>Planning to top up more EXR tomorrow. And that’s it for last month’s salary</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-03-02 19:03:50+10:00">
   <body>Got some more today around 0.255, will look for more dips in the coming days.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mojoblazer" created="2021-03-02 19:21:01+10:00">
    <body>Do you have any particular decision point when buying at a price above your current average?</body>
    <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-03-02 19:28:51+10:00">
     <body>Not really. Was probably a bit emotional, frustrated because it was down around .22 I think yesterday and I wasn’t around. Under opening price is nice. Stock seems solid though, smashed a tonne of beer and watched a few hours of interviews with Neil young a week or so ago before buying in. Late to the party, long way to go, but could be a big thing.</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Snoo_94254" created="2021-03-02 20:08:31+10:00">
      <body>Jumped in at .265 today, has heaps of potential.</body>
      <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AngryTennisDad" created="2021-03-02 20:23:56+10:00">
       <body>Agreed. Hoping these price points will be a distant dream for us snoo later in the year.</body>
      </comment>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="is2017goingtobebad" created="2021-03-02 17:52:58+10:00">
  <body>Didn't even realise I had a order pending . Was surprised when checking email. Thought I scored free stock for a second</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 18:17:21+10:00">
  <body>Dont even see the point of checking the ASX or US futures after the last few days. No fuckin correlation</body>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-02 18:20:36+10:00">
   <body>I think in penny stocks, the actual news (or potential) about certain stock is more relevant than the futures. Like everything was red yesterday and VML was up 36%. Today the US market was great when I checked this morning to only find out most of my stocks end in red. LKE had a great announcement and for that reason was booming until mid day.</body>
   <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-02 18:26:31+10:00">
    <body>Penny stocks are Volatile bastards why alot of people stick to Blue Chips.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 18:22:20+10:00">
    <body>certainly seems that way</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="I_P_L" created="2021-03-02 18:18:20+10:00">
  <body>So how long a hold should PEN be now?</body>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-03-02 18:32:31+10:00">
   <body>About 9 inches.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 18:44:38+10:00">
   <body>I've heard 30 brings great joy</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="n0tNotanaLtaccount" created="2021-03-02 19:13:16+10:00">
   <body>It's always been till the middle of the year at least</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-03-02 18:29:26+10:00">
  <body>Plans are dead might just cry</body>
  <comment ups="16" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-03-02 18:36:14+10:00">
   <body>Save those tears for when they turn off your water :(</body>
   <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-03-02 18:41:12+10:00">
    <body>true then I have to drink my own piss and eat my 2 min noodles raw</body>
    <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="rattled1315" created="2021-03-02 18:43:00+10:00">
     <body>Cook your two min noodles with your piss then bottle the warm piss for later use. Taken from Pg.42 of the Barefoot Investor</body>
     <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-03-02 19:05:24+10:00">
      <body>you have restored hope, Green Wensday here we come! or piss drinking it is</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="-3" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 18:56:02+10:00">
   <body>If you want steady consistent gains go with real estate. This is high risk high reward</body>
   <comment ups="15" downs="0" author="blaze7736" created="2021-03-02 19:03:00+10:00">
    <body>Fuck is AusFinance leaking again? next minute you be telling me about them 0.2% per year rates I can get</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="smileedude" created="2021-03-02 18:46:25+10:00">
  <body>https://imgur.com/jXvXsjn.jpg

HC throwing serious shade</body>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="lululemonhead" created="2021-03-02 19:43:24+10:00">
   <body>Boomers. Raised on eating lead paint chips and driving with leaded petrol. The pinnacle actual retard generation</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Sir_Z" created="2021-03-02 17:18:54+10:00">
  <body>I need to go with my gut more often, was screaming at me to sell LKE and VML this morning but monkey brain decided not to.</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Shawzus" created="2021-03-02 17:41:53+10:00">
   <body>VML will be back up. Didn’t do to bad all things considered</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 17:58:05+10:00">
   <body>Always follow your gut and not the hype</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Fckhedgefunds666" created="2021-03-02 17:26:17+10:00">
  <body>WBT hopefully upward trend after positive webinar, LKE to hold around the .39-.40, NVX well I bloody hope they start an upwards trend. US markets looking like they may finger fuck us but see how it pans out. DYOR TLDR</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="RayGamble" created="2021-03-02 18:11:59+10:00">
  <body>Idk what OAR is doing anymore</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ninenet909" created="2021-03-02 18:13:42+10:00">
  <body>I'm trying to have my folio moon enough to roll it into EXR and forget about it for mass gains over the next 12-24 months. Just hoping it waits at the station for me</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="mojoblazer" created="2021-03-02 18:25:15+10:00">
   <body>Best of luck!! 🚂</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 18:47:49+10:00">
   <body>Love the idea. My plan is similar of I can find something I consider truly worthwhile</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="opal_dude" created="2021-03-02 19:13:28+10:00">
    <body>Have a look at FYI resources with a view to a big return by eoy.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="ssTilley" created="2021-03-02 18:43:54+10:00">
  <body>Looking for some knowledge.

Ive been trading TMR a fair chunk over the last year. Its been pre good to me. But i dont understand its current market cap and the sentiment around it.

Current MC - 14/15mil
SP 17c

Gold explorer potentially to be producer within a year.  Major project is the blackdome/elizabeth mine in canada. This was a previously producing mine that shut down due to shit gold prices like a decade plus ago. Currently hitting large quantities of shallow low grade gold in the blackdome area (average value, not good - not bad) and triple digit assays high grade sweet shiz gold in the elizabeth section of the project. Aiming to have a full resource assessment done by mid year, with potential to do a half arsed one as is with the assays its already drilled.


On top of this, it also has a mill on site that wouldnt be more than a few mill to get back up and running. 

So what the fuck is going on with the pump and dumps and massive volatility. Im so confused my smooth brain doesnt get it. I know its  low liquidity and shit atm is a pain but im pretty sure its got more in assets than it does MC and thats wild AF.


any thoughts fellow apes?</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="peglegsmeg" created="2021-03-02 18:59:32+10:00">
   <body>Sir this is a casino</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Nevelo" created="2021-03-02 18:46:36+10:00">
  <body>Welp. Managed to time the shutdown of Moranbah North just about perfectly and am down 14% on my position so far. I wonder if this is a sign to buy more?</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="fishdoghat" created="2021-03-02 19:39:54+10:00">
  <body>wow, droneshield got massacred today</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="SugeKnight_StandOver" created="2021-03-02 19:54:10+10:00">
   <body>Wow 14.5c , what happened ?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="Muffinstubbs" created="2021-03-02 20:08:13+10:00">
  <body>Woah! We’re half way there. 
Woah! Living on a prayer. 
Hold my shares and we’ll make it I swear. 
Woah! Living on a prayeahhhh

Please mr bovine joni. Bring the green</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="WimpParsnip" created="2021-03-02 20:10:23+10:00">
  <body>Surprised to see a few people wanting to sell or have already sold VML today. Why think about selling now when the real tendies are coming soon?</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-02 20:24:26+10:00">
   <body>Thats the way of the market some are chasing the grass is greener ideal, others have different goals but don't be fooled there are still alot holding strong.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Tony_Macaroni123" created="2021-03-02 17:27:02+10:00">
  <body>When is BD1 gonna stop tanking</body>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="Meh-Levolent" created="2021-03-02 18:04:48+10:00">
   <body>It was 60c 3 weeks ago. It's got a way to go yet.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Uries_Frostmourne" created="2021-03-02 19:21:04+10:00">
    <body>Lol you heartless bastards</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="Scomosbuttpirate" created="2021-03-02 17:42:11+10:00">
   <body>Probs like some time</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="I_P_L" created="2021-03-02 18:19:04+10:00">
   <body>It got waaaay overbought. You're gonna have to give it a while.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-03-02 18:55:22+10:00">
   <body>Do you normally not pull out after ejaculation?</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:14:51+10:00">
   <body>Wish I could downvote more than once</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="6wolfy9" created="2021-03-02 18:02:30+10:00">
  <body>Anyone jumping on the EZZ listing tomorrow? Read that DD and was intrigued.</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-03-02 19:41:08+10:00">
   <body>Considering doing a YOLO on it tomorrow. See how it goes after opening.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="6wolfy9" created="2021-03-02 19:49:13+10:00">
    <body>If you don't mind sharing, what might trigger your YOLO?</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="basicbitchez" created="2021-03-02 20:09:20+10:00">
     <body>I'm hopefully aiming for below IPO price. But anything between 50c and 55c would be nice.</body>
     <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="6wolfy9" created="2021-03-02 20:12:04+10:00">
      <body>fair enough, good luck to you! Lots of optimism in HC as usual for it.</body>
     </comment>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Hypertrollz" created="2021-03-02 18:07:41+10:00">
  <body>6.3% down today after a 3% down day yesterday. FML!</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="lennyau" created="2021-03-02 18:10:31+10:00">
   <body>FML? fuck it, i'm all in.</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="WilyWillow" created="2021-03-02 18:53:03+10:00">
    <body>I think you mean VML.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="tinfoilturducken" created="2021-03-02 18:13:00+10:00">
   <body>23% down but my balls are flying high. Ready for next deployment.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="sulmar" created="2021-03-02 18:14:55+10:00">
  <body>So I'm looking at investing in one of the following and if you're holding one, would be nice to hear ya thoughts.

NTI - Not mentioned much around here but did a CR today to fund for their upcoming human trials. Hoping for it to drift more so that I can get on. Current SP 0.063

VML - Might see it drift a little more and hoping to get it below 0.05 (I know I know, a man can still dream). Current SP 0.062

SPT - I know the BNPL is dominated by Afterpay and Z1p but their recent results don't look too bad. Can definitely see this heading back to the 1.5 mark at some point this year. Current SP 1.110

AGY- Was keen on it but with their report out today, seems as if their production is headed for end of 2022 (read earlier it would be end of 2021) so dunno sorta discouraged me. Still think it has plenty of potential and room to grow. Current SP 0.115</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="Doomkoon4648" created="2021-03-02 18:23:08+10:00">
   <body>VML going below 5c is not going to happen sorry mate. Its the beginning of the Ramp up to Production going from Explorer to Producer it may hover in the 6c range for a small time frame but eventually its going to bust out and move up again.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:24:25+10:00">
   <body>Held SPT but got out with some popcorn chicken and so glad I did
Think they've still got $90M to spend but for fk sake spend it !  They are at massive risk of being left behind

AGY. I'm all in</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="clueaboutmeaning" created="2021-03-02 18:34:22+10:00">
   <body>Do some DD on CPV and KTG for safe and ongoing growth.  You might be surprised.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="rainydaytoast86" created="2021-03-02 19:37:30+10:00">
   <body>NTI is a diamond in the rough - this is one to keep an eye on</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="t20joel" created="2021-03-02 18:48:11+10:00">
  <body>What is happening to Ava picked up a parcel at 515</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="SerbianWolf1389" created="2021-03-02 19:03:40+10:00">
   <body>I wouldn’t worry - it’s a solid company and will find support at these levels before moving up and above the previous highs</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-03-02 19:53:51+10:00">
   <body>Nice one I got in at 5.2 obviously on the bloody way down. Lol oh well I wanted to top up and I did so that’s nice.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Hot_Acanthocephala53" created="2021-03-02 20:11:23+10:00">
  <body>Trouble is both deleveraging in the CFD scene, and the massive Ponzi that is property investment in Australia.

Both sucking the blood out of the market</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Fostered_meme" created="2021-03-02 20:20:44+10:00">
  <body>I’ll just be watching JXT after that cheeky announcement. Maybe next month they will publicly announce who the deals are with.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="Auspat884" created="2021-03-02 20:22:21+10:00">
  <body>Dripping with anticipation for IXR to come back out of TH with a monster resource upgrade


TMZ went into a TH today for (another) acquisition...so have to wait till Thursday to see what they’re snapping up 


Falling asleep watching SRK do sfa with all their massive potential. It’s starting to drive me nuts. But soon this will pop to the moon and I’ll be able to say - told you so !! 🚀</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Crashworx" created="2021-03-02 20:24:25+10:00">
   <body>IXR upgrade is going to be huge. And with how hot rare earths are right now, it will run massively at open.</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 17:29:29+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="4" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 17:29:30+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Massive_Button9434" created="2021-03-02 18:12:17+10:00">
  <body>Hunting for something oversold...</body>
  <comment ups="7" downs="0" author="coastie_trader" created="2021-03-02 18:24:54+10:00">
   <body>TLG</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Drswing69" created="2021-03-02 19:09:15+10:00">
    <body>There's quite a bit of 'short interest' on TLG currently (which is a minor concern)...but a great company from everything i can see.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 19:10:13+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 19:10:13+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 19:52:35+10:00">
  <body>[removed]</body>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 19:52:36+10:00">
   <body>Your Comment has been removed because new accounts post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. It's nothing personal, just take a chill pill, get a Sausage and watch the fun for a while. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="mariellen-asx" created="2021-03-02 20:12:49+10:00">
  <body>WTF &amp; OOF going gangbusters again today. 

topped up Ava as she flew past me in a downwards direction. That’s my money gone for another fortnight. 

Wake me up next week. Lol</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="zupahorse" created="2021-03-02 20:24:49+10:00">
  <body>What do you lot think of NEU? Did a t+2 reccie purchase today to try it on for size.  Might drop in again after some more dd.</body>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="0" downs="0" author="Steponmy92" created="2021-03-02 17:17:26+10:00">
  <body>Consider picking up some FFR. If you have some by Friday then you get free shares in their new listing next week. Stock is pretty solid overall and the price hasn't gone up much since the anouncement. I am hoping for a boost on Friday to sell, but if not I will just get some free shares.

1 share for every 12 in FFR</body>
  <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="staytha" created="2021-03-02 17:55:47+10:00">
   <body>Is there a DD posted in FFR somewhere?</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Steponmy92" created="2021-03-02 18:01:34+10:00">
    <body>It was just one of their announcements on monday.</body>
   </comment>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="CliffyA" created="2021-03-02 18:23:24+10:00">
    <body>Obviously biased but there's a youtube interview with the director
https://www.fireflyresources.com.au/investors-and-media/

Interesting note that the owner of their most interesting site was paid in stock and also invested 1 million into Firefly. So they should have a vested interest in a good return on that land.

I don't know anything tho, this has been my fist stonk purchase late last week.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-2" downs="0" author="PogoStyle" created="2021-03-02 18:56:25+10:00">
  <body>ANW has been oscillating between 0.001 and 0.002 for quite a while. Based on the large volumes I'm guessing people are taking advantage of this to buy low/sell high and double their money each fluctuation.

Downsides to this approach?

Edit: now I know haha. Thanks to commenters below for setting me straight. Downvotes well deserved 😅</body>
  <comment ups="8" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 19:20:06+10:00">
   <body>Me meet outside the GE, I'll double ya money much quicker</body>
   <comment ups="2" downs="0" author="TendiePoweredRockets" created="2021-03-02 20:00:23+10:00">
    <body>Bring your bank to wildy, it’s part of the glitch man I promise.</body>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="6" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-03-02 18:59:52+10:00">
   <body>&gt;Downsides to this approach?

Your money sitting in the fucking buy/sell queue forfuckingever.

How much is 1 million of 0.1c? $1000

Now, how much volume do you see traded daily in the stock?

[let this be your example ](https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/lpk8hu/noob_question_bought_into_anl_recently_at_0001_to/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;utm_source=share)</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="woodbutcher6000" created="2021-03-02 19:00:30+10:00">
   <body>No one is buying at 0.002, im guessing there's a bunch of people stuck in the loop</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 19:38:45+10:00">
   <body>Similar to my VAL - can't sell the fucker when it goes up because every buy is below the constant high</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-11" downs="0" author="Trixster_moon" created="2021-03-02 17:56:51+10:00">
  <body>Surely FIJ has got to start moving soon, its been sideways for 3 months now 🙄 

Apparently someone on hot crapper requested the latest Top 20 holders and a new broker account registered to JP Morgan has recently entered the Top 20 with 3,000,000 Shares, surely thats a good thing right? 🤷‍♂️

(also requested this to confirm)

DYOR</body>
  <comment ups="13" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 18:00:23+10:00">
   <body>Go back to your Boomer containment board</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="3" downs="0" author="timbuckley66" created="2021-03-02 18:21:58+10:00">
   <body>Just means JPM are about to manipulate pricing for their own interests.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="overdose_on_Telfast" created="2021-03-02 18:52:44+10:00">
   <body>It could just be of of JPM's clients, $300k is nothing to those who have accounts with the bank, and this person could just be trading his own money without having to call the trading desk. 

It's a small company with a very small and tight float, just around 25mil shares to be traded on the market. It's currently at 9.9c, two pips up, it makes 5% profit each pip up to whoever gets in at the current price. Combine these factors and you get a good mix of a nice quick trade.

If you're bagholding from the previous pump and dump, get out if it pumps up. It's a penny stock of penny stocks, don't dream big.

There was someone trading $300k parcels in GRR and I imagine the person is sitting on a pretty profit now. $300k is nothing, it's not going to be some "JPM becoming a partner" type of bullshit.</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="newfakeaccount_asx" created="2021-03-02 18:52:45+10:00">
   <body>3,000,000 shares? That's like $300 for FIJ, yeah?</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-22" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 19:06:47+10:00">
  <body>[deleted]</body>
  <comment ups="11" downs="0" author="Mutated_Cunt" created="2021-03-02 19:20:37+10:00">
   <body>Get fucked cunt</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="5" downs="0" author="spank-hair" created="2021-03-02 19:08:59+10:00">
   <body>Nah</body>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="FameLuck" created="2021-03-02 19:34:33+10:00">
   <body>Suck my PEN stock buddy</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
 <comment ups="-25" downs="0" author="Wrong_Ad5180" created="2021-03-02 17:24:22+10:00">
  <body>CGB. Less than 1 cent. 12,500 shares for a $100. I like the stock.</body>
  <comment ups="17" downs="0" author="gboy333" created="2021-03-02 18:03:18+10:00">
   <body>Jesus Christ you’re from Facebook for sure</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 18:10:41+10:00">
    <body>[removed]</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 18:10:41+10:00">
     <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="9" downs="0" author="Oz_2468" created="2021-03-02 17:47:55+10:00">
   <body>So only $8000 to own a million shares. 🤔 always wanted to own a million</body>
   <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="DELETED" created="2021-03-02 18:51:52+10:00">
    <body>[removed]</body>
    <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="AutoModerator" created="2021-03-02 18:51:53+10:00">
     <body>Your Comment has been removed because Account with negative Karma post a lot of spam to /r/ASX_bets. Feel free to post comments elsewhere to get your Karma higher. [Have you read the welcome post or checked out the FAQ/wiki] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ASX_Bets/comments/iqpmfe/welcome_to_rasx_bets/)

*I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please [contact the moderators of this subreddit](/message/compose/?to=/r/ASX_Bets) if you have any questions or concerns.*</body>
    </comment>
   </comment>
  </comment>
  <comment ups="1" downs="0" author="Snoo38972" created="2021-03-02 20:10:20+10:00">
   <body>Cum Guzzling Bastards? Not sure I would trust a company with that name</body>
  </comment>
 </comment>
</Comments>
</root>
